<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-003344</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/27/2023 02:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/27/2023 02:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/27/2023 02:16:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/27/2023 02:16:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>A male and female were in an argument which later turned physical. The female's son stepped in to defend his mother and an altercation ensued between him and the male half. The male suspect stabbed the female's son. During the altercation, the suspect also broke a bedroom door.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 02:48:25</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3143</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 09:19:17</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MDOP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>450252</AddressId>
      <City>MDC381</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 02:48:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 05:07:01</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>450252</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>16945</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Three Notch</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Dameron</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20628</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.365344</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.132263</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/27/2023 02:48:22</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/27/2023 02:48:22</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/31/2023 08:54:45</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 02:48:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-car camera operational, T-6, T-16, and T-19. BWC utilized.  Scene Processing:   I responded to a residence for a reported assault/domestic dispute. While on scene, a juvenile male was located with a hand injury from the assault. The suspect was located in the woods behind the residence and taken into custody. Child Protective Services was contacted and briefed on the situation. A DHR/SSA Form 180, Report of Suspected Child Abuse/Neglect, was also completed and attached to this report. A handle with care notification was also completed. Photographs of the scene and the victims injuries were captured, attached to this report, and uploaded to VeriPic.   This incident occurred within the sight and sound of the juvenile victim.  Damaged Property:   One (1) bedroom door; Value: $100  Total loss value: $100  Narrative:   On January 27, 2023 at approximately 0218 hours, I, TFC Engleman #7197 along with Tpr. Pettyjohn #7329 responded to 16945 Three Notch Road, Dameron, St. Marys County, Maryland 20628 for a reported assault. Tpr. Eckrich #7350 and Tpr. Baden #7152 also responded to assist. While responding, the St. Marys County Emergency Communication Center (ECC) reported a fifteen (15) year old male was cut with the knife at the residence by the callers boyfriend. ECC broadcasted the suspect is identified as Delonte Roger Rivens (B/M DOB: 04/20/1985). Rivens was later identified by his MVA photograph. Lastly, ECC stated Rivens was attempting to leave the residence in a white Hyundai.   We arrived on location and located a Hyundai SUV still in the driveway. While driving down the driveway, Tpr. Eckrich observed a black male exit the rear of the residence and run into the woodline behind the residence. Tpr. Pettyjohn, Tpr. Eckrich, and I then began to canvas the woodline for the black male. The male stated Im here while inside the woods. I then gave the male commands to exit the woods with his hands up, which he complied. Tpr. Pettyjohn then placed the male, Rivens into custody without incident.   St. Marys County Sheriffs Office Deputy Hunsinger P-385 and Deputy Wilhemi P-365 also arrived on scene to assist at the same time. Deputy Hunsinger made contact with the victim, Dayquon Navelle Mason (B/M DOB: 02/05/2007) and observed him to have a bleeding laceration under his left thumb. Deputy Hunsinger applied a tourniquet to Masons upper left arm and quik clot gauze to his wrist to attempt to control the bleeding. Mason was alert and conscious while on scene and was able to speak with police. Ridge Rescue Squad (Ambulance #498) arrived on scene and took over primary care of Mason.   While in the ambulance, I captured photographs of Masons injuries and bandages. Deputy Hunsinger and I asked Mason what occurred tonight. Mason stated his mother, Tanita Dorsena Thompson (B/F DOB: 08/12/1986) and Rivens were in an argument. It should be noted, Mason stated Rivens resides at the residence and had been since the beginning of December, 2022. Thompson was later identified by her MVA photograph. Mason stated he entered the bedroom after he heard Rivens assaulting his mother to defend her. Mason stated he then began hitting Rivens when he produced a knife and attempted to stab him in the stomach. Mason had no visible injury to his stomach, however, there was a hole in his shirt where Rivens attempted to stab him. Mason stated Rivens then assaulted him a second time, this time slicing his skin off of his wrist and hand just below his left thumb. Mason stated he then began actively bleeding and his mother called the police.   While on scene, Tpr. Pettyjohn and I checked the residence with Thompsons permission for the knife used in the assault, however, the knife could not be located. Thompson stated when Rivens left the residence prior to our arrival he left with the knife. The immediate area surrounding the residence and part of the wood line was searched for the knife, however, it was not able to be located. It should be noted, a K-9 unit was contacted and was not available for an article search of the scene.   Photographs of the inside of the residence were taken, attached to this report, and uploaded to VeriPic. Blood was visible in the living room and on the door which was damage during the altercation. While inside the residence, I spoke with Thompson briefly about the incident. Thompson stated she and Rivens were in an argument in the bedroom which turned physical. Thompson stated Rivens pushed her during the argument causing her to fall. Thompson stated Rivens pushed her in the upper torso with both of his hands. Thompson stated she did not have any injuries or bruises. Thompson showed me her upper chest and I did not observe any injuries at that time. Thompson stated her son, Mason then came into the bedroom to break up the altercation and defend her. Thompson stated Rivens then pulled a knife on Mason and stabbed him. I asked Thompson about the broken door on the living floor and if it was done by Rivens and she stated, Yes. Thompson stated she was trying to keep Rivens and Mason separated, however, Rivens broke down the door.   Mason was transported to MedStar St. Marys Hospital for treatment (Reference EMS Run #12001130). At this time, Tpr. Larimer #7397 responded to the hospital to stand by for Masons arrival. Thompson then cleared the scene and followed the ambulance to the hospital. Tpr. Eckrich also responded to the hospital to interview Thompson and Mason again about the incident and collect written statements. See Tpr. Eckrichs supplemental report for further witness/victim statements from Thompson and Mason.   At 0305 hours, Tpr. Pettyjohn read Rivens his Miranda Rights and he knowingly waived. Tpr. Pettyjohn asked Rivens what happened tonight. Rivens explained he and Thompson were having a misunderstanding and an altercation occurred. Rivens stated he and Thompson were pushing on each other and Mason came in to stop the altercation. Rivens stated Mason began punching him and hitting him, at which point he was brought to the ground and Mason was choking him. Rivens could not give any details on how Mason was choking him. Rivens stated Mason told him he was going to kill him and that no one hurts his mother. Rivens stated he was having trouble breathing and Mason let go. Rivens stated he then blacked out, however, he stated he just does not remember what happened. Rivens stated the last thing he remembers is someone stating the police were coming. Rivens had no further information to provide.   Rivens was then transported to the St. Marys County Detention Center where he was charged with First Degree Assault, Two (2) count of Second Degree Asssualt, and Malicious Destruction of Property  $1,000. Rivens was held pending a hearing with the District Court Commissioner. It should be noted, Rivens told the Detention Center staff he had consumed alcoholic beverages this morning, however, he did not say how much. A PBT was not offered.   It should be noted, Rivens adult son was on scene of the incident, however, neither he or his son would provide his information. Thompson stated Rivens son did not witness the incident.   A handle with care notification was completed for the juveniles involved in the incident.   At 0327 hours, Sgt. Oles #5857 contacted Child Protective Services to brief them on the incident. Sgt. Oles made contact with Megan McCaskill and she was notified of the incident. The DHR/SSA Form 180, Report of Suspected Child Abuse/Neglect, was also completed and forwarded to Child Protective Services. A copy of the form has been attached to this report.  Case closed by arrest.  All of the above events occurred in St. Marys County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 06:14:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7197</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 07:44:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7350</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baden</LastName>
            <FirstName>Craig</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7152</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>LARIMER</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kimberly</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7397</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pettyjohn</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7329</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Engleman</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7197</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5857</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Warrenfeltz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6510</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Engleman</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7197</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Engleman</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7197</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492727</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1420</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/27/2023 02:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1420</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 06:19:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7197</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/27/2023 06:22:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492727</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/27/2023 02:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 06:19:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7197</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/27/2023 06:22:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492727</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3 4025</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/27/2023 02:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3 4025</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 07:46:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7197</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 07:46:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 06:19:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>367322</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rivens</LastName>
               <FirstName>Delonte</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Roger</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/20/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2023 06:17:27</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D453</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rivens</LastName>
               <FirstName>Delonte</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Roger</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/20/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D453</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2023 06:17:27</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6229</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Hil Mar</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>District Heights</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20747</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2980</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.899218</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.841254</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>609</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2440</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 07:47:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 07:47:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>36</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 06:24:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:29</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>367323</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Thompson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tanita</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dorsena</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/12/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2023 06:23:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Thompson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tanita</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dorsena</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/12/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2023 06:23:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>16945</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Three Notch</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Dameron</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20628</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3206</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.365343</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.132263</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>538</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7668</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 06:25:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>15</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 06:25:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>367324</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mason</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dayquon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Navelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/05/2007 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2023 06:24:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mason</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dayquon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Navelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/05/2007 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2023 06:24:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>16945</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Three Notch</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Dameron</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20628</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3206</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.365343</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.132263</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 07:46:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 06:27:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7197</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 07:47:21</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) bedroom door. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>555</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>100</PropertyValue>
         <Value>100</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242332</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>WHI</PrimaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/27/2023 06:46:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/27/2023 06:46:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/31/2023 08:54:45</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 06:46:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Body Worn Camera and In-Car Camera Operational T-16.  SCENE PROCESSING:  One MSP Form 76 Written Statement, from victim, Tanita Thompson. One MSP Form 246 Domestic Violence Supplement, from victim, Tanita Thompson.  NARRATIVE:  On January 27, 2023 at 0216, I responded to 16945 Three Notch Rd Dameron, St. Marys County, Maryland 20628 for a reported domestic dispute. The St. Marys County Emergency Communications Center advised the suspect had cut the complainants 15-year-old son with a knife.   Upon arrival, I made contact with victim/complainant who was identified by her MVA photograph as Tanita Dorsena Thompson (B/F DOB 08/12/1986). Thompson advised the suspect Delonte Rodger Rivens (B/M DOB 04/20/1985) cut her son, Dayquan Navelle Mason (B/M DOB 02/05/2007) with a knife. While on scene, Thompson advised her and Rivens were in their bedroom in an argument about infidelity. Rivens believes Thompson has been cheating on him with another guy from work. Thompson advised during the course of the argument, Rivens shoved her to the ground, by placing both of his hands on her chest and extending his arms. Thompson advised that is when Mason came into the bedroom to protect her from Rivens. Thompson advised Mason and Rivens then got into a physical altercation and Rivens cut Mason with a pocket knife. Thompson advised Rivens always carries a blue pocket knife with him.   Due to the seriousness of Masons injury, I was unable to interview Mason while on scene. Mason was transported by EMS to St. Marys Hospital, located at 25500 Point Lookout Rd Leonardtown, St. Marys County, Maryland. I responded to the hospital for further interviewing.   Upon arrival, I made contact with Thompson again to further interview her. Thompson again advised me her and Rivens were in their bedroom in an argument about infidelity. Rivens shoved Thompson to the ground. Thompson advised Mason could hear her fall to the ground. Thompson advised her bedroom door was locked, so Mason used his school ID and slid the ID between the door and door jam in order to unlock the door. Upon Mason entering the bedroom, he got into an argument with Rivens. Thompson advised Mason was defending her and asking Rivens why did he hit his mom. Thompson advised at that time, Rivens and Mason got into a physical altercation, which went from the bedroom to out in the living room. Thompson advised both Rivens and Mason were punching and hitting each other. Thompson advised Mason picked Rivens up and threw him onto the couch. Thompson advised she was able to break up the fight and get Rivens back into the bedroom. Thompson advised she closed the bedroom door behind her. Thompson advised Rivens was angry and upset because he got his ass kicked by a 15-year-old. Thompson advised Rivens then ran through the bedroom door, breaking it, attacking Mason with a knife. Thompson advised she did not see Rivens with the knife in his hand, however she said Rivens always carries a blue pocket knife with him. Thompson advised she heard Mason start yelling and screaming that Rivens just cut him with a knife. Thompson advised Rivens then left the residence in a white Hyundai Santa Fe and she called 911. Thompson advised after being on the phone for serval minutes with 911, Rivens returned back to the residence in order to look for his cell phone. At that time, the police arrived and Rivens left out the back door, where he was apprehended a short time later.   While speaking with Thompson, I did not observe any physical injuries on her body. Thompson advised me her and Rivens have been in an intimate relationship for 6 months and have been living together at the above address for approximately 4 months. Thompson completed an MSP Form 76, Written Statement. It should be noted Thompson advised me she did not want to write down all of the details of the incident, she rather tell me the details verbally, which was captured on my body camera. Thompson also completed an MSP Form 246, Domestic Violence Supplement. I contacted the on-call Southern Maryland Family Advocate, which Thompson declined to talk to, however asked if they could follow up with her tomorrow.   I made contact with Mason, he advised me that Thompson and Rivens had been arguing and he heard commotion coming from the bedroom. Mason advised he could hear Thompson crying from inside the bedroom. Mason advised he grabbed his school ID and used it to open up the bedroom door due to it being locked. Mason stated when he got into the bedroom, he started asking Rivens why did he hit his mom. Mason advised he and Rivens got into an argument. Mason advised Rivens then charged towards him and they get into a physical altercation in the living room. Mason admitted to picking up Rivens and throwing him onto the couch. Mason stated he was on top of Rivens and they were both punching each other. Mason advised me that he had his right hand around Rivens lower neck and collar bone holding him down onto the couch. Mason stated he did not choke Rivens nor was he trying to choke Rivens. Mason stated he realized that he needed to calm down so he got off of Rivens. Mason advised Rivens then got up off the couch and went back into the bedroom. Mason advised Rivens came back out of the bedroom and charged towards him again and cut him with a knife. Mason stated he did not realize Rivens had a knife until he was approximately 5 feet from him and by then it was too late and Rivens cut Mason on his left hand. While speaking with Mason, I did observe a severe laceration to Masons left hand. Due to his injuries and medical treatment Mason had received, Mason was unable to complete an MSP Form 76, Written Statement.  Thompson and Mason were provided with the case number and advised on how to obtain a peace/protective order. This concluded my portion of the investigation. TFC Engleman remains the primary investigator for this incident.  All events occurred in St. Marys County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 06:47:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 03:55:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5857</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7350</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/30/2023 13:48:43</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/30/2023 13:48:43</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/31/2023 08:54:45</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP3143</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 13:48:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>  On Monday, January 30, 2023 at approximately 1334 hours, I called the victim, Ms. Thompson. Ms. Thompson advised me she got a Temporary Protective Order this morning at District Court. Ms. Thompson said she hasnt had any contact with the suspect. Ms. Thompson said she spoke with Marcus from the Southern Maryland Center for Family Advocacy (SMCFA) and I encouraged her to stay in contact with them for victim services. I also encouraged Ms. Thompson to talk to the St. Marys County States Attorneys Office. Ms. Thompson said her son is doing better, she said her son was taken to Union Memorial Hospital in Baltimore, MD. Ms. Thompson reiterated the sequence of events captured in the initial report/supplement. Ms. Thompson said she was fearful for her son, she didnt want to think about what could have happened had he not raised his hand to defend himself from the attack. Ms. Thompson said her son had his muscle and skin sewed, hes in a brace, however, he doesnt have any restrictions. Ms. Thompson said she does have a bruise on her arm which she discovered while at the hospital, but shes unsure how it occurred.   Ms. Thompson told me shes been together with the suspect since the end of August, early September 2022. Ms. Thompson said they dont have any children together, she became upset while we spoke, she questioned herself as to letting the suspect move in to her house so quickly. Ms. Thompson said there were no indications up to this point that it could have gone so bad, she said the suspect and her son got along well and arguments between her and the suspect never escalated to anything like what happened. Ms. Thompson said she packed the suspects belongings and took them to his sisters house. Ms. Thompson confirmed the suspects 20 year old son was present, however, she said he wouldnt say anything. The suspects son has since left her residence. Ms. Thompson said there is no reason the suspect should be at her home. I asked Ms. Thompson if the suspect was drunk, she said he was, they had been taking shots of Amsterdam vodka. Ms. Thompson said they were in bed together and the suspect was accusing her of infidelity.   Ms. Thompson said she has not had any contact with Child Protective Services, however, her sons football coach (Deputy Muschette) had responded to the hospital to meet with them. I informed her of the handle with care notification that was sent as well.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP3143</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 13:49:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP3143</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/30/2023 14:08:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5857</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Linger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3143</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>