<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002261</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/19/2023 07:00:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/19/2023 07:00:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/19/2023 07:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/19/2023 07:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Execution of a search warrant</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 11:10:32</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3267</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/01/2023 14:57:42</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>582240</AddressId>
      <City>MDC103</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 11:10:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 12:52:16</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>582240</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>6800</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Aviation</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Baltimore</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.64624</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.16559</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>GLEN BURNIE - BARRACK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/19/2023 11:10:28</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/19/2023 11:10:28</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40J</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/01/2023 12:22:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 11:10:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>NARRATIVE:  On January 21, 2021, Law enforcement at the JFK Mail Branch intercepted two packages intended for OG at 4917 Midwood Ave, Baltimore, MD (TARGET ADDRESS), and both contained a firearms suppressor which is controlled by the following any device for silencing, muffling, or diminishing the report of a portable firearm, including any combination of parts, designed or redesigned, and intended for use in assembling or fabricating a firearm silencer or firearm muffler, and any part intended only for use in such assembly or fabrication. (18 U.S.C.  921(a)(24). Under the national firearms act, the making of a silencer must be approved in advance by ATF. Unlicensed persons must file an ATF form 1, application to make a firearm, pay a $200 making tax, and comply with all other provisions of the law prior to making the firearm. Approval of the form 1 results in registration of the silencer to the maker. Subsequent transfers of the registered silencer must be approved in advance by ATF. In addition, defense articles cannot be imported into the U.S. from China because of section 27 CFR  447.52(a) of the Arms Export Control Act. (18 U.S.C.  921(a)(24). The firearms suppressor was ultimately seized. Also listed on the packages was a phone number 443-847-4520. Law enforcement issued a subpoena for the subscriber information to T-Mobile for 443-847-4520 and it was listed as Tony K JOSHUA of the above TARGET ADDRESS.  On July 10, 2022, at 10:26 PM, Baltimore, MD City Police (BPD) responded to 4917 Midwood Ave, Baltimore, MD, (TARGET RESIDENCE) in reference to a service of a protective order Case #0101SP042302022.  Upon arrival BPD spoke to the victim who produced a protective order issued by the court commissioners office Case#0101SP042302022 due to a previous domestic related incident between the victim and JOSHUA. BPD advised JOSHUA of the reason for their visit and the terms of the protective order which included that JOSHUA must vacate the premises of 4917 Midwood Ave, Baltimore, MD, 21212 until the court date for this case. JOSHUA left the premises as directed.  On August 4, 2022, Law enforcement at the JFK Mail Branch intercepted one package intended for Tony J at the TARGET ADDRESS which contained two firearms suppressors which is controlled by the following any device for silencing, muffling, or diminishing the report of a portable firearm, including any combination of parts, designed or redesigned, and intended for use in assembling or fabricating a firearm silencer or firearm muffler, and any part intended only for use in such assembly or fabrication. (18 U.S.C.  921(a)(24). Under the national firearms act, the making of a silencer must be approved in advance by ATF. Unlicensed persons must file an ATF form 1, application to make a firearm, pay a $200 making tax, and comply with all other provisions of the law prior to making the firearm. Approval of the form 1 results in registration of the silencer to the maker. Subsequent transfers of the registered silencer must be approved in advance by ATF. In addition, defense articles cannot be imported into the U.S. from China because of section 27 CFR  447.52(a) of the Arms Export Control Act. (18 U.S.C.  921(a)(24). The firearms suppressor was ultimately seized. Also listed on the packages was a phone number 443-847-4520. Law enforcement issued a subpoena for the subscriber information to T-Mobile for 443-847-4520 and it was listed as Tony K JOSHUA of the above TARGET ADDRESS.  A review of JOHSUAs criminal history revealed he has numerous arrests and has one pending criminal case for assault 1st degree. CONVICTIONS: -2006, Anne Arundel County, MD: Possession of MJ, Resisting Arrest, Probation -2007, Baltimore, MD: Handgun on person, Probation -2007, Baltimore, MD: Possess Forgery Documents, 6 Months jail -2009, Baltimore, MD: Resisting Arrest, Probation -2013, Baltimore, MD: Assault 2nd Domestic Related, Probation On August 4, 2022, at approximately 1:48 PM, law enforcement drove by the TARGET RESIDENCE and observed a silver Audi 4 door car bearing MDLP: 3FC0425 (R/O: TONY KEVIN JOSHUA Jr., Address: 4917 MIDWOOD AVE BALTIMORE, MD 212124526, DOB: 1983-05-16, Driver License: J200799465371, VIN: WAUDF78E76A198424) parked out front of the residence.  On November 28, 2022, at approximately 12:14 PM, BPD was dispatched to 229 N. Eutaw St for a reported family disturbance and upon arrival BPD spoke with the victim and a witness. The victim stated her husband, JOSHUA had been verbally and physically aggressive with her. The victim stated she has been married to JOSHUA for the last 2 years and for the duration of their marriage it had been constant problems.  The victim stated she had family come in from out of town for Thanksgiving to include a cousin identified only as Russel A and yesterday, JOSHUA, surprise punched Russel in the face.The victim called her father about the incident, and he advised that he was going to come to their house (TARGET RESIDENCE) to see what the problem was. The victim advised when JOSHUA found out he retrieved a handgun, waved it around, and made various statements that he would shoot her father. No further incidents occurred, and the victim left the location with her father. The victim was then relocated to a safe location by her father for her and her childrens safety.  The victim returned to her home this morning to get her children ready for school. The victim did so because she believed being away for the night would have given JOSHUA time to regain his composure and cool off. However, JOSHUA was still angry and after sending the first two children to school, and they began to verbally argue with each other. The victim stated they continued to argue, and JOSHUA eventually went downstairs and retrieved a black semi-automatic handgun. JOSHUA aimed the handgun on the right side of her head and taunted her. After taunting her, JOSHUA displayed that the handgun had been unloaded the entire time but stated he wanted her to know what he was capable of. The victim stated JOSHUA returned the handgun to where he got it and proceeded to take his son to school. The victim contacted the cousin who went to the residence, and they left. The victim advised she had previously sought a protective order but failed to follow through because she thought they could work things out. The victim showed BPD at the scene photographs of several firearms that JOSHUA had in their house to include two handguns and a rifle.  In late 2022, law enforcement issued a subpoena for records to E-bay for JOSHUAs purchase activity which revealed he completed over 30 separate orders of varying firearms parts including but not limited to firearms barrel kits, slides assembly kits, handgun night sites, bullet magazines and polymer handles starting in December 2020 and his last order was due to arrive on January 2, 2023. While these parts are not illegal to order and receive, they are indicative of manufacturing firearms as once the parts are composed and fully assembled can form a fully functional non-traceable firearm.  In early 2023, law enforcement served a subpoena on KM Tactical for order history related to JOSHUA which revealed he had firearms related items shipped to the TARGET ADDRESS in 2021 which included a stainless Glock 26 barrel, parts for a Glock 26 Generation 3 Frame Kit Polymer 80, Glock 26 Upper Slide parts kit, and a Polymer 80 frame.  Based on the information above a search warrant was authored and signed by an honorable Anne Arundel County Judge. On January 23, 2023 the Maryland State Police Special Investigative Section and Homeland Security executed the search and seizure warrant at 4917 Midwood Ave Baltimore MD 21212. Investigators knocked and announced for several minutes with no contact at the front door. After several minutes and a neighbor advising investigators that nobody was home, entry was made into the residence. Upon entry and deeming the residence secure, a methodical hand search was conducted of the residence. The following items were located during the search:  1) One suppressed black Walther P 22 handgun with an inserted magazine containing 11x .22 caliber ammo (serial # WA259246) located in the basement ceiling utility room. 2) One .22 caliber magazine located in a basement work area/desk. 3) One Glock barrel located in basement work area/desk. 4) One .22 caliber high capacity magazine located in basement work area/desk. 5) Multiple rounds of shotgun shells, .22 mm ammo and one .9 mm ammo located throughout the residence.  All the evidence was seized by myself, Corporal Choe and transported to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie barrack for processing. The Maryland State Police Gun Center was contacted regarding the arrest and all recommended charges were advised by the Gun Center.  A warrant will be requested for Joshua and I request this case remain open pending the service of the warrant.  All events occurred in Baltimore City, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:45:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6042</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 12:30:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Domico</LastName>
            <FirstName>Raymond</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0557</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Choe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Chul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6042</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491644</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>01</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1106</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/19/2023 07:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1106</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:17:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6042</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 11:17:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491644</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>01</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1285</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/19/2023 07:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1285</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:19:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6042</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 11:19:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:28:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368384</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Joshua</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tony</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kevin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/16/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/07/2023 11:26:59</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Joshua</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tony</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kevin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/16/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/07/2023 11:26:59</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:28:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:17:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6042</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 11:17:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:32:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6042</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 11:44:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>610</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>WA259246</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243030</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>Walther</Make>
         <Model>P 22</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:34:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6042</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 11:34:18</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Shotgun shells </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>424</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243031</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>5</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:35:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6042</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 11:35:08</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>.22 caliber short </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>424</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243032</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>4</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:36:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6042</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 11:44:23</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>.9 mm </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>424</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243033</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:38:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6042</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 11:44:34</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>1 x .40 caliber magazine, 1 x .22 caliber magazine and 1x .22 caliber high capacity magazine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>ACC</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243034</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>3</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:39:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6042</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 11:39:47</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Glock barrell</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>ACC</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243035</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6042</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 11:40:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6042</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 11:40:37</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>silver suppressor </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>ACC</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243037</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>