<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-029878</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/24/2023 13:02:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/24/2023 13:02:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/24/2023 12:51:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/24/2023 12:51:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop that led to a DWI arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/24/2023 13:02:20</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0392</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 10:19:20</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>District Heights MD, 20747</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>707714</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 07:34:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/22/2023 14:48:45</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>707714</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Marlboro Pike</StreetName>
         <City>Distict heights</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20747</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.9042</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.85736</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/24/2023 13:02:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/24/2023 13:02:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/25/2023 10:19:22</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/24/2023 13:02:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>L-41 is equipped with an MVR this incident was also recorded with my body-worn camera.  Defendant: John William Harris Date of Birth: 03/04/1958 Date of Arrest: 08/24/2023 Time of Arrest: 1300 hours MD License #: NO LICENSE DUI #: 23-  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES   Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on December 5th-8th, 2022.  Trained in administering Preliminary Breath Tests through the Maryland State Police Forensics Science Division on December 9, 2022.  Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through the Baltimore County Police DepartmentsTraffic Training Team on May 15-16, 2023.  Vehicle in Motion (Phase 1):   I, Trooper Stacey #7390, of the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack was conducting traffic enforcement in the area of Silver Hill Road and Marlboro Pike in Prince Georges County Maryland, when I observed a white Ford Explorer bearing DC GF3212 in front of my vehicle. A METERS/NCIC check revealed that the vehicles registration was expired since 02/2020. At this time I initiated a traffic stop on this vehicle and the vehicle pulled to the right shoulder.  Personal Contact (Phase 2):  Upon my drivers side approach of the vehicle I identified the driver as John William Harris (B/M, DOB: 03/04/1958). Harriss eyes were glassy and bloodshot. There was a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I noticed a brown paper bag with a can in it, stuffed between the drivers seat and the center console. Harris had his right leg up trying to cover the can up. I asked Harris to show me the can and when he did, it was a 16 oz. can of Natural Ice. I felt the can, and it was cool to touch which led me to believe Harris just started consuming it. I asked Harris multiple times if he had consumed any other alcoholic beverages prior to driving, and he said no. However, he later told me he had a mini (liquor) before leaving home. I asked Harris to exit the vehicle and perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which he agreed. Once Harris exited the vehicle I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath and person.  Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3): The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of the highway. The weather was clear and approximately 80 degrees. Lighting conditions were daylight. The ground was level and free of any debris. Harris was wearing flat heeled shoes. Harris appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible signs of injuries.  I asked Harris the following questions: Medical Conditions: Sciatic nerve pain Glasses or contacts: Glasses (not present)  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from his eyes. Harris was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. Harris pupils were of equal size and showed equal tracking.  Harris displayed the following clues:    Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eye  WALK AND TURN TEST (4/8 clues observed) Prior to Harris performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Harris was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and to touch heel to toe on an imaginary line. Harris was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat as his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Harris was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Harris was instructed to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Harris was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around. Harris was again explained and demonstrated the series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series, Harris was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. Harris advised he understood the test.  Instructional Stage: Nothing to report  Walking Stage (1st set of nine steps):     margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Missed heel to toe   margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Stops the test   margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Uses arms for balance  Walking Stage (2nd set of nine steps):     margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Misses heel to toe   margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Uses arms for balance   margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Actual steps taken, takes 10 steps   ONE LEG STAND (could not complete) Prior to Harris performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down by his side while the instructions were given. During the test he was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start, once the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Harris advised he understood the instructions given.  Harris could not complete the ONE LEG STAND due to his nerve injury. He attempted it however it could not be completed.  ARREST: Based off of the following, I had reason to believe Harris was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:    Odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath  Eyes glassy and bloodshot  Open container in arms reach  Clued observed during field sobriety  Harris was arrested at 1300 hours, transported to the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack. At approximately 1322 hours, Harris was read the DR15 Advice of Rights played aloud via the MVA website English audio recording. Harris agreed to take the intoximeter test at 1329 hours. The test was given by Cpl Rogers #5660 with results of .03. Harris was given the appropriate citations and all pertinent paperwork and released to his friend at 1402 hours. All of the above events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 07:44:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 16:19:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rogers</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dominique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5660</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stacey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7390</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519327</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/24/2023 12:51:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 07:34:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 07:34:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>65</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 07:41:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 16:18:24</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386264</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Harris</LastName>
               <FirstName>John</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/04/1958 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 07:40:06</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Harris</LastName>
               <FirstName>John</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/04/1958 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 07:40:06</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1213</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>SE</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>34th</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>washinton</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20019</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 07:41:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 07:41:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 07:41:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 07:34:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 07:34:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156514</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 07:43:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 07:43:08</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FMEU74E37UA72088</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2007</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>XPL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DC</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>GF3212</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/18/2023 09:37:09</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/18/2023 09:37:09</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/25/2023 10:19:22</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/18/2023 09:37:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INTOX SHEET ADDED VIA ATTATCHMENT</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/18/2023 09:37:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/18/2023 09:37:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0392</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stacey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7390</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>