<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-019002</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/28/2023 00:27:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/28/2023 00:27:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/28/2023 00:11:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/28/2023 00:11:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Briana Danielle Carpenter.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 00:27:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/12/2023 08:09:52</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN EXPY/ RACETRACK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 00:27:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 15:15:15</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>EXPY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.170578</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.38053</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 E/O 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB/ 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 PRIOR 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MERGING OFF OF 90 INTO OCEAN PINES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB BETWEEN BRIDGE AND OCEAN PINES EXIT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB PAST 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11083-11086 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1296-1352 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/28/2023 00:27:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/28/2023 00:27:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/12/2023 08:00:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 00:27:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Briana Danielle Carpenter [Subsequent Offender] Maryland SOUNDEX: C-615-098-135-645 Breath Test Result: 0.17 DWI Citation #: 4NN0J79 DWI MVR/Body Cam #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-019002 (Axon View XL Software).   TROOPER CERTIFICATES / TRAINING / SPECIAL ASSIGNMENTS  1. Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. 2. Certified SFST Instructor. 3. Chemical Breath Test Operator. 4. Graduate of the University of Marylands DUI Institute. 5. Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. 6. Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). 7. Trained in Cannabis Impairment Detection (Maryland State Police). 8. Assigned to the Berlin Barrack V Special Enforcement Team (focusing exclusively on DUI enforcement) from October 2017 - June 2022.   NARRATIVE   -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION  On 05-28-2023 at approximately 0011 hours, I (Corporal J. Ruiz #6312), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating marked MSP vehicle V-15 in the area of Maryland Route 90 westbound on the Assawoman Bay Bridge (Ocean City). At that time, I observed a sedan also traveling westbound on the Bridge. There was a truck and an SUV in between my patrol vehicle and the suspect vehicle, but that did not obstruct me from observing the following on the suspect vehicle:   ASSAWOMAN BAY BRIDGE  1. The vehicles left tires were directly on top of the solid yellow center double line on two (2) occasions. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane each time.   ST. MARTINS NECK ROAD  2. The vehicles left tires were directly on top of the solid yellow center line near the guardrail on two (2) occasions. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane each time.   PRIOR TO THE ST. MARTIN RIVER BRIDGE  3. The vehicles left tires crossed (1 tire width) the solid yellow center line near the guardrail on two (2) occasions. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane each time.   ST. MARTIN RIVER BRIDGE  4. The vehicles left tires were directly on top of the solid yellow center double line on one (1) occasion. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane.  After crossing the Bridge, the truck which was in between my patrol vehicle and the suspect vehicle pulled over into the right shoulder area.   BETWEEN MILE MARKER 7 AND THE MARYLAND ROUTE 589 OVERPASS  5. The vehicles left tires were directly on top of the solid yellow center line on three (3) occasions. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane each time.  6. The vehicles right tires were directly on top of the solid white shoulder line on two (2) occasions. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane each time.   ADDITIONAL OBSERVATIONS   7. The vehicle failed to maintain proper lane position due to pronounced and excessive weaving (alternately moving toward one side of the lane and then the other) during the entire duration of my observations.  8. Total distance traveled was approximately 5.02 miles.    DWI INDICATORS / REASON FOR STOP  The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHSTA) published a The Visual Detection of DWI Motorists booklet in March 2010. The research revealed that DWI cues related to problems in maintaining proper lane position include:  1. Weaving 2. Weaving across lane lines 3. Drifting  All of the above DWI indicators were exhibited by the sedan prior to my initiating a traffic stop on the same vehicle.   TRAFFIC STOP  I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle, initiating a traffic stop on MD Route 90 westbound just west of MD Route 589. The vehicle was a white 2003 Chevrolet Monte Carlo bearing Maryland Registration 4Z0012.   -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT  I made contact with the driver via the driver side door, and I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested the drivers license and the registration card to the vehicle. The driver immediately stated: I was on my phone. The driver handed me a DR-15A Form and a Maryland drivers license. The driver was identified as Briana Danielle Carpenter by her Maryland drivers license. I asked Carpenter where she was traveling from, and she responded: Work.    As Carpenter spoke, I made the following observations:  1. I intentionally observed her eyes to be glassy and bloodshot.  2. Carpenter displayed a glazed look/expression on her face as she interacted with me.  3. Carpenter was wearing a black polo shirt with an Alley Oops logo on the left chest area. I asked Carpenter what her job position was at Alley Oops, and she replied: Im a manager.  4. When asked how much she had to drink earlier in the evening, Carpenter advised: Ive not had any.  5. When asked for a reason as to why I could smell the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from inside the vehicle, Carpenter responded: Its in my car. Its in a cup. And thats from last night. But Ive not had any.   I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Carpenter.   I later returned to the Chevrolet and requested Carpenter exit the vehicle and walk to the front of it, to which she complied. While at the front of the vehicle, I continued to speak with Carpenter. I restated to Carpenter what she had advised me upon initial contact  that she was traveling home from work and that she had not consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to driving. Carpenter acknowledged: Yes.  During my second interaction with Carpenter, I observed the following:  1. As Carpenter spoke, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I informed Carpenter that I wanted her to perform field sobriety tests which she agreed to submit to.    -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING  STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder area. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and vehicle headlamps. Weather was clear and approximately 46 degrees. I asked Carpenter if she had any significant medical issues with her eyes, arms, or legs which would prevent her from performing the field sobriety tests or if she had taken any medication prior to driving. Carpenter responded: No and Im on Suboxone. Im on Vyvanse. Carpenter appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, or any limb ailments.  Carpenter was wearing a black polo shirt, tan pants, and black/white Vans shoes.   **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**   1. Carpenter displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   2. Carpenter displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  3. Carpenter displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.   **WALK AND TURN: 4 of 8 clues**  1. Carpenter missed heel-to-toe on steps 5 and 6 during the first series. Carpenter missed heel-to-toe on steps 1, 8, and 9 during the second series. All misses were of more than half an inch.   2. Carpenter took 8 steps during the first series, which was contrary to my instructions.  3. Carpenter did not complete the turn in a satisfactory manner, turning to the right which was contrary to my instructions.  4. Carpenter was unable to maintain a straight line and stepped off the line on all steps during the second series.    **ONE LEG STAND: 3 of 4 clues**  1. Carpenter put her right foot down on count 9.   2. Carpenters body swayed to the left and right on count 15.  3. Carpenter raised her arms for balance (higher than 6 to her sides) on count 15.   ADDITIONAL ANNOTATIONS REFERENCE FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS // ADDITIONAL TESTING  One Leg Stand (OLS):  A. At no point during the test did Carpenter look down at her raised right foot as instructed. Instead, she looked out directly in front of her.  **ALPHABET  COUNT TESTS**:  Both tests were completed satisfactorily.   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Carpenter the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Carpenter submitted to a PBT with a reading of 0.18 BrAC.    ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Carpenter was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Driving vehicle in a negligent manner which caused it to commit 12 lane violations in addition to excessive weaving  DRIVING SKILLS IMPAIRED. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot. * Glazed look/expression on face. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. * My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests.  * PBT reading of 0.18 BrAC.  I determined that Carpenter was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in her system that adversely affected her ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the persons ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Carpenter under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0025 hours on 05-28-2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Carpenters mouth for any foreign objects and none were found.    ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)  Carpenter was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Carpenter was given her Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form (played through the patrol vehicles laptop speakers). A copy of the DR-15 Form was placed directly in front Carpenter, attached to the sun visor. At the conclusion of the audio version, I verbally re-explained the drivers license sanctions and penalties (section printed in red) to Carpenter. Carpenter stated that she understood her Advice of Rights and agreed to submit to a breath test at approximately 0045 hours on 05-28-2023.   TRANSPORT  Carpenter was subsequently transported to the Berlin Barrack for processing. During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Carpenter continued to be strong.   **INTOXIMETER RESULT**:  Prior to the breath test, I observed Sergeant D. Harper #1464 visually check the inside of Carpenters mouth for any foreign objects. None were found.  The breath test was administered by SGT Harper at approximately 0106 hours on 05-28-2023, and two (2) sufficient samples of Carpenters breath were obtained. The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of 0.17 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.   RELEASE  Carpenter was released to a sober driver at approximately 0130 hours on 05-28-2023 hours.   SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER DETAILS  A check of the E-tix system revealed that Carpenter was previously charged with DUI on one (1) occasion:  1. 03-21-2023 (Wicomico County)   CHARGES  Carpenter was charged with the following citations:  1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (4NN0J79) 2. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol Per Se (4NP0J79) 3. Driving Vehicle While Impaired By Alcohol (4NQ0J79) 4. Failure To Drive Right Of Center (4NR0J79) 5. Failure To Obey Designated Lane Directions (4NS0J79) 6. Negligent Driving (4NT0J79)   Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 15:29:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 17:10:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508436</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 15:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 15:14:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 15:17:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508436</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 15:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 15:14:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 15:17:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508436</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 15:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 15:14:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 15:16:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508436</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 15:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 15:14:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 15:16:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>25</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 15:14:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378544</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Carpenter</LastName>
               <FirstName>Briana</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Danielle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/18/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 09:04:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C615</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Carpenter</LastName>
               <FirstName>Briana</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Danielle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/18/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C615</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 09:04:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12623</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Shell Mill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>62</SubNumber>
               <City>Bishopville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21813</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.186763</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.42578</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>614</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7204</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 15:19:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 15:19:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 15:15:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 15:15:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153625</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 15:20:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 15:20:49</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2G1WX12K139154777</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2003</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MOC</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4Z0012</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>