<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044305</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/15/2023 10:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/15/2023 10:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/15/2023 10:45:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/15/2023 10:45:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic road rage incident leads to an assault taking place involving mace</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/15/2023 10:56:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 17:53:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DIS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>717505</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/15/2023 10:56:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 02:46:00</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>717505</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I/L I-695</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RAMP</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Pikesville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21208</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>AVE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.6858</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.39567</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/15/2023 10:56:34</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/15/2023 10:56:34</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/12/2024 06:32:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE PROCESSED-ORIGINAL</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/15/2023 10:56:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/12/2024 06:32:33</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP MARKED VEHICLE R-42 NOT EQUIPPED WITH MVR // INCIDENT WAS CAPTURED ON TROOPERS BWC  VIDEO REQUESTS CAN BE MADE TO SGT. TWARDOWSKI AT ( text-decoration:underline"&gt;JOSEPH.TWARDOWSKI@MARYLAND.GOV)  SUSPECT: Robert Wayne Weckesser  DOB: 08/06/1990 ADDRESS: 705 WASHINGTON AVE, CLARKSBURG, WV 26301-2828 (Harrison County)  VICTIM:  Joshua Ryan Tievy 02/06/1996  ATTACHMENTS:   Witness statement  Photos of victim  Photos of victims truck   margin-left:8px"&gt;Photo lineup (submitted into evidence)   NEIGHBORHOOD CHECK: A check of the surrounding area including businesses were checked but no sight of the suspects vehicle. A lookout of the suspect and vehicle was provided to the Baltimore County Police Department.  NARRATIVE: On Friday, December 15th, 2023, I TFC. Howard #7278 of the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack was on routine patrol in full uniform operating my marked police vehicle. At approximately 1038 hours, the emergency dispatcher provided a BOLO for a vehicle described as a black Dodge Durango traveling on the inner loop in the area of Reisterstown Road driving recklessly. Approximately two minutes post the previous lookout, the dispatcher provides us with another lookout involving the same vehicle. The black Dodge Durango now allegedly threw an object, possibly a soda can at another vehicle still on the inner loop I-695 in the area of Stevenson Road. At approximately 1045 hours, I received a call to respond to the ramp from the inner loop I-695 to Greenspring Avenue (ex 22) for suspicious conditions. The caller reported multiple vehicles stopped on the ramp potentially spray-painting one another.   At approximately 1055 hours, Myself, Trooper Hunt #7356 and Trooper Pezold #7512 began canvassing the area. I then located a white Ford F-150 bearing a Maryland Registration of (9FM2319). I observed a white male standing outside the vehicle near the driver side rear of the truck leaning forward on the bed of the truck appearing to be in agonizing pain. I approached the man, introduced myself to him, and questioned him on what just occurred. I identified him as Joshua Ryan Tievy, DOB: 02/06/1996, W/M by his Maryland drivers license. Tievy informed me he was involved in a road rage incident where this black Dodge Durango was operating recklessly, cutting other motor vehicles off, driving on the shoulder and harassing him. The Durango repeatedly drove alongside Tievy and rolled his window down continuously cursing at him telling him to pull his vehicle over for unknown reasons. Tievy photographed the rear registration plate of the Durango, which displayed a West Virginia registration of (FC10277). Tievy began taking the exit ramp to Greenspring Ave. The Durango overtook him pulled in front of him then slammed on breaks. Tievy applied his breaks firmly, locking his breaks up to avoid striking the Durango. Tievy stated, a white male described as a larger male approximately 510, 230 lbs wearing a black jacket and blue jeans exited the Durango, ran back to him shouted, Stop following me! Pulled out a black handle of what appeared to be bear mace and doused the side of his face, back of his head  neck, side window and truck. Moments later, the suspect sprinted back to his truck, fled the scene and accelerated aggressively onto Greensrping Avenue.  I called for medical personnel to evaluate Tievy. Medics arrived at the scene a short time later and began providing the necessary treatment. Ultimately, Tievy refused to be transported to the hospital. I asked if he would be willing to return to the barrack to provide a written statement and to be interviewed further, to which he agreed.   We arrived at the barrack at approximately 1138 hours. Tievy provided a detailed statement outlying the entire incident from beginning to end.  I arranged a photo lineup to identify our suspect. Sergeant Iman #5709 and I properly explained the instructions on how this next step of the process will be conducted. It must be noted, Tievy did not observe the photos being put together or did he look at any of the pictures prior to the photo array. Sgt. Iman presented 6 photos. One being the registered owner of the black Dodge Durango who is a potential suspect and the other 5 were random men matching the description of our person of interest. The first picture was the registered owner Robert Wayne Weckesser. Tievy paused on Weckessers picture, hesitated then stated no however his no was not strong and sound. The other 5 photos Tievy quickly said no they were not the guy who sprayed him and was adamant of it. We asked if he needed to review the photos once more, he stated, No. We asked him if anyone of the pictures presented to him resembled the person who sprayed him. He stated, #1 looks familiar, but I am unsure. It must be noted the photos we used are Motor Vehicle Administration drivers license pictures, so it is possible the photographs are dated. However, according to Tievys initial appearance description of the suspect he gave 510  230 pounds. Weckessers MVA records show he is approximately 510  220 pounds  At this point, I had reasons to believe Mr. Robert Wayne Weckesser is in fact our suspect. I checked the areas of the two Baltimore addresses he has on file 1930 Bell Ave, Baltimore, MD 21227 as well as 7209 Gough St, Dundalk MD, 21222 in attempt to locate the vehicle. The vehicle was not located. I then utilized a law enforcement database to obtain a working cell phone number which I had negative results. I contacted the West Virginia State Police and requested their assistance. WV Troopers responded to his residence and informed him to give us a call.   I conducted a phone interview with the witness who made the call to 911. I introduced myself to him and informed him the reason for the call. I identified him as Richard Bruce Frankle, 12/12/1956. Frankle informed me traffic speed was reducing on the inner loop I-695 heading towards Greenspring Avenue he was in the right lane, this is when he observed a white ford truck driving down the shoulder maybe in an attempt to flee someone. He took the exit to Greenspring Ave and traffic was stopped due to heavy traffic congestion. As soon as he turned the corner midway through the ramp, he observed a white male spray a huge cloud of substance at the person in the White Pickup truck. He described it to appear like a sizeable cloud of chemicals that emits from a fire extinguisher. He then watched a white male sprint to a black SUV and leave the scene.  On Sunday, December, 17th, 2023, at approximately 1535 hours, I received a call from a gentleman identifying himself as Robert Weckesser. I introduced myself to him and informed him I was conducting an investigation. Weckesser insisted he would love to help with my investigation to get his name cleared up and exclude him from my investigation. At 1537 hours I verbally advised Weckesser of his Miranda Rights over the phone. Weckesser decided to waive his rights and continue speaking with me. I asked him if he recalls being anywhere near the Pikesville area on Friday, December 15th he declined stating he was not. I then asked the following questions, along with his responses. Does anyone beside you have access to your vehicle? No Does anyone else drive your vehicle? No one but me Was your vehicle previously stolen? No Is your black Dodge Durango your only means of transportation? Yes Is there any reason you commute to the state of Maryland? Yes, I come there every first week of the month to get my kids Are you in current possession of your Durango Now? Yes sir Did you lend your vehicle to anyone recently? Not at all Weckesser voluntarily made a statement saying, I dont have any damage to my vehicle at all, I did not hit anyone or make contact with another car and I can provide you pictures if you need me to I replied with yes could you email me the photos. Seconds later Weckesser stated, Actually sir I do not wish to answer any more questions and I believe its in my best interest to contact my attorney because I dont know what I am not supposed to say or what I can say, and I know yall are trying to charge me. At 1543 Weckesser invoked his 5th amendment rights to remain silent. At this moment, all questions were ceased. I provided my contact information and email to Weckesser to provide to his lawyer.   On December 18th, 2023, at approximately 1556 hours I was contacted by his lawyer and he stated his client will not be answering anymore questions and if we have enough to charge his client then to do so and inform him, so he can have his client turn himself in.  All above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/23/2023 13:54:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/23/2023 13:56:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hunt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7356</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Iman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5709</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Howard</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles </FirstName>
            <InternalID>7278</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533782</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 5200</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/15/2023 10:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 5200</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 03:44:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 03:44:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533782</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>01</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>42</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/15/2023 10:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2024 01:49:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 02:49:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 01:51:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>54686</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Tievy</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ryan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/06/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2015 20:17:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Tievy</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ryan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/06/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2015 20:17:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1220</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>LEAFY HOLLOW</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>MOUNT AIRY</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.17837549400109</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.373269799147266</Latitude>
               <SubBeat>MT AIRY</SubBeat>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>672</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2731</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/02/2024 01:51:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 01:51:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/02/2024 01:51:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 01:51:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/02/2024 01:51:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 01:51:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>67</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 02:56:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 03:28:05</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396471</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Frankle</LastName>
               <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bruce</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/12/1956 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 02:56:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R263</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Frankle</LastName>
               <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bruce</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/12/1956 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R263</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 02:56:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Red Maple</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Owings Mills</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21117</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.77752</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.45177</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>812</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9700</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 03:28:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 03:28:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 03:25:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 01:50:25</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396473</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Weckesser</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/06/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 03:05:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W226</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Weckesser</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/06/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W226</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 03:05:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>705</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Washington</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Clarksburg</City>
               <StateCode>WV</StateCode>
               <Zip5>26301</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-80.3474</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.28011</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/02/2024 01:50:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 01:50:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/02/2024 01:50:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 01:50:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>160384</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>VI</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2024 03:38:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 03:38:20</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/02/2024 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FTEW1E83FFC25902</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>F15</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>LL</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>160310</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2024 03:40:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 03:40:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C4RDJDG6NC106824</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>DUR</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>WV</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>FC10277</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/03/2024 06:56:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/03/2024 06:56:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/12/2024 06:32:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>FAILED VALIDATION</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/03/2024 06:56:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/12/2024 06:32:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On December, 1st, 2023, I, TFC. Howard #7278 of the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack typed an application for statement of charges for the subject Robert Wayne Weckesser, DOB: 08/06/1990 and presented it before a district court commissioner of Baltimore County. Commissioner Hall #8124, provided me with an arrest Warrant for Weckesser which has been linked to the attachment section of this report.  I request this case remain open pending warrant service..  All above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/03/2024 06:58:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/04/2024 22:50:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dunlap</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6273</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Howard</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles </FirstName>
            <InternalID>7278</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>