<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013169</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/14/2023 00:37:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/14/2023 00:37:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/14/2023 00:19:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/14/2023 00:19:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Brittany Lee Smack.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 00:37:30</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 09:27:13</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN EXPY/ RACETRACK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 00:37:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 12:12:29</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>EXPY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.170578</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.38053</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 E/O 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB/ 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 PRIOR 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MERGING OFF OF 90 INTO OCEAN PINES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB BETWEEN BRIDGE AND OCEAN PINES EXIT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB PAST 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11083-11086 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1296-1352 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/14/2023 00:37:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/14/2023 00:37:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/23/2023 08:19:03</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 00:37:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:46</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Brittany Lee Smack [SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER] Virginia SOUNDEX: A61256070 Breath Test Result: 0.11 DWI Citation #: 4M20J79 DWI MVR/Body Cam #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-013169 (Axon View XL Software).   TROOPER CERTIFICATES / TRAINING / SPECIAL ASSIGNMENTS  1. Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. 2. Certified SFST Instructor. 3. Chemical Breath Test Operator. 4. Graduate of the University of Marylands DUI Institute. 5. Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. 6. Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). 7. Trained in Cannabis Impairment Detection (Maryland State Police). 8. Assigned to the Berlin Barrack V Special Enforcement Team (focusing exclusively on DUI enforcement) from October 2017 - June 2022.   NARRATIVE   -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION-  On 04-14-2023 at approximately 0019 hours, I (Corporal J. Ruiz #6312), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating marked MSP vehicle V-14 in the area of Maryland Route 90 near Mile Marker 8 at the base of the St. Martin River Bridge (Ocean Pines). I was stationary on the right shoulder area, monitoring all westbound traffic. I was operating stationary radar. The in-car Kustom Golden Eagle II (MSP Serial #50010806) front and rear radar antennas were activated and had been checked before (and later after) my shift and appeared to be functioning properly. At that time, I observed a compact sedan traveling westbound pass my location at what appeared to be a high rate of speed. I made the following observations on the same vehicle:   NEAR MILE MARKER 8  1. As the vehicle continued traveling westbound, a speed of 85 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone was captured as the vehicle entered the influence of the radar beam.  I safely entered the roadway and closed in on the same vehicle near Mile Marker 7.   BETWEEN MILE MARKER 7 AND THE MARYLAND ROUTE 589 EXIT  2. The vehicle continued traveling at a high rate of speed, and then began to decrease its speed as it approached the MD Rout 589 exit.   ADDITIONAL OBSERVATIONS  3. Total distance traveled was approximately 1.88 miles.   DWI INDICATORS / REASON FOR STOP  The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHSTA) published a The Visual Detection of DWI Motorists booklet in March 2010. The research revealed that DWI cues related to problems in maintaining proper lane position include:  1. Speed 2. Varying speed.  All of the above DWI indicators were exhibited by the sedan prior to my initiating a traffic stop on the same vehicle.   TRAFFIC STOP  I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle, initiating a traffic stop on MD Route 90 westbound at the MD Route 589 exit. The vehicle was a gray 2013 Mazda 3 bearing Virginia Registration TUV7866.   -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT-   I made contact with the driver via the driver side door, and I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested the drivers license and the registration card to the vehicle. The driver was identified as Brittany Lee Smack by her Virginia identification card. I asked Smack where she was traveling from, and she responded: Uh, out in the city boardwalk. I asked Smack where she was traveling to, and she replied: Virginia. We were gonna hit the Casino, but guess not. I asked Smack how much she had to drink earlier in the evening, and she responded: Um, 1.   As Smack spoke, I made the following observations:  1. I intentionally observed her eyes to be glassy and bloodshot.  2. Smack displayed a glazed look/expression on her face as she interacted with me.   I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Smack.  I later returned to the Mazda and requested Smack exit the vehicle and walk to the front of it, to which she complied. While at the front of the vehicle, I continued to speak with Smack. I asked Smack again where she was traveling from, and she stated: Uh, Seacrets. I asked Smack how many total alcoholic beverages she had consumed prior to driving, and she advised: Um, I had 2 total. I asked Smack what kind of drinks she had consumed, and she responded: Grapefruit. I asked Smack if the drinks she had consumed were grapefruit crushes, and she replied: Yeah. When asked at approximately what time she had finished consuming her last drink prior to driving, Smack advised: Id say about 20 minutes ago, something like that. As Smack spoke, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I informed Smack that I wanted her to perform field sobriety tests which she agreed to submit to.   -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING-  STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder area. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and vehicle headlamps. Weather was clear and approximately 61 degrees. I asked Smack if she had any significant medical issues with her eyes, arms, or legs which would prevent her from performing the field sobriety tests or if she had taken any medication prior to driving. Smack responded: I have loss of cerebraldosis, which is a spinal deficiency where my spine here is deteriorating. So, I cant really balance myself very well. Um, I drive alot and I take pain medication. Smack appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, or any limb ailments.  Smack was wearing a black tank top, blue jeans, and gray Adidas athletic shoes.   **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**  1. Smack displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  2. Smack displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  3. Smack displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.   **WALK AND TURN: 5 of 8 clues**  1. Smack could not maintain her balance during the Instruction Phase. Smacks feet broke from the start position on two (2) occasions, and she stumbled to her right each time.  2. Smack missed heel-to-toe on steps 3, 4, and 8 during the first series. All misses were of more than half an inch.  3. Smack took 10 steps during the first series, which was contrary to my instructions.  4. Smack did not complete the turn in a satisfactory manner, simultaneously pivoting both feet to her left which was contrary to my instructions.  5. Smack was unable to maintain a straight line and stepped off the line on step 4 during the first series and step 1 during the second series.   **ONE LEG STAND: 2 of 4 clues**  1. Smacks body swayed to the left and right on counts 7 and 8.  2. Smack put her left foot down on counts 7 and 8.   ADDITIONAL ANNOTATIONS REFERENCE FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS // ADDITIONAL TESTING  Walk And Turn (WAT):  A. The solid white shoulder line was used for this test.  B. At no point during this test did Smack count her steps out loud as instructed.   **ALPHABET TEST**:  Smack advised that she was a high school graduate and that she was capable of reciting the English alphabet and numbers. I instructed Smack to recite from the letter F to the letter S.  -Smack stopped at the letter P.  **COUNT TEST**:  I instructed Smack to count backwards from 36-19.  -Smack counted down in the following manner: 36-35-34-33-32-31-30-29-28-27-26-25-24-23-22-21-20-19-18-19-7-YOU SAID 19.   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Smack the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Smack submitted to a PBT with a reading of 0.128 BrAC.   ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Smack was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Driving vehicle in a negligent manner which caused it to travel 30 MPH above the posted speed limit  DRIVING SKILLS IMPAIRED. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot. * Glazed look/expression on face. * Admission to consuming more than one (1) alcoholic beverage prior to operating a motor vehicle. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. * My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests. * PBT result of 0.128 BrAC.  I determined that Smack was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in her system that adversely affected her ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the persons ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Smack under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0036 hours on 04-14-2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Smacks mouth for any foreign objects and none were found.    ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)  Smack was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Smack was given her Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form (played through the patrol vehicles Bluetooth speakers). At the conclusion of the audio version, I verbally re-explained the drivers license sanctions and penalties (section printed in red) to Smack. Smack stated that she understood her Advice of Rights and agreed to submit to a breath test at approximately 0055 hours on 04-14-2023.   TRANSPORT  Smack was subsequently transported to the Berlin Barrack for processing. During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Smack continued to be strong.   **INTOXIMETER RESULT**:  Prior to the breath test, I observed Sergeant C. Sweitzer #3675 visually check the inside of Smacks mouth for any foreign objects. None were found.  The breath test was administered by SGT Sweitzer at approximately 0115 hours on 04-14-2023, and two (2) sufficient samples of Smacks breath were obtained. The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of 0.11 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.   RELEASE  Smack was released from the Berlin Barrack to a sober driver at approximately 0136 hours on 04-14-2023.   CHARGES  Smack was charged with the following citations:  1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (4M20J79) 2. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol Per Se (4M30J79) 3. Driving While Impaired By Alcohol (4M40J79) 4. Speed: 85 MPH In A Posted 55 MPH Zone (4M50J79) 5. Negligent Driving (4M60J79) 6. Driving On Suspended Out-Of-State License (4M70J79)   DRIVERS LICENSE CHECK  SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER  A check of Smacks license status revealed one (1) previous DWI charge (05-19-2019).   Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/21/2023 19:29:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 17:07:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zaykoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7068</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502574</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3099</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/17/2023 12:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3099</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 12:11:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 12:14:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502574</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/17/2023 12:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 12:11:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 12:15:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502574</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/17/2023 12:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 12:11:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 12:14:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502574</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/17/2023 12:13:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 12:11:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 12:13:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 12:11:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374523</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Smack</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brittany</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/20/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.24619511E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 09:42:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B635</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Smack</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brittany</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/20/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.24619511E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B635</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 09:42:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9561</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Atlantic</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>Box 599</SubNumber>
               <City>Atlantic</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>23303</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1000</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.504171</Longitude>
               <Latitude>37.90342</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>571</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>201</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1908</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 12:16:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 12:16:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 12:12:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 12:12:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152056</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 12:19:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 12:19:47</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JM1BL1U88D1706283</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MAZD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MZ3</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>TUV7866</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>12</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>