<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-007180</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/25/2023 03:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/25/2023 03:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/25/2023 02:47:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/25/2023 02:47:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Jada Lynese Schoolfield. Schoolfield also charged with providing a false name.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 03:08:16</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4792</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 10:56:14</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN HWY/ ALLEN RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>269130</AddressId>
      <City>MDC217</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 03:08:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 19:18:23</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>269130</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Princess Anne</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21853</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.676146</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.24844</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13390-13655 OCEAN HWY / 13390-13746 ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 OCEAN HWY / 0-0 ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12350-13389 OCEAN HWY / 13390-13746 ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/25/2023 03:08:13</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/25/2023 03:08:13</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/05/2023 01:31:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 03:08:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Jada Lynese Schoolfield Maryland SOUNDEX: S-414-357-564-450 Breath Test Result: 0.08 DUI Citation #: 4L80J79 DUI Tape #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-007180 (Axon View XL Software).   TROOPER CERTIFICATES / TRAINING / SPECIAL ASSIGNMENTS  1. Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. 2. Certified SFST Instructor. 3. Chemical Breath Test Operator. 4. Graduate of the University of Marylands DUI Institute. 5. Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. 6. Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). 7. Trained in Cannabis Impairment Detection (Maryland State Police). 8. Assigned to the Berlin Barrack V Special Enforcement Team (focusing exclusively on DUI enforcement) from October 2017 - June 2022.   NARRATIVE   -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION-  On 02-25-2023 at approximately 0247 hours, I (Corporal J. Ruiz #6312), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating unmarked MSP vehicle X-17 in the area of U.S. Route 13 southbound near Eden Allen Road (Eden). I was stationary on the right shoulder area, monitoring all southbound traffic. At that time, I observed a white sedan traveling in Lane 2 pass my location. While behind the same vehicle, I made the following observations:   AT EDEN ALLEN ROAD  1. The vehicles right tires crossed (1 tire width) the solid white line into the right shoulder area on one (1) occasion. The vehicle drifted back into Lane 2.  2. The vehicles right tires crossed into the right turn lane. The vehicle drifted back into Lane 2.   BETWEEN EDEN ALLEN ROAD AND ALLEN ROAD  3. The vehicles right tires were directly on top of the solid white shoulder line on five (5) occasions. The vehicle drifted back into Lane 2 each time.   ADDITIONAL OBSERVATIONS  4. The vehicle failed to maintain proper lane position due to pronounced and excessive weaving (alternately moving toward one side of the lane and then the other) during the entire duration of my observations.  5. Total distance traveled was approximately 2.84 miles.   DWI INDICATORS / REASON FOR STOP  The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHSTA) published a The Visual Detection of DWI Motorists booklet in March 2010. The research revealed that DWI cues related to problems in maintaining proper lane position include:  1. Weaving 2. Weaving across lane lines 3. Straddling a lane line 4. Drifting  All of the above DWI indicators were exhibited by the same white sedan prior to my initiating a traffic stop.   TRAFFIC STOP  I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle, initiating a traffic stop on U.S. Route 13 southbound near Allen Road. The vehicle was a white 2008 Lexus IS 250 bearing Maryland Registration 2ES0146.   -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT-  I made contact with the driver via the driver side door, and I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I informed the driver the reason for the stop and requested the drivers license and the registration card to the vehicle. The driver immediately stated: I wasnt though, thats the thing. I was driving straight. But all Im saying is that youre pulling me over for nothing. I asked the driver where she was traveling from, and she replied: Im coming from my sisters house. The driver was identified as Ashley Nicole Taylor by a Maryland Identification Card that she presented. I asked Taylor how much she had to drink earlier in the evening, and she responded: I havent had nothin much. Im not drunk, sir.   As Taylor spoke, I made the following observations:  1. I intentionally observed her eyes to be glassy and bloodshot.  2. Taylor displayed a glazed look/expression on her face as she communicated with me.   I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Taylor.  I later returned to the Lexus and requested Taylor exit the vehicle and walk to the front of it, to which she complied. While at the front of the vehicle, I continued to speak with Taylor. I asked Taylor again where she was traveling from, and she stated: Im coming from my sisters house. In Fruitland. We had a little get together. I asked Taylor where she was traveling to, and she replied: Im headed to Princess Anne to my house. I asked Taylor how many total alcoholic beverages she had consumed prior to driving, and she responded: I only had like 1 or 2 drinks. I asked Taylor what kind of alcoholic drinks she had consumed prior to driving, and she replied: They were only was like Henny drinks, thats fine. When asked at approximately what time she had finished consuming her last drink, Taylor advised: Probably around like 12:30-1. As Taylor spoke, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I informed Taylor that I wanted her to perform field sobriety tests to determine any impairment, which she agreed to submit to.   -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING-  STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder area. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 35 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and vehicle headlamps. I asked Taylor if she had any significant medical issues with her eyes, arms, or legs which would prevent her from performing the field sobriety tests or if she had taken any medication prior to driving. Taylor responded: I do wear glasses. My glasses broke and No, I just take medication like Zoloft and stuff like that for anxiety and depression. Taylor appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any limps or any limb ailments.  Taylor was wearing a black crop top, black lace pants, and black boots.   **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**  1. Taylor displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  2. Taylor displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  3. Taylor displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.   **WALK AND TURN: 6 of 8 clues**  1. Taylor could not maintain her balance during the Instruction Phase of the test. Taylors feet broke from the start position on one (1) occasion, and she stumbled to the right.  2. Taylor missed heel-to-toe on steps 5, 7, 8, and 9 during the first series. Taylor missed heel-to-toe on steps 1, 2, 3, 4, and 5 during the second series. All missed steps were of more than half an inch.  3. Taylor stopped walking after the first series. I had to prompt Taylor to continue the test as instructed.  4. Taylor did not complete the turn in a satisfactory manner, lifting her lead foot and taking one (1) large step to the left and losing her balance which was contrary to my instructions.  5. Taylor took 10 steps during the second series, which was contrary to my instructions.  6. Taylor was unable to maintain a straight line and stepped off the line during all missed steps.   **ONE LEG STAND: 3 of 4 clues**  1. Taylors body swayed to the left and right during counts 9, 13, 15, 16, and 17.  2. Taylor put her right foot down on counts 9, 13, 15, and 17.  3. Taylor raised her arms for balance (higher than 6 to her sides) during counts 9, 13, and 15.   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Taylor the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Taylor submitted to a PBT with a reading of 0.088 BrAC.    ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Taylor was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Driving vehicle in a negligent manner which caused it to commit 7 designated lane direction violations in addition to excessive weaving  DRIVING SKILLS IMPAIRED. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot. * Glazed look/expression on face. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. * My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests. * PBT reading of 0.088 BrAC.  I determined that Taylor was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in her system that adversely affected her ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the persons ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Taylor under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0307 hours on 02-25-2023.   ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)  Taylor was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Taylor was given her Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form (played through the Bluetooth speakers of the patrol vehicle). At the conclusion of the audio version, I verbally re-explained the drivers license sanctions and penalties (section printed in red) to Taylor. Taylor stated that she understood her Advice of Rights and agreed to submit to a breath test at approximately 0327 hours on 02-25-2023.   TRANSPORT  Taylor was subsequently transported to the Princess Anne Barrack for processing. During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Taylor continued to be strong.   **INTOXIMETER RESULT**:  Prior to the breath test, I observed Corporal M. Meyers #2748 visually check the inside of Taylors mouth for any foreign objects. None were found.  The breath test was administered by CPL Meyers at approximately 0349 hours on 02-25-2023, and two (2) sufficient samples of Taylors breath were obtained. The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of 0.08 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.   DETERMINATION OF TRUE IDENTITY OF DRIVER  The registered owner of the Lexus IS 250 responded to the scene of arrest in a silver 2010 Chevrolet Camaro bearing Maryland temporary tag T1257029. Trooper C. Carew #7074 conducted a check of the temporary tag associated with the silver Chevrolet Camaro. The check revealed that the vehicle was registered to Jada Lynese Schoolfield (DOB: 06-16-2001). A Motor Vehicle Adminstration (MVA) check of the registered owner revealed that Schoolfield had a suspended license. In addition, an MVA photograph revealed a positive match to the arrestee -- Ashley Taylor.  Trooper Carew conducted further investigation, which revealed that Ashley N. Taylor was the victim of identity theft. Trooper Carew brought all of this new information to my attention. After further inspection of the Identification Card provided to me throughout my interaction with the arrestee, it was determined that the facial features of Ashley Taylor did not match the arrestee.  At approximately 0415 hours, I presented the arrestee with the MVA photograph of Jada L. Schoolfield and asked the arrestee who the person in the photograph was. The arrestee replied that it was her cousin named Jada Schoolfield. I then located a Facebook profile belonging to Jada Schoolfield. The profile photograph matched the arrestee, to include the same gold necklace the arrestee was wearing. I presented this Facebook photograph to the arrestee, at which time she freely uttered that she was the female in the Facebook profile photograph. I asked the arrestee for her true name and date of birth, and she replied that her name was Jada Lynese Schoolfield and her date of birth was 06-16-2001.  Schoolfield  knowingly and with intent to deceive  made a false statement to me concerning her identity in order to avoid being correctly identified. Schoolfield was subsequently found to be wanted on three (3) bench warrants (1R70W9F-1 / 00W0X6S-1 / 0WX0GVP-2).  *This interaction took place inside the Corporal/Sergeant Room. There was no body camera footage due to the fact that my body camera was in my patrol vehicle charging due to very low battery.*   INITIAL APPEARANCE/RELEASE  Schoolfield was provided all forms and citations prior to her Initial Appearance. An Initial Appearance with the Somerset County District Commissioners Office was conducted via telephone inside the DUI Processing Room. Per the District Commissioner, Schoolfield was released on a $3,000 UNSECURED BOND at approximately 0643 hours on 02-25-2023.   CHARGES  Jada L. Schoolfield was charged with the following:  1. False Statement To Peace Officer (CR 9-502) 2. Driving While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (4L80J79) 3. Driving While Under The Influence Of Alcohol Per Se (4L90J79) 4. Driving While Impaired By Alcohol (4LB0J79) 5. Failure To Obey Designated Lane Directions (4LC0J79) 6. Negligent Driving (4LD0J79) 7. Driver Giving False And Fictitious Name To Uniformed Police (4LF0J79) 8. Driving on Suspended License And Privilege (4LG0J79)   Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Somerset County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:37:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 20:59:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Carew</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7074</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496577</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0690</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/03/2023 19:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0690</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:10:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 19:24:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496577</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21457</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/03/2023 19:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21457</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:10:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 19:25:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496577</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3096</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/03/2023 19:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3096</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:10:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 19:25:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496577</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/03/2023 19:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:10:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 19:26:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496577</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/03/2023 19:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:10:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 19:26:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496577</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/03/2023 19:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:10:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 19:24:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496577</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/03/2023 19:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:10:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 19:24:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496577</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/03/2023 19:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:10:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 19:25:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:10:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370128</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Schoolfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jada</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynese</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/16/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/25/2023 21:22:13</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S414</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Schoolfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jada</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynese</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/16/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S414</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/25/2023 21:22:13</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11302</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>GREENWOOD SCHOOL</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>PRINCESS ANNE</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.69215718820887</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.19176738463469</Latitude>
               <SubBeat>954</SubBeat>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>669</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7481</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:32:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:32:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 21:01:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370670</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Carew</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christian</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/03/2023 21:00:14</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Carew</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christian</FirstName>
               <SLastName>C600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/03/2023 21:00:14</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 21:01:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:18:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 19:18:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150264</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 19:31:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 19:31:21</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JTHCK262785021873</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2008</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>LEXS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>IS250</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2ES0146</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>