<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-033099</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/21/2023 04:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/21/2023 04:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/21/2023 02:44:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/21/2023 02:44:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Domestic Dispute/Hindering Arrest/Use of Force</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 04:08:04</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5162</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/21/2023 10:52:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>707556</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 04:08:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 18:00:32</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>707556</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>7958</StreetNumber>
         <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Chesapeake Beach</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20732</Zip5>
         <Zip4>4665</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.559277</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.690846</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/21/2023 04:08:01</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/21/2023 04:08:01</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 16:53:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 04:08:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was recorded using my Axon body worn camera. This incident was also recorded on TFC Bauers #6719, TFC Mooremans #, and Tpr Sklars #7675 BWC.  Narrative:  On September 21, 2023, at approximately 0244 hours, TFC Bauer #6719 and I, Trooper Sivic #7673, were dispatched to a call involving domestic altercations at 7958 Stream Walk Way, Chesapeake Beach, MD 20732.  Upon arriving on scene, TFC Bauer and I made contact with the complainant and owner of the home, Roy Walangie Ndeh (W/M, DOB: 9/14/1995). Ndeh stated that he has been renting his basement out to a family, and he has been trying to evict the tenants. At this time, Devean Michael Gemoya (B/M, DOB: 11/2/2003) walked out from behind the home to the front yard. TFC Bauer and I began to question Gemoya. Gemoya stated that there was a domestic situation involving a boyfriend and girlfriend, but they took care of it. While speaking with Gemoya, I could smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. At this time, we asked Gemoya for his drivers license to identify him. Gemoya stated that it was in the basement. TFC Bauer and I walked down to the basement door with Gemoya. As we walked towards the basement door, Gemoya had to use the wall to maintain his balance. As we approached the basement door, Jordan William Blackwell (W/M, DOB: 12/29/2004) opened the door. Gemoya immediately closed the door and stated you cant open this door. Blackwell immediately locked the door and walked into another room in the basement. I observed injuries to Blackwells lip when he locked the basement door. TFC Bauer told Blackwell to open the door, but Blackwell ignored all warnings. TFC Bauer attempted to open the basement door. At this time, Gemoya placed his hands on TFC Bauer in an attempt to stop him from opening the door. TFC Bauer immediately told Gemoya not to put his hands on him again, or he would be arrested. At this time, Gemoya told Blackwell again to not open the door. Gemoya grabbed the door handle in an attempt to stop us from entering the home. Gemoya was told again to step back away from the residence to which he failed to comply. Due to not knowing what was happening inside the residence, multiple calls for noise complaints, and Gemoyas statements and behavior, we were unable to delay the investigation any longer. At this time, we attempted to place Gemoya under arrest for obstructing and hindering the investigation and Gemoya began to resist arrest by refusing to keep his hands behind his back and remain still. At this time, TFC Bauer, Calvert County Deputy Hudson #7339, and I executed a take-down on Gemoya. TFC Bauer gained control of Gemoyas right arm while Deputy Hudson gained control of his left arm. I gained control of Gemoyas legs and I placed Gemoya in handcuffs. TFC Bauer gave warnings to Gemoya to stop resisting. TFC Bauer also told Gemoya he was being placed under arrest for obstructing and hindering. Once compliance was gained, all force was stopped, and we brought Gemoya back to his feet. Gemoya was charged with obstruction and hindering, second degree assault, and resisting arrest. An ambulance was requested by for pre-cautionary reasons. Once on scene, Gemoya refused medical treatment. Once Gemoya was placed under arrest, he was placed into a Calvert County Sheriffs police vehicle and transported to the Calvert County Detention Center.    Approximately two minutes after placing Gemoya under arrest, Jessica Lee Hamilton (W/F, DOB: 12/28/1978) came from the front of the home and advised us that there were two males and her daughter, Skyler Jewell Mclean (W/F, DOB: 9/20/2005), inside the basement. At this time, Jenna Michelle Munoz (W/F, DOB: 11/24/2004) came to the basement door from the inside of the basement and opened the door. Munoz advised that there were three subjects in the back room of the basement. Munoz also advised that it was Mcleans 18th birthday and the three subjects were heavily intoxicated. Munoz also stated that Mclean was possibly suicidal. TFC Bauer and I entered the basement and attempted to make contact with the three subjects. I knocked on the door and announced myself as the Maryland State Police multiples times and there was no answer. At this time, I opened the door and made contact with the three subjects. The two males in the room were Blackwell and Roman Avery Pirner (W/M, DOB: 7/22/2004). Blackwell was lying on a bed along with Mclean while Pirner was on the floor. There were multiple alcoholic bottles on the bed and the floor of the bedroom.The three subjects were separated from one another while being questioned about the incident.    TFC Bauer, Deputy Hudson, and I spoke with Mclean in the bedroom. While speaking with Mclean, I observed the right side of her face to be swollen and beginning to bruise. We asked Mclean how this happened, and she denied there being any marks or swelling on the right side of her face. Mclean agreed to received medical attention while we were at the residence. Mclean stated that they were being loud around 2400 hours because it was her 18th birthday.Mclean stated that she got into a verbal argument with her mother and that was all that happened. Mclean denied there being any physical altercation between anyone inside the residence that night.TFC Bauer asked Mclean is she was suicidal or if she wanted to harm herself or others. Mclean stated that she was suicidal a few months ago, but no longer felt that way after getting help.    Munoz stated that Mclean and Blackwell got into a physical altercation at a bar in Anne Arundel County a few hours before our arrival. Munoz stated that Blackwell put Mclean in a headlock. After Mclean became free from the headlock, Munoz stated that Mclean struck Blackwell in the mouth with a punch causing the cut on his lip. Blackwell and Mclean denied this incident happening. Munoz also stated that she was the only subject at the residence that had not consumed alcohol that night.    Tpr. Sklar #7675 spoke with Pirner. Tpr. Sklar asked Pirner how Blackwells lip became injured. Pirner stated that he does not know how that happened. When Pirner was asked about the noise complaint, he stated that they were being loud because there were verbal arguments between some people but the arguments never became physical.    Tpr. Sklar then spoke with Jessica Hamilton. Hamilton stated that her daughter, Skyler Mclean, arrived home from Anne Arundel County and was fine. She then stated that Mclean went crazy out of nowhere and lunged at her. Hamilton stated that Mclean didnt hit her and then fell to the ground. Hamilton stated that as Mclean fell, she hit her head on her vanity in her bedroom. Hamilton stated that she probably fell due to the alcohol in her system. Hamilton stated that no one got into a physical altercation.    Shortly after speaking with Mclean, TFC Bauer and I placed Blackwell under arrest for obstruction and hindering for locking the back door of the residence. Blackwell did not resist arrest when being placed in handcuffs. After being placed in handcuffs, Blackwell attempted to bring his arms to the front of his body by taking his arms under his legs. As Blackwell attempted to do this, TFC Bauer took his hand and put in on the back of Blackwells head and guided him towards the ground. At this point, Blackwell already had his arms under one of his legs. TFC Bauer and I escorted Blackwell outside to my Marked Maryland State Police cruiser U-23. While attempting to buckle Blackwell, he refused to remain still in the seat. Blackwell was transported in a Calvert County Deputys police vehicle, with a cage in the back seat, to the Calvert County Detention Center.    Copies of the Probable Cause Statement and Application for Statement of Charges are attached to this report.    Case closed by arrest.  All events above occurred in Calvert County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:41:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7673</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 19:19:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bauer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6719</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Moorman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6980</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rucker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Natasha</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6120</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sklar</LastName>
            <FirstName>Camden</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hunt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kemery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5162</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5829</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sivic</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bryson</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7673</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522554</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0043</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/21/2023 02:44:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0043</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:14:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7673</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 18:04:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522554</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/21/2023 02:44:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:15:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7673</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 18:05:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:17:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 18:00:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388344</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Blackwell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/29/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 05:29:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B424</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J635</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Blackwell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/29/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B424</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J635</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 05:29:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1940</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Rosemary</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Port Republic</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20676</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.53676</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.518876</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:17:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:17:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:18:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 18:00:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388345</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gemoya</LastName>
               <FirstName>Devean</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/02/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 06:08:02</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gemoya</LastName>
               <FirstName>Devean</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/02/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 06:08:02</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4777</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>St Leonard</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>St Leonard</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20685</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2806</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.507701</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.47597</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:18:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:18:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:24:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 18:00:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388347</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hamilton</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jessica</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/28/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 06:23:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H543</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J220</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hamilton</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jessica</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/28/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H543</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J220</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 06:23:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>17101</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>St Marys Church</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Aquasco</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20608</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.709819</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.591167</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:24:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:24:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:27:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 18:00:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388348</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mclean</LastName>
               <FirstName>Skyler</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jewell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/20/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 06:27:11</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M245</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S460</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mclean</LastName>
               <FirstName>Skyler</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jewell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/20/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M245</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S460</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 06:27:11</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7958</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Stream Walk</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Chesapeake Beach</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20732</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.559276</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.690845</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:27:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:29:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 18:00:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388349</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Munoz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jenna</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/24/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 06:29:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Munoz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jenna</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/24/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 06:29:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2410</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Wildflower</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Huntingtown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20639</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4210</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.536517</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.604863</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:29:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:37:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 18:00:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>313321</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Pirner</LastName>
               <FirstName>Roman</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Avery</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/22/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/12/2021 00:17:14</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P656</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R550</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Pirner</LastName>
               <FirstName>Roman</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Avery</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/22/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P656</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R550</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/12/2021 00:17:14</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:37:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:38:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 18:00:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388350</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>NDEH</LastName>
               <FirstName>Roy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Walangie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/14/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 06:38:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R000</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>NDEH</LastName>
               <FirstName>Roy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Walangie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/14/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>N300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R000</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/21/2023 06:38:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7958</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Stream Walk</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Chesapeake Beach</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20732</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.559276</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.690845</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:38:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 06:38:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 18:04:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 18:04:23</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389562</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>U</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/04/2023 18:03:02</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <DateOfInfo>10/04/2023 18:03:02</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7673</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 18:04:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/21/2023 05:38:50</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/21/2023 05:38:50</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 16:53:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7675</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 05:38:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was audibly and visually recorded on my Axon Body worn camera.  On September 21, 2023, at 0357 hours, I, Trooper Sklar #7675 was at 7958 Stream Walk Way for a domestic dispute. TFC Bauer #6719 and Trooper Sivic #7673 arrested Jordan William Blackwell W/M, (D.O.B. 12/29/2004) for obstructing/hindering. I observed Blackwell become very argumentative and attempt to step through his handcuffs. I observed TFC Bauer place his right hand on the back of Blackwells head, and guide the back of his head downward so that he was unable to get out of the handcuffs. Blackwell rolled onto the ground and was re-positioned in the handcuffs properly.    This concludes my assistance in this investigation.  All events occurred in Calvert County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7675</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 05:39:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7675</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 06:06:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5829</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oleksak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jaroslaw</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6300</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sklar</LastName>
            <FirstName>Camden</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/21/2023 05:54:19</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/21/2023 05:54:19</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 16:53:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6980</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 05:54:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative:  On September 21, 2023, at approximately 0357 hours, I, TFC Moorman #6980, was assisting TFC Bauer #6719 and Trooper Sivic #7673 on a possible domestic dispute at 7958 Stream Walk Way, Chesapeake Beach, Calvert County, Maryland.  I was standing approximately six feet away from TFC Bauer who was placing, Jordan William Blackwell, W/M, DOB: 12/29/2004, under arrest for obstructing/hindering. TFC Bauer placed Blackwells hands behind his back and placed him in handcuffs. Blackwell became argumentative. I observed Blackwell attempt to move the handcuffs to the front of his body by stepping over them with his feet. TFC Bauer instructed Blackwell to stop attempting to step over the handcuffs, and Blackwell did not listen. TFC Bauer placed his right hand on the rear of Blackwells head and assisted him to the ground. Blackwell rolled forward and laid on his back on the ground. Blackwell then stopped attempting to rearrange the handcuffs when lying on his back on the ground. Once compliance was gained, no further force was used.  This concludes my portion of the investigation.  All events occurred in Calvert County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6980</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 05:55:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6980</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/21/2023 05:55:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5829</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Moorman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6980</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/30/2023 10:08:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/30/2023 10:08:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 16:53:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 10:08:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was audibly and visually recorded on my BWC utilizing the Axon Digital Recording System.  Narrative:    On September 21, 2023 at approximately 0243 hours, Tpr. Sivic #7673 and I responded to a possible domestic disturbance in progress at 7958 Stream Walk Way, Chesapeake Beach, Calvert County, Maryland.    Upon arrival, we made contact with the complainant, Roy Walangie Ndeh (B/M, DOB: 09/14/1995) who advised that he heard yelling and a loud disturbance coming from his basement. Ndeh advised that he was currently trying to evict the tenants that currently were renting his basement portion of his residence. Ndeh advised that he was going to obtain shoes and then walk us down to the basement, which was accessed by walking around to the back of the house.  I then proceeded around to the left side of the residence when I observed a white male, later identified as Devean Michael Gemoya (W/M, DOB:11/02/2003), walking up the hill from the backside of the house. I made contact with Gemoya who advised that a boyfriend and girlfriend were involved in a domestic, but we handled it. At that time, I had asked for his ID card and he stated that it was inside. We then began to walk with him to the basement to obtain his ID card. As Gemoya approached the door to the basement, another white male subject inside the residence, later identified as Jordan William Blackwell (W/M, DOB:12/29/2004) initially opened the door. At that time, Gemoya pulled the door shut and Blackwell subsequently locked the door. I observed Blackwell to have a cut on his lower lip and it was bleeding. While speaking with Gemoya at the door, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage and he appeared to be extremely intoxicated. When I attempted to open the door, Gemoya grabbed my arm, pushed it away from the door, and said, The door is closed, you cant go in. I advised to Gemoya to not put his hands on me, back away from the door, and that the door needed to be opened, or I would force entry into the residence. I then yelled at Blackwell from outside of the door and stated, Open this door! Blackwell returned to the door and reached out towards the door knob. At that point, Gemoya grabbed the door knob from the outside and began pulling on the door to keep it closed while telling Blackwell, No, No, No, dont open the door. I attempted to grab the door once more and Gemoya once again assaulted me by grabbing my arm and pushed it away from the door. Due to Gemoya not allowing me to investigate and determine if Blackwell was okay due to his injuries, Gemoya was taken to the ground and placed into handcuffs. Gemoya was placed under arrest for obstructing and hindering and later transported to the Calvert County Detention Center by Dep. Hudson of the Calvert County Sheriffs Office.  At that point, Jenna Michelle Munoz (W/F, DOB: 11/24/2004) opened the door to the basement and advised, they are back there while pointing down the hallway. I then asked who they were. Munoz advised that three subjects were in the back room and that they were the ones who were having the domestic. We made our way down the hall and made contact with three subjects who were sleeping in the room. One of the subjects I was able to easily identify as Blackwell due to him locking the door. The other two subjects were identified as Roman Avery Pirner (W/M, DOB: 07/22/2004) and Skyler Jewell Mclean (W/F, DOB: 09/20/2005). Blackwell rolled over and immediately stated, What the fuck are you doing, youre a grown ass man. Pirner then stood up and began talking and trying to explain how I was not legally allowed to be in here. Pirner advised me that I was breaking federal laws. Pirner, Blackwell, and Mclean were separated for questioning. I observed Mclean to have a welt underneath her right eye, however, Mclean failed to cooperate and provide any information about the welt or information about Blackwells lip. Contact was made once more with Blackwell and he was also placed under arrest for Obstructing and Hindering due to me watching him lock the door and walk away. Shortly after being placed into handcuffs, Blackwell attempted to step through his handcuff in order to place his hands in front of his body. I applied pressure to the back of Blackwells head towards the carpet and Blackwell was able to roll forward onto his back. Blackwell was quickly apprehended, assisted to his feet, and immediately taken outside to Dep. Newtons vehicle where he was transported to the Calvert County Detention Center.  Contact was made with Munoz was made who advised that Blackwell and Mclean had been involved in a verbal altercation in Anne Arundel County earlier in the evening where Blackwell was hit in the lip by Mclean. Munoz also stated that Mclean and her mother, Jessica Lee Hamilton (W/F, DOB: 12/28/1978) were in an altercation just prior to our arrival. Munoz advised both parties were yelling at each other and Mclean began swinging at Munoz. It is unclear how Mclean got the welt on her face due to conflicting stories from all parties on scene.  This concluded my investigation with this case.  All events occurred in Calvert County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 10:10:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6719</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 16:41:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5829</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bauer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6719</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>