<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012605</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/09/2023 10:35:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/09/2023 10:35:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/09/2023 09:40:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/09/2023 09:40:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Accident/DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 10:35:20</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/26/2023 12:36:41</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>25560</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>533</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 10:35:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 08:24:22</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>25560</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>504</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>EDGEWOOD</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>EDGEWOOD</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>533</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-76.29489588715803</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.42218236353106</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7-11</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/09/2023 10:35:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/09/2023 10:35:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/17/2023 20:59:55</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE PROCESSED-ORIGINAL</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 10:35:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4849</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 20:59:55</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> Maryland State Police, Barrack D Marked MSP Vehicle D-7. In-Car Camera Operational.  Defendant: Humphrey, Amber Marie Date of Birth: 01/27/1994 Date of Arrest: 04/09/2023 Time of Arrest: 0940hours DUI #: 23-099(Bel Air) Blood test Result: Refusal     Witness: Spruell, Jesses Adarly Date of Birth: 03/14/1988 MD Soundex: MD-10273651038 Cellphone: 443-617-5761   BEHAVIOR/CONDUCT:Humphrey was combative, disruptive, disrespectful and verbally and physically abusive.  CERTIFICATION  TRAINING NHSTA Trained/certified to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Test (SFST) Preliminary breath test operator certified Certified Radar/Laser Operator  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On 04/09/2023at approximately 0940hours, I, Trooper Kumador #7052 of the Maryland State Police, Bel Air Barrack responded to the 7/11 gas station located at 504 Edgewood Road in Edgewood, Harford County, Maryland in reference to a lookout for a Blue Hyundai Elantra displaying Maryland registration 3FF5989. The vehicle was reportedly swerving all over the road, striking two mailboxes on Magnolia Road, causing damage to 700 Magnolia Road mailbox. Two separate citizens called the barrack to report the incident. One of the callers followed the vehicle to the 7/11 and remained with the vehicle where he took photographs of the female driver passed out behind the wheel.  I arrived at the location and made contact with the citizen whomI identified by his Maryland drivers license as Spruell, Jesse Adarly, DOB: 03/14/1988. Spruell, being a Harford County, Joppa Magnolia Volunteer emergency vehicle driver, stated that he followed the vehicle from the intersection of US-40 and MD-152 out of concern for the safety of the driver because of the unsafe manner the vehicle was being operated. Spruell was traveling south on MD-152 directly behind the vehicle and observed the vehicle striking two mailboxes and driving against traffic crossing the double yellow lines many times.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I located the vehicle at 2118 Old Edgewood Road and observed a white female taking stuff out of the vehicle. I approached the female, introduced myself and the reason for the contact and asked her if she was the driver of the vehicle to which she acknowledged yes. She stated that she was just arriving home from obtaining her Methadone and was the driver of the vehicle. I identified her by her Maryland Identification Card as Humphrey, Amber Marie. I informed Humphrey that we had reports of her vehicle striking two mailboxes and swerving all over the road in the area of MD-152 and Hanson Road. She later stated that she used the same route but did not remember striking any mailboxes. I also showed Humphrey a photograph of her completely passed out behind the wheel at the 7/11. Humphrey acknowledged that she was at the 7/11 to get something to drink. Humphrey appeared unsteady on her feet and her speech was extremely slurred.  Her pulpi were conscripted.Humphrey stated that she consumed 110 milligrams of Methadone about two hours before arriving home and has been on Methadone for the past six years.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) My interactions withHumphreygave me reasons to believe that she was under the influence of a controlled dangerous substancebased on the following facts.   Humphreyadmitted to consuming 110 milligrams of methadone about 2hours before the accident,  Passing out completely behind the wheel  Recklessly and negligently swerving and driving against traffic on the roadway striking mailboxes  Witnesss observation of reckless operation of vehicle on roadway.  I therefore asked Humphreytoperform theStandardized Field Sobriety Tests. She agreed to take the test. The evaluation was performed in the parking lot in front of the location.The area wasflat and free of any debris and the temperature was approximately 68degrees.Prior to the testsI asked Humphreythe following questions: Contacts - No,Glasses - No, andAny injuries - No.Any medication: Methadone.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (0/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the Tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Humphreyseyes. Shewas instructed to look straight ahead, keeping herhead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hereyes until told to stop. I asked herif she understood the directions, and she advised yes. Herpupils were equal in size and did show equal tracking.     Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Not present  The distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation  Not present  The onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Not present.   WALK AND TURN (5/8) Before Humphreyperformed the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. She was instructed to place herright foot directly in front of herleft foot and touch heel-to-toe. She was instructed to place herhands flat at herside and to remain in the position until told to begin. Shewas advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. She was to keep herhands flat at herside, keep hereyes focused on herfeet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, she was demonstrated and explained to keep herlead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around to herleft with herrear foot to turn completely around. She was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. She was then instructed that once she began the test she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep herhands down by herside, look down at herfeet, and count each step out loud.   During the instructional stage:I explained and demonstrated the starting position to Humphreyandplaced herin thestarting position. Shestood straight in the starting position.  Walking stage (1st Nine).    Missed heel-to-toe by more than an inch  Stepped offline during the test and almost fell.  Stopped walking on the 9th step to ask question  Incorrect number of steps. Took 10 steps instead of 9   Turn: The turn was unsatisfactory. Humphreyturned in one fluid motion instead of taking a small series of steps toward herleft. Walking stage (2nd Nine).    Stepped offline during the test.     Incorrect number of steps. Took 10 steps instead of 9   ONE LEG STAND (3/4) Prior to Humphrey performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. She was instructed to stand with herheels together and hands down by herside, while the instructions were given and during the test. She was instructed not to begin the test until she was instructed to start. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of herchoice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While herleg was raised, she was to keep herleg straight, watch herraised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two), and to continue the test until told to stop. The following clues were observed.    Put foot downduring the test  Swayed side by side during the test and almost fell  Raised arms for support during the test.    TFC. Allen also conducted further Advance Roadside Impairment Detection Tests and has a supplement for this report.  PRELIMINARY BREATH A preliminary breath test was not offered to Humphrey.   ARREST Based on the following facts, I havereasons to believe that Humphrey was operating hervehicle while under the influence of a controlled dangerous substanceand was unable to operate itsafely.    Humphreyadmitted to consuming 110 milligrams of methadone beverage about 2hours before the accident,  Passing out completely behind the wheel  Recklessly and negligently swerving and driving against traffic on the roadway striking mailboxes  Observed signs of impairment during the tests  I arrested Humphreyat 0940hours for driving hervehicle while under the influence of a drug causing damage to mailboxes. Humphrey was handcuffed to the front because she stated that she was 4 months pregnant. Humphrey was placed in front of my patrol vehicle and transported to the back to her residence where her vehicle was parked. While Humphrey was in my patrol vehicle, TFC. Allen was standing at the front passenger door monitoring her.  I started a probable cause search of her vehicle. Humphrey became upset that I should not search her vehicle and exited my patrol vehicle in an attempt to prevent me from conducting the search. TFC Allen held her by her arms in an attempt to restrain her from reaching my location. Humphrey was resisting and trying to break free from TFC. Allen holds. I stopped the search and assisted FTC. Allen in getting her back into my patrol vehicle, and she resisted all our attempts.  Humphrey became more aggressive and kicked me with her foot. She also kicked TFC. Allen with her foot. Due to her aggressive behavior, Humphrey was laid to the ground in order to prevent injury to her unborn baby, herself and troopers. While on the ground, she was handcuffed to her back and her feet restrained in order to gain effective control over resistance and prevent her from further kicking troopers.  EMS was requested to the location where she was evaluated and determined to be ok. She was asked to be transported to the hospital for further evaluation, and she declined. Humphrey was later transported to the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack where she listened to the English audio version of DR-15 Advice of Rights in its entiretyand at the conclusion; she agreedtosubmit to the test. She signedthe paper copy of the DR-15 at 120hours. While transporting Humphrey to the barracks, she passed out completely snoring loudly. Even at the barrack, she continued sleeping most of the time snoring.  20-MINUTES OBSERVATION PERIOD. Humphreys observation startedafter heroral cavitycheckwas completed in the barrack just after the arrest  INTOXIMETER RESULT:REFUSAL Breath test was explained andoffered to Humphrey. Humphrey was so drowsy and weak that she could not submit sufficient breath samples and was deemed to have refused. Humphrey was charged with driving while impaired by drugs and other DUI related charges. Humphrey was also charged with 2nd Degree Assault on Law Enforcement officer, Resisting and failure to obey lawful order and arrest.   Humphrey wasgiven copies of all pertinent paperwork andlater transported to the Harford County Detention Center. During a change of clothing at IPC, an orange needle cup and other transparent plastic cups were recovered from her vagina.  Closed by arrest.  All events occurred in HarfordCounty, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 14:18:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 20:43:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stanley</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4849</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kumador</LastName>
            <FirstName>Linford</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7052</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19745</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/09/2023 09:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19745</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 08:30:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 08:30:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 08:27:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:50</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>302392</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Humphrey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Amber</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.04413323E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/01/2021 02:29:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H516</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A516</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Humphrey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Amber</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.04413323E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>H516</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A516</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/01/2021 02:29:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>200</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Middleway</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>1A</SubNumber>
               <City>Middle River</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21220</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.4513698</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.3349627</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2118</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old Edgewood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Edgewood</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21040</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3326</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.293421</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.415961</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>433</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Winterberry</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Edgewood</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21040</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.274364</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.432633</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>318</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3114</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>667</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>308</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4081</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/12/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 08:31:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 08:31:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 08:31:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 08:31:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 08:30:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 08:30:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151793</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 09:30:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 09:30:32</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>13</StatusCode>
         <VIN>KMHDN46D45U183953</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2005</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ELN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>DBL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>DBL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3FF5989</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>