<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008763</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/10/2023 01:43:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/10/2023 01:43:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/10/2023 01:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/10/2023 01:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Single vehicle crash resulted in the arrest of the driver for DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 01:43:05</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/21/2023 08:08:18</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>2914 PHILADELPHIA ROAD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>686866</AddressId>
      <City>MDC308</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 01:43:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/16/2023 15:27:59</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686866</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2914</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Philadelphia</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/10/2023 01:43:01</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/10/2023 01:43:01</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/19/2023 12:40:55</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 01:43:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:49</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-car camera and body worn camera operational, Marked Car D25.  Maryland State Police, Bel Air Barrack DWI #23-066 23-MSP-008763  Defendant: Sharron Patrice Crippens Defendant Address:511 Meadowood Dr, Edgewood MD 21040 DOB: 05/11/1990 Date of Arrest: 03/10/2023 Time of Arrest: 0159 Subsequent Offender: No Minor in the vehicle: No Driver License Number: MD DL MD-10272940501 CDL: No  First Observation:  On 03/10/2023 at approximately 0137 hours I, TFC Allen #7267, was dispatched for a single vehicle accident near the residence of 2914 Philadelphia Rd, Abingdon. Upon my arrival I witnessed a blue Honda Accord that had run off the roadway into a field. Harford county Sherriff was also on scene, Deputies informed me that the driver was retrieving paperwork from her vehicle. Deputies also stated that the driver ran off to road to avoid hitting an animal. I then met with the driver who I later identified via her MD license as Sharron Crippens (B/F DOB 05/11/1990).  Phase Two- Personal Contact:  I then met with Crippens and she stated that she saw an unidentified animal that ran in front of her vehicle and she swerved to avoid it. This caused Crippens to run off the roadway because she did not want to kill an animal. When describing the animal, Crippens described it as having a fluffy tail but heavily slurred the word tail. Crippens would also slur her speech occasionally through our conversation and seemed to act in a disorganize manner, often talking quickly and would frequently apologize. I asked Crippens where she was coming from and where she was going, to which she replied that she was coming from work at a bar and restaurant called Humagalas. Crippens stated she was a waitress and bartender there and that she had a few shots of an alcoholic beverage during her shift. When I asked Crippens if she had anything else to drink she stated that she was at Bushmill Tavern and had a few more shots at that location as well. I asked Crippens to perform standardized field sobriety testing which she consented too.   Phase Three- Prearrest Screening  Standardized Field Sobriety Test:  The evaluation administered to Crippens was on Philadelphia Rd during nighttime hours. Emergency lights were deactivated and Crippens was tested facing away from any emergency equipment. The roadway was also free of debris and deformities. When I asked Crippens if she had anything to drink and she stated that she had a few shots at different bars. It should also be noted that when speaking with Crippens I was able to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on her breath. I also noticed that Crippens had bloodshot and glassy eyes. It should also be noted that while guiding Crippens to the correct position for field sobriety testing, Crippens would often raise her arms from her side holding them straight out with not instruction to do so.  Questions: Glasses or contacts: Yes, for distance.  Medical conditions: None Injuries: None  Medications: Takes medication for anxiety but did not take that medication on the day of testing.   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) (6/6 Clues observed) (Instructed and Understood/ Defendants Response: YES) The first test administered was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. A stimulus pen was used and held approximately 12 inches from Crippenss face. I instructed Crippens to follow the stimulus with her eyes and eyes only. She was also instructed to stand with her feet together and hands to her side. I asked Crippens if she understood the instructions which she stated she did.It should be noted that Crippens needed to be reminded to keep her head still several times during the test. The following observations were made:  Lack of smooth pursuit: 2 clues observed Distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation: 2 clues observed Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees: 2 clues observed Vertical Nystagmus: Not Present. Total Observed Clues: 6/6   Walk and Turn Test (6/8 Clues Observed) (Instructed and Understood/ Defendants Response: Yes) The second test offered to Crippens was the Walk and Turn. I instructed Crippens to stand in the starting position by placing her right foot in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe.I then instructed Crippens to remain in that position and that she was not to begin the test until told to do so. I then explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I instructed Crippen to take 9 heel to toe steps while keeping her hands to her side, and continuously look at her feet while counting aloud. On the ninth step, I explained that Crippen was to keep her lead foot planted, while she took a series of small steps around her lead foot with her rear foot to turn completely around and take an additional 9 steps in the same manner. I then reminded Crippen that she was not to start or stop the test until it was completed. I then asked Crippen if she understood the instructions, which she stated that she did. It should be noted that Crippens performed the WAT test twice due to needing to urinate in the middle of her first attempt. After relieving herself, Crippens performed the test a second time.   Instructional stage:  Stepped out of the starting position.  Walking stage: First attempt.   First Nine Steps:  Toe to Heel: no contact on all steps Stepped off line: on step 4, 6, and 23 Used arms for balance: none Total steps: 23 steps  Second set of first attempt.  Toe to Heel: missed on all steps Stepped off line: on steps 1,2,3,4 and 6 Used arms for balance: none Total steps: 6 steps Started too soon: No Stopped during the test: Yes, on step 4, 6, 16 and 23 of the first set and after the turn. The second set of steps, Crippens stopped on step six to use the bathroom.  The Turn: Unsatisfactory.   Second Attempt.   First Nine Steps:  Toe to Heel: no contact on all steps Stepped off line: on step 4,5,6,9,12, and 19. Used arms for balance: none Total steps: 20 steps  Second set of first attempt.  Toe to Heel: missed on all steps Stepped off line: on steps 2,3,4,6, and 12 Used arms for balance: on steps 4 and then 9 through 20 Total steps: 20 steps Started too soon: No Stopped during the test: Yes, on step 9 of the first set and after the turn. The second set of steps, Crippens stopped on step 2, 3, and 4.  The Turn: Unsatisfactory.  It should be noted that after step 20 of Crippens second set I ended the test due to Crippens showing no sign of stopping.   Total Clues (7/8)   One Leg Stand (4/4 Clues observed) (Instructed and understood/ Defendants Response Yes) I instructed Crippen to assume the starting position for the One Leg Stand test by placing her feet together and keeping her arms by her side. I also told Crippensto not begin the test or move from the starting position until she was instructed to do so. Crippens stated that she understood the instructions. I demonstrated to Crippens, once instructed to do so, she was to raise one of her feet approximately 6 inches off the ground and to point her toes forward to let the foot be parallel to the ground. I then instructed Crippens to look at her toes the entire time while she counted by thousands aloud. (Thousand one, thousand two) I told her to continue to count until told to stop. I asked Crippens if she understood the instructions to which he stated Yes.  Balance and Counting Stage  0-10 Seconds: Put foot down: n/a Swayed: n/a Used Arms for balance: yes Hops: n/a  11-20 Seconds: Put foot down: yes Swayed: yes Used Arms for balance: yes Hops: n/a   21-30 Seconds: Put foot down: n/a  Swayed: n/a Used Arms for balance: yes Hops: n/a  Total Clues (3/4)  Arrest Due to my training of over 40 hours in DUI detection with live donors at the Maryland State Police Academy, being certified to conduct ARIDE testing through Baltimore County, and the observations of impairment made during the Field Sobriety testing; I determined I had probable cause to believe that Crippens was driving under the influence and unable to operate the vehicle safely. Due to the following:   Glassy eyes  Bloodshot eye  Omission to drinking alcohol prior to driving  Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on the drivers breath.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Clues of field sobriety testing  I then placed Crippens under arrest fordriving or attempting to drive while under the influence of alcohol at 0159 hours.  Advice of Rights (DR-15) / Certified Breath Test (Refused). I presented Crippens with the Advice of Rights form (DR-15) in English audio form while transporting her to the barrack and she refusedto submit to an intoximeter test at 0217 hours. It should be noted that after playing the DR-15 to Crippens she stated that I am no sure what to do, I am drunk. This admission can be heard on my in-car camera during the transportation of Crippens at approximately 16 minutes and 35 seconds. Crippens also advised to me that she had no insurance on her vehicle the night of the incident.  Crippen was charged with driving under the influence of alcohol and issued all pertinent paperwork.  Crippens was released to a license driver at approximately 0322 hours Status- closed by arrest. All events occurred in Harford County Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 15:31:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 15:31:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Urbano</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6588</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Turner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6761</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498162</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3096</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/10/2023 01:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3096</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 15:47:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 12:18:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498162</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19733</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/10/2023 01:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19733</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 15:47:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 12:21:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498162</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/10/2023 01:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 15:47:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 12:22:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498162</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/10/2023 01:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 15:47:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 12:23:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498162</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/10/2023 01:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 15:47:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 12:24:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498162</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/10/2023 01:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 15:47:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 12:25:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498162</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/10/2023 01:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 15:47:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 12:20:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498162</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/10/2023 01:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 15:47:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 12:26:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 15:47:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:39</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371750</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Crippens</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sharron</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Patrice</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/11/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/16/2023 15:33:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C615</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Crippens</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sharron</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Patrice</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/11/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C615</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/16/2023 15:33:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>511</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Meadowood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Edgewood</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21040</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.311906</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.421346</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>819</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6757</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 12:27:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 12:27:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 15:47:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/16/2023 15:47:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>