<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025685</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/18/2023 17:16:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/18/2023 17:16:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/18/2023 16:48:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/18/2023 16:48:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Single Vehicle Motor Vehicle Collision - Personal Injury</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 17:16:27</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5555</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 17:14:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>NANTICOKE RD/ WHITEHAVEN RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>701323</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 17:16:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 19:16:26</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>701323</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Whitehaven</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Quantico</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21856</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.726652</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.355444</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/18/2023 17:16:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/18/2023 17:16:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>07/19/2023 17:10:54</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 17:16:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5555</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 17:12:53</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Incident:Motor Vehicle Collision Driver:Charles Tubbs Sr (W/M 6/27/1940) Location:Whitehaven Rd  Nanticoke Rd, Quantico MD 21856 Date:7/18/2023 Time:1648 hours   Narrative: On 7/18/23 at approximately 1648 hours, I TFC Eckrich, was dispatched to the area of Whitehaven Rd and Nanticoke Rd in reference to a single vehicle accident into a tree. Upon my arrival, I observed a red Dodge Ram 1500 bearing Maryland registration 21R830 in a tree line off the roadway. The driver and sole occupant of the vehicle was identified as Charles Tubbs Sr (W/M 6/27/40). Tubbs had already been transported by Hebron EMS to Tidal Health prior to my arrival on scene. I was advised by Fire/EMS personnel that were still on scene, that Tubbs was considered priority 1 with life-threatening injuries. Fire personnel stated that they did not notice any odor of alcohol coming from Tubbs person. Tubbs was identified by his Maryland drivers license. Upon further investigation it was determined that Tubbs was traveling West on Whitehaven Rd when it appeared that his vehicle went over the right shoulder line. Based on the skid marks left by the tires it appears that Tubbs suddenly veered to the left, causing him to go off the roadway striking multiple trees. Due to the seriousness of injury I requested an accident re-constructionist respond to the scene. I noticed in the rear seat of the vehicle was an open bottle of Lord Calvert which is an alcoholic beverage. While on scene I contacted Tidal Health emergency department, and they advised Tubbs was listed in critical condition. S/Tpr S. Marshall responded to the scene to conduct the reconstruction investigation. City Towing towed the vehicle from the scene.  I responded to Tidal Health to get an update on Tubbs condition. According to hospital personnel Tubbs was in critical condition with a small brain bleed. I made contact with Tubbs wife identified as Ruth Tubbs (W/F 11/20/46). Ruth advised that Charles was visiting a friend and was on his way home at the time of the accident. Ruth advised that Charles had been having some difficulty breathing as of late and was supposed to be on oxygen. Over the past couple weeks Charles pulse oximeter had been going down to the lower 90s in the evening time. Charles had not been on his oxygen at the time of the accident. I inquired about the bottle of Lord Calvert and Ruth stated that he has had that bottle for approximately 3 years. Based on speaking with Ruth and the nurses at Tidal Health, I do not believe alcohol was a factor in this accident.   On 7/19/23 at approximately 1430 hours, I contacted Tidal Health to check on Charles status. As of the time of the call, Charles was listed in critical but stable condition. I was also advised by MSP Salisbury barrack that a witness to the accident had called the barrack. I called the witness who was identified as Jason Schroeder (W/M 4/24/02). Schroeder stated that he was traveling in the opposite direction on Whitehaven Rd, when he noticed Charles red Dodge truck. Schroeder observed the right side tires of Charles vehicle go over the right shoulder line. As Schroeder passed Charles vehicle he looked in his rearview mirror and observed Charles vehicle sharply turn to the left crossing the center line and then going off the roadway to the left into the tree line. Schroeder stopped his vehicle and attempted to help Charles out of his vehicle. When fire personnel arrived on scene, Schroeder left the scene  At this time the accident reconstruction investigation has been turned over to S/Tpr S. Marshall.  All events occurred in Wicomico County Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 19:30:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 16:41:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mareck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Keven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3258</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>83</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 19:27:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382861</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Tubbs</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
               <DOB>06/27/1940 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>SR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 19:27:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Tubbs</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
               <DOB>06/27/1940 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>SR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>T120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 19:27:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4972</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Ladys</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Eden</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21822</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2296</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.697645</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.330886</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 19:27:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 19:27:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 19:27:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 15:02:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:09</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>358476</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Schroeder</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/24/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/17/2022 13:33:06</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S636</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Schroeder</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/24/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S636</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/17/2022 13:33:06</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2667</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Clara</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Tyaskin</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21865</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2052</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.818288</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.268021</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>931</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>572</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7726</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/17/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 15:02:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155255</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AC</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 19:29:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 19:29:34</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1D7HU18N28J142634</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2008</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>R15</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>21R830</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/19/2023 19:15:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/19/2023 19:15:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/05/2023 17:12:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 19:15:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5555</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 17:12:53</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Detailed Crash Investigation Report  (For review by the MSPCrash Team)   Section I. - Introduction: On 7/18/2023 at approximately 1650 hours, Troopers from the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack were dispatched to respond to the area of Whitehaven Road and Nanticoke Road, Hebron, Wicomico County, Maryland reference a single vehicle motor vehicle collision. Prior to their arrival, Troopers were advised that the vehicle had traveled off the roadway and into the trees. Troopers were also advised the driver and sole occupant of the vehicle possibly sustained life-threatening injuries. Upon arrival to the scene, Troopers learned the vehicle involved in the collision was a 2008 Dodge Ram pickup truck and the driver was Mr. Charles Tubbs SR.  Preliminary investigations revealed the Dodge was traveling on Whitehaven Road just prior to Nanticoke Road. For an unknown reason, the Dodge traveled onto the right shoulder line and then traveled back onto the roadway. The Dodge then crossed the double yellow lines of the center of the roadway, traveled on the southbound lane of Whitehaven Road, traveled over the shoulder and down into a ditch, and struck multiple trees. After striking the trees, the Dodge rotated and came to its final resting position.  Due to the nature of this collision, a request was made for a Reconstructionist to respond to the scene. I, Senior Trooper S. Marshall was contacted at 1717 hours and responded to the scene.  The scene was photographed and marked for processing. The Dodge was towed from the scene by City Towing. The roadway closure was approximately three hours.  The scope of this investigation will address the various elements that caused and/or contributed to the collision event. The scope of this investigation was accomplished by either direct investigation action of through the review of the findings from other investigative sources. Section II. - Scene Description: (The following descriptions are based on the area where the collision occurred.) Primary Roadway: Whitehaven Road, is also known as Maryland Route 352. Whitehaven Road traveled in an east and west direction. The stretch of roadway the collision occurred on was straight and did not have a change in elevation. The stretch of roadway where the collision had occurred on had no artifical lighting and was in an area surrounded by cornfields. The center of the roadway was marked by solid yellow lane markers. The eastbound lane was supported by a solid white line. The westbound lane was supported by a solid white line. The surface was constructed of asphalt material and appeared to be in good condition. The posted speed limit was 50 miles per hour.  Environmental Conditions: At the time of the collision, the weather was reported clear, dry, with an approximate temperature of 90 degrees at the time of the collision. There were no adverse weather conditions that would have contributed to the collision. Section III. - Scene Evidence: I was able to observe several skid marks on the roadway from the Dodge. (Refer to Pictures DSCN 2023,2034,and 2059). The skid marks started in the northbound travel portions of the roadway and crossed over the solid yellow lane markers into the southbound travel portion. I used spray paint and follow the directions of the skid marks on the roadway. The first marking that I obtained a measurement for was approximately 97 feet in length. The second marking that I obtained a measurement for was approximately 59 feet. The last marking that I obtained a measurement for was approximately 115.4 feet in length. I did not observe any other markings from the Dodge on the roadway. The debris field from the Dodge was in a northbound direction in the trees. Section IV. - Vehicle(s) Involved: Vehicle #1: 2008 Dodge Ram Truck VIN:1D7HU18N28J142634 The 2008 Dodge Ram Truck was driven by Charles Tubbs SR of Eden, Maryland. The Dodge Ram was owned by Charles and Ruth Tubbs of Eden, Maryland. The Dodge was bearing Maryland registration 21R830. The Dodge sustained damage overall damage. The passenger side front tire came off the rim and was located on the shoulder of the roadway. The passenger side doors and bed of the pickup truck were dented in approximately 10 inches. Section V. - Person(s) Involved: Person #1: Charles Tubbs SR. Mr. Tubbs was the driver and sole occupant of the Dodge truck. Mr. Tubbs was wearing his seatbelt at the time of the collision. Mr. Tubbs sustained life threatening injuries from the collision and was transported to Tidal Health.  Person #2: Jason Schroeder Mr. Schroeder was a witness to the collision. Mr. Schroeder spoke with TFC Echrick about the collision. Mr. Schroeder advisedTFC Eckrich that he was traveling in the opposite direction on Whitehaven Road, when he noticed Mr. Tubbs red Dodge truck. Schroeder advised TFC Echrick he observed the right side tires of Mr. Tubbs vehicle go over the right shoulder line. Schroeder advised as he passed Mr. Tubbs vehicle he looked in his rear-view mirror and observed Mr. Tubbs vehicle sharply turn to the left, crossing the center line, and then going off the roadway to the left into the tree line. Schroeder advised that he stopped his vehicle and attempted to help Mr. Tubbs out of his vehicle and then fire personnel arrived on the scene. Section VI. - Follow-up Investigation: Date: 7/19/2023 On 7/19/23 at approximately 1430 hours, TFC Eckrich contacted Tidal Health to check on Mr. Tubbs status. As of the time of the call, Mr. Tubbs was listed in critical but stable condition. TFC Eckrich contacted me and advised me of Mr. Tubbs status.  TFC Eckrich was also advised that there was a witness to this collision. The witness was Jason Schroeder. Schroeder advised TFC Eckrich that he was traveling in the opposite direction on Whitehaven Road, when he noticed Mr. Tubbs red Dodge truck. Schroeder advised TFC Echrick he observed the right side tires of Mr. Tubbs vehicle go over the right shoulder line. Schroeder advised as he passed Mr. Tubbs vehicle he looked in his rearview mirror and observed Mr. Tubbs vehicle sharply turn to the left, crossing the center line, and then going off the roadway to the left into the tree line. Schroeder advised that he stopped his vehicle and attempted to help Mr. Tubbs out of his vehicle and then fire personnel arrived on the scene.  Date:8/3/2023 On 8/3/2023, I contacted Ruth Tubbs, who is Mr. Tubbs wife. Mrs. Tubbs to get status check on Mr. Tubbs. Mrs. Tubbs advised Mr. Tubbs was still in the Intensive Care Unit at Tidal Health in Salisbury, Maryland. Mrs. Tubbs advised Mr. Tubbs was on a ventilator, had a tracheal tube, a neck collar, and a feed tube was inserted to assist with nutrition. Mrs. Tubbs advised Mr. Tubbs had two brain bleeds and fractured bones. Mrs. Tubbs advised that Mr. Tubbs stopped squeezing hands when instructed to do so and has recently loss movement in his appendages. Mrs. Tubbs also advised that the doctor and her did the paperwork for a DNR (do not resuscitate order).  With this information I received from Mrs. Tubbs, I contacted CPL Moore and SGT Gore and advised them of the updated status of Mr. Tubbs.  Date: 8/7/2023 I received an email that Mrs. Tubbs had called the barrack. Mrs. Tubbs advised that Mr. Tubbs had been moved to Wilmington Hospital due to being on a trach/vent machine and still did not recognize or have memory of anyone.  Date: 8/18/2023: On 8/18/2023, I received an email from SGT Barkley that Mrs. Tubbs had contacted the barrack reference Mr. Tubbs. Mrs. Tubbs advised that Mr. Tubbs had passed away in the Wilmington Hospital after he was transferred from Tidal Health.  Date: 9/7/2023: I received the medical records for Mr. Tubbs from Tidal Health Regional Medical Center via email. The total pages for the three days worth of medical records was 1718 pages. I briefly read over them and found on page 75 that Mr. Tubbs had a blood alcohol content of .19BAC. The hospital records advised that Mr. Tubbs sustained multiple lacerations to his body and sustained a lot of trauma. Section VII. - Analysis of Electronic Control Modules: No Electronic Control Modules were completed reference this collision. Section VIII. - Speed Analysis: No Speed Analysis was completed reference this collision. Section IX. - Crash Dynamics: The Dodge was traveling on Whitehaven Road just prior to Nanticoke Road. For an unknown reason, the Dodge traveled onto the right shoulder line and then traveled back onto the roadway. The Dodge then crossed the double yellow lines of the center of the roadway, traveled on the southbound lane of Whitehaven Road, traveled over the shoulder and down into a ditch, and struck multiple trees. After striking the trees, the Dodge rotated and came to its final resting position. Section X. - Attachments that were included in for this report:  The following items were attached to this report: 1. Photograph DSCN2105 2. Photograph DSCN2016 3. Photograph DSCN 2017 4. Photograph DSCN 2023 5. Photograph DSCN 2034 6. Photograph DSCN 2059 Conclusion: On 7/18/2023,Troopers from the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack responded to the area of Whitehaven Road and Nanticoke Road reference a single vehicle motor vehicle collision. The collision involved a 2008 Dodge Ram Pickup truck. The driver of the Dodge, Mr. Tubbs sustained lift threatening injuries due to the collision and subsequently died due to the injuries.  This case is closed due to the death of at-fault party.  Senior Trooper Shadoe N. Marshall 95- Princess Anne 30581 Perry Road Princess Anne, MD 21853 443-260-3700</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 14:26:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 00:43:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CT</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5555</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Marshall</LastName>
            <FirstName>Shadoe</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6066</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515128</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>MSP1004</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/18/2023 16:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>Motor Vehicle Collision - Collision Reconstruction </Remarks>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 19:17:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 19:17:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>