<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-033924</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/27/2023 00:29:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/27/2023 00:29:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/26/2023 23:49:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/26/2023 23:49:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 00:29:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 10:26:42</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>3320 CRAIN,WALDORF</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>708162</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 00:29:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 05:01:56</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>708162</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>3320</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Crain Waldorf</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20603</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.916177</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.620784</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/27/2023 00:29:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/27/2023 00:29:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/10/2023 09:23:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 00:29:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:51</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-car camera, H-28 and BWC operational. Defendant: Jesus Manuel Paez-Dominguez Soundex #/STATE: N/A /N/A Date of Birth: 12/27/1986 Date of Arrest: 09/27/2023 Time of Arrest: 0025 Temperature: 58 Degrees  Weather Condition: Clear Foot Wear: Black Tennis Shoes DUI # 23-168  Attachments:   Six (6) photographs of the open Budweiser bottle.   CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING    Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police.  Advance Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E).   margin-left:8px"&gt;Admitted as an expert in Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (H.G.N) in State VS Robert Kramer on July 03, 2023 (0B70Y24).   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On September 26, 2023 at approximately 2349 hours, I, Tpr. Nain #7452 was on duty, operating marked Maryland State Police vehicle H-28, traveling northbound on US RT 301 at Plaza Drive, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland. At that time, I observed a green Honda Accord traveling northbound on US RT 301 in lane #2 in front of my patrol vehicle. I observed the sedan swerving over the solid white lines Three (3) times and not maintaining its lane. On the third occasion I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle came to a stop northbound US RT 301 north of Plaza Drive. The vehicle was identified as a green Honda Accord bearing Virginia registration TRB9806.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I made contact with the driver of the vehicle. While speaking with the driver, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. The driver stated, I do not speak any English. I informed the driver that I observed his vehicle swerving in and out of the lane on multiple occasions. I asked the driver how many alcoholic beverages did he consumed. Due to the language barrier I then requested the assistance of a Spanish-speaking Charles County Deputy to translate. Charles County Deputy Palacios #773 arrived on scene moments later. I informed Deputy Palacois, I stopped the vehicle due to the driver swerving over the solid white line on three (3) occasions and upon my initial approach I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. Deputy Palacois made a driver side approach to the vehicle and introduced herself to the driver. Deputy Palacois detected the strong odor of an alcohol emitting from his vehicle and person. Deputy Palacois asked the driver how much alcohol he had to drink tonight, Dominguez admitted, I had three (3) Budwiser beers earlier that night. Deputy Palacois advised that Dominguez admitted to Deputy Palacois, Dominguez stated, I drank one (1) Budwiser while I was driving. One (1) open bottle of Bud-wiser was found behind the front passenger seat. The driver was identified as Jesus Manuel Paez-Dominguez (H/M, DOB: 12/27/1987) by his Venezuelan Identification card. I observed Dominguezs eyes to be bloodshot red and glassy. Deputy Palacois askedDominguez if he would be willing to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Test to which he consented. The result are as follows.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed on the side of the road, in front of my patrol vehicle. The surface was dry, level, and free from any debris or obstructions. Lighting conditions consisted of my headlamps, streetlights and my flashlight, with my front emergency lights deactivated.Dominguez appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, or limb aliments.   Medical conditions or injuries which would inhibit his ability to walk in a straight line or stand on one foot: Nothing to report.  Medications: Antibiotic For back pain.  Glasses: Nothing to report   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6)  The first test was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The silver tip of my pen was used as a stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Dominguezs face, slightly above eye level of his brown eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the silver tip of the pen with his eyes only until told to stop. Dominguezs pupil was equal in size and showed equal tracking and no resting Nystagmus was observed. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I askedDominguez if he understood the instructions, and he stated, Yes.   Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes.    Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes.  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degree  Present in both eyes.  Vertical Nystagmus - Present in both eyes.  WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)  Prior toDominguez performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted.Dominguez was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, touching heel to toe. Dominguez was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin.Dominguez continually nodded his head up and down to show he understood.Dominguez was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step.Dominguez was advised to keep his hands flat by his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth stepDominguez was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around, and make an additional nine (9) heel to toe steps. After the first set of nine (9) steps and the turn was demonstrated,Dominguez was informed that once the test is started he should not stop until the test is completed. Instructional Stage:  Walking Stage (1st Nine Steps): 1. Dominguez broke the instruction stage two (2) times. 2. Dominguez performed an improper turn by not keeping his lead foot planted. 3. Raises arm. Walking Stage (2nd Nine Steps): 1. Raised his arms continuously throughout the test.    2.Dominguez performed an improper turn by not keeping his lead foot planted.  ONE LEG STAND - (4/4 clues observed)   Prior toDominguezperforming the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted.Dominguezwas instructed to stand with his legs together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were explained. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately six (6) inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, keep his hands at his sides, watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one thousand  one, one thousand two), and continue the test until told to stop. I askedDominguezif he understood the test, and he stated, Yes.  Instructional Stage: Nothing to Report Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10:  Dominguez raised arms for balance greater than 6 inches throughout the test.  Dominguezhopped throughout the test. Dominguezswayed throughout the test. Dominguezput his foot down.  Seconds 10-20:  Dominguez raised arms for balance greater than 6 inches Dominguezhopped throughout the test. Dominguezswayed throughout the test.  Dominguez put his foot down.  Seconds 20-30: Dominguez then advised that he was finished.   After completing the One Leg Stand test, I askedDominguezif he would consent to a preliminary breath test.Dominguezagreed to submitting to the preliminary breath test.  Result PBT: 0.082 BrAC.   Based on my training knowledge and experience, I had reason to believeDominguezwas operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: Dominguez strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle, his breath, and person. Dominguezeyes glassy and bloodshot red with a glazed look.  Dominguez weaving over the solid white lines. I observed signs of impairment as Dominguez performed field sobriety tests.    Due to a language barrier the above interaction took longer than usual, the interaction took approximately two (2) hours before Dominguez got to the intoximeter. During that time I could see Dominguez demeanor started to change, and his eye color was starting to change.    I arrested Dominguez for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0025 hours. I then securedDominguez in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle (H-28) and transported him to the La Plata Barrack for processing. A mouth check was conducted at 0028 hours as well as 0054 hours. Nothing was located inside his mouth. I arrived at the La Plata Barrack with Dominguez. After arriving at the Barrack, I gaveDominguez a copy of the DR-15, Advice of Rights, in Spanish to review. I also played the Spanish version of the DR-15 via the MVA website. AfterDominguez reviewed the DR-15 he agreed to submit to the intoximeter test.  Intoximeter Result: 0.07 BrAC.           Dominguezwas then transported to from the La Plata Barrack to Charles County Detention Center (CCDC). All copies of the proper paperwork were completed and given toDominguez for his records.  Charges:   Dominguez was charged with the following citations.  1. Driving while under the influence of alcohol (0R50Y24) 2. Driving while impaired by alcohol (0R60Y24) 3.Negligent driving (0R60Y24) 4.Reckless driving (0R70Y24) 5.Driver failure to obey traffic control device (0R80Y24) 6. Driver consuming alcoholic beverage of motor vehicle on highway (0R90Y24)  Case closed by arrest. All events occurred in Charles County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 05:14:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7452</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 14:33:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lagchu</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gilbert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6846</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schrock</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7586</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nain</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7452</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Casarella</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5627</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nain</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7452</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nain</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7452</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523381</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/27/2023 05:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 05:02:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7452</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 05:06:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523381</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/27/2023 05:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 05:02:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7452</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 05:06:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523381</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/27/2023 05:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 05:02:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7452</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 05:07:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523381</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/27/2023 05:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 05:02:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7452</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 05:08:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523381</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15667</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/27/2023 05:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15667</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 05:02:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7452</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 05:09:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>36</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 05:02:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7452</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 01:26:41</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388857</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Paez-Dominguez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jesus</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Manuel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/27/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 04:34:39</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J220</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Paez-Dominguez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jesus</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Manuel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/27/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J220</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 04:34:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2951</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Nelson</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>SE</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubNumber>APT 4</SubNumber>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20019</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.965408</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.875616</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>804</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>877</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5763</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 01:26:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 01:26:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 01:26:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 05:02:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7452</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 05:02:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157486</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 05:12:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7452</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 05:12:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1HGCG6684YA02913</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2000</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ACCORD</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRN</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>TRB9806</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>