<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025354</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/16/2023 00:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/16/2023 00:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/16/2023 00:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/16/2023 00:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>ACRS into DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 00:15:46</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4873</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 23:49:48</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>S 495-CJ TO E CLARA BARTON RAMP / CLARA BARTON PKWY</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>701864</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 00:15:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:09:26</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>701864</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I-495</StreetName>
         <City>Bethesda</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20817</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.16081</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.98386</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/16/2023 00:15:45</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/16/2023 00:15:45</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/12/2023 23:49:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 00:15:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>N-17 is equipped with a mobile recording device Defendant: Monica Alejandra Hernandez Garay De Guirola Date of Birth: 03/06/1989 Date of Arrest: 07/16/2023 Time of Arrest: 0017 hours MD Soundex: MD10272722331 DUI #: 23-165 (Rockville) TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Certified by NHTSA to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) * Certified as a Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator  * Certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE)  * Attended the 2021 Maryland Impaired Driving Conference in Ocean City, Maryland * Participated in several DUI Special Assignments * DUI Award Recipient for 2021  2022 * Gaithersburg Germantown Chamber of Commerce Award Recipient 2023 * Since 2020 have made over 120 DUI arrest VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On Sunday, July 16, 2023 at approximately 0000 hours, I, Trooper Canizalez #7087 was dispatched to the outer loop of I-495 just West of River Road, Potomac, Montgomery County, Maryland, to respond to a single-vehicle collision with property damage. Upon arrival, I observed an orange Ford Fiesta bearing Maryland Registration 7EK9250 with damage to its front left fender. My investigation revealed that HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was driving the at fault vehicle (vehicle one). HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA advised she was traveling on the beltway and slammed on her breaks to avoid striking the rear end of a tractor trailer, subsequently hydroplaned to the left and struck a concrete barrier (fixed object one) with its front left fender while on the outer loop just West of River Road on the right shoulder.   CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the scene and contacted the driver of vehicle one. I opened the driver door to find both the driver and her front passenger still sitting in the vehicle with all airbags deployed. I asked the driver and her passenger if they were O.K. and if they needed any medical attention. They both advised they did not. Immediately I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from within the vehicle. I continued and asked the driver for her license, insurance card and registration card, later asking her to step out of the vehicle for further questioning. The driver was later identified by her Maryland Drivers License as: HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA, Monica Alejandra (MD SDX: MD10272722331, H/F, DOB: 03/06/1989). While speaking with HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA from outside her vehicle, I continued to detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath even with traffic passing. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was also displaying other signs of impairment such as bloodshot and glassy eyes and swaying in place back and forth. When asked about consuming any alcoholic beverages she stated she had consumed 4 Budweiser beer bottles approximately 1 hour prior to driving. I asked HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA if she was willing to perform voluntary SFSTs and she advised that she would.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the left shoulder of the outer loop of I-495 just West of River Road (pavement). The surface was wet and clear from any debris. The weather was partially raining and light conditions consisted of my flashlight. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was not displaying any visible injuries. Prior to beginning the test, I asked HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA the following questions: Glasses or Contacts: None. Medical Conditions: None. Injuries: soreness in her left arm from collision.  Medications: None.  *TEST #1 HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN): 6/6 The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches, slightly above eye level. I instructed her to look straight ahead, keeping her head stationary while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. I asked HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA if she understood the test and she stated Yes. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLAs pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Not present in both eyes.   *TEST #2 WALK AND TURN (WAT): 5/8 Prior to HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was instructed to place her left foot on a straight imaginary line then place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until told to begin the test. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to the left to turn completely around. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA if she understood the test and she stated, Yes.     margin-left:8px"&gt;HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was unable to maintain her balance during the instructional phase.   margin-left:8px"&gt;HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA stepped off line during her first set on her 2nd step.    margin-left:8px"&gt;HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA raised her arms during her 3rd step taken on her second set.    margin-left:8px"&gt;HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA took the incorrect number of steps and took 10 steps during her first set.    margin-left:8px"&gt;HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA incorrectly completed the turn. She did not turn on the planted lead foot. Instead, she used both of her feet to complete the turn to the right, raising her planted foot.   *TEST #3 ONE LEG STAND (OLS): 2/4 Prior to HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count aloud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, Yes. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA performed this test balanced on her left foot.     margin-left:8px"&gt;HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA put her foot down at the 17th and 23rd second mark   margin-left:8px"&gt;HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA used her arms for balance at the 8th second mark  I offered HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA a preliminary breath test and she agreed to take it.  PBT taken at 0015 hours. PBT Results: .12 BrAC  ARREST: Based on the following, I had reason to believe HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of an alcoholic beverage: * HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA failed to control her speed to avoid a collision. * blood shot and Glassy eyes. * HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA constant swaying in place during HGN. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLAs breath. * HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA admitting to have consumed 4 Budweiser beer bottles approximately 1 hour prior to driving.  Due to a number of observations, I had reason to believe HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was driving while under the influence of an alcoholic beverage and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0017 hours, I placed HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA under arrest for Driving While Under the Influence of Alcohol. A preliminary search of HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was conducted on the scene and it revealed that she had nothing on her person. HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was seat belted into my marked MSP patrol vehicle N-17 and was transported to the MSP Rockville Barrack per departmental policy. While conducting the secondary search on HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA at the barrack, her oral cavity was checked and was clear and had nothing in her mouth. During the 20-minute observation period, HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA remained in my custody and did not introduce any foreign object in her mouth. The DR-15 Advice of Rights form was read to HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA at 0100 hours to which she advised she would submit to the intoximeter test. INTOXIMETER RESULT  0.12 GRAMS OF ALCOHOL PER 210 LITERS OF BREATH HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and was released to the care of her sister at 0130 hours.  Case status: closed by arrest. All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 06:33:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/10/2023 10:15:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Saucerman</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4873</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514796</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 06:22:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:12:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514796</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 06:22:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:12:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514796</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 11:09:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 06:22:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:12:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514796</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 11:09:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 06:22:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:12:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514796</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 11:09:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 06:22:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:12:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514796</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 11:09:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 06:22:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:12:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 06:22:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:24</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382643</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA</LastName>
               <FirstName>MONICA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ALEJANDRA</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/06/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/16/2023 02:12:39</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>HERNANDEZ GARAY DE GUIROLA</LastName>
               <FirstName>MONICA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ALEJANDRA</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/06/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/16/2023 02:12:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5020</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>53rd</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hyattsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20781</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2703</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.9247606</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.9499546</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>571</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>419</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4068</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 11:15:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 11:15:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 11:15:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 11:09:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:09:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155172</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 11:16:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:16:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3FADP4BJ3KM117216</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FIE</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>ONG</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7EK9250</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>