<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-031352</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/06/2023 15:57:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/06/2023 15:57:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/06/2023 15:27:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/06/2023 15:27:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Accident, DUI,DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/06/2023 15:57:31</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4976</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 20:12:24</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>PERRYLAWN DR/ TURNPIKE DR</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>584400</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/06/2023 15:57:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 19:58:05</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>584400</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Perrylawn</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Port Deposit</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>DR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.067587</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.595857</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB RT 222 @ CHESAPEAKE OVERLOOK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>250-299 PERRYLAWN DR / 0-0 TURNPIKE DR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>230-249 PERRYLAWN DR / 0-0 TURNPIKE DR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/06/2023 15:57:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/06/2023 15:57:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/09/2023 20:12:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/06/2023 15:57:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 20:12:26</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police (MSP)  North East MSP marked car F-16 is equipped with an MVR which was recording and body camera activated Defendant: Christopher Raymond Kearns Date of Birth: 03/15/1972 Vehicle: 2016 Jeep Renegade Registration: MD 6EX3552 Time of Arrest 09/06/2023, 1557 hours Case Number# 23-MSP-031352 DUI# 23-129 Certification  Training *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFTS) by the Maryland State Police through National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) standards. *A.R.I.D. E (Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) trained by the Maryland State Police. On September 6th, 2023, at approximately 1530 hours, I TFC Mott #7053 of the Maryland State Police responded to the area Perrylawn Dr and Turnpike drive for a motor vehicle collision. Upon arrival, I made contact with Cpl Porter from the Maryland State Police JFK Highway Barrack. Cpl Porter advised it was a two-vehicle collision involving one of the drivers possibility being under the influence.  Personal Contact. I made contact with the driver of a silver Jeep Renegade displaying Maryland registration 6EX3552. The driver was identified as Christopher Raymond Kearns (DOB 03/15/1972 W/M). Kearns advised he rear ended the second vehicle in the collision at the traffic light. (See ACRS report attached). While speaking to Kearns, I observed Kearns having trouble maintaining his balance, Keanrs was also slurring his speech.  Based on these observations I requested Kearns perform Standardized Field Sobriety, I asked Kearns the following questions.  Medical conditions: Took depression and anxiety medication earlier in the day.  Injuries: Had a back injury in 1995 HORIZONTAL GAYZE NYSTAGMUS (0/6 CLUES OBSERVED) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Kearns eyes. Kearns was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Kearns pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Kearns was having a hard time keeping his eyes on the tip of the pen. During the test Kearns could not keep his eyes open. Kearns stated it was due to the sun in his eyes, Kearns was repositioned with the sun to his back. Kearns continued to close his eyes and squint. I was not able to clearly see his eyes through the duration of the test.  During the test the following clues were observed: 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Not Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Not Present 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Not Present in both eyes WALK AND TURN (6/8 CLUES OBSERVED) Prior to Kearns performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Kearns was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Kearns was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Kearns was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Kearns was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Kearns was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Kearns was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Kearns was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Kearns if he understood the test and he said he did. During the instructional stage Kearns continued to put his left foot in front of his right foot, after being told multiple time that his right foot was suppose to be in front of his left foot.  During the test the following clues were observed: Instructional Stage: Unable to maintain balance, Began the test prior to being told to begin 1St Walking Stage: Missed heal to toe, stepped off line, only took (8) eight steps, Improper turn 2nd Walking Stage: Missed heal to toe, stepped off line. ONE LEG STAND (3/4 CLUES OBSERVED) Prior to Kearns performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Kearns was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Kearns was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he said he did. Kearns chose to raise his right foot. During the test Kearns had to switch to his left foot because he could not maintain his balance.  During the test the following clues were observed: Balance and Counting: Put Foot down multiple times Hopped and almost fell over towards the roadway Swayed multiple times Based on my observations, Kearns was placed under arrest at1557 hours. Kearns was read his DR15 Advice of rights form while seated in my patrol car on roadside. At approximately 1607 hours, Kearns agreed to submit to the intoximeter test. Kearns was transported to the North East Barrack for processing. At approximately 1644 hours, Kearns successfully took the test performed by Cpl Kim and had a result of .000 Grams of alcohol per liters of breath. After receiving the breath test results, I determined that the breath test results were not consistent with the level of impairment that was observed. I then requested that a Drug Recognition Expert respond to the North East Barracks and perform a drug influence evaluation. TFC Matt Hughes #7111, a Certified Drug recognition Expert, responded to the Barrack and conducted a 12 step NHTSA/IACP approved drug evaluation of the defendant and found him to be under the influence of CNS Depressant impaired, and unable to operate a vehicle safely.  Kearns was ultimately transported to Christiana Care Union Hospital and an MSP Blood kit was completed according to policy and procedure. Kearns was transported back to the barrack and released.  Charges are pending the results of the blood kit. All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland. I request this case remain open.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 21:13:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7053</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 21:13:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mooney</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5854</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tereman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Connor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Porter</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6499</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mott</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kenneth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7053</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>520803</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>08</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/06/2023 15:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 20:08:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7053</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 20:08:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 20:07:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 20:07:33</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389174</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kearns</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Raymond</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/15/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2023 20:04:56</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kearns</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Raymond</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/15/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>K652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2023 20:04:56</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3110</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Dubois</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Parkville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21234</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.538459</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.375434</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>667</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>292</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0609</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 20:07:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 20:08:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7053</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 20:08:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/06/2023 20:02:43</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/06/2023 20:02:43</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/09/2023 20:12:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/06/2023 20:02:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 20:12:26</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Date and Time of Evaluation: 09/06/2023  1719 hours MSP Case Number: 23-MSP-031352 Other Agency Case Number: N/A Rolling Log Number: 23-007-0021 Location of Evaluation: MSP  Barrack F North East Suspect: Kearns, Christopher Raymond  Date of Birth: 03/15/1972  1. Breath Alcohol Test  The suspect agreed to the breath alcohol test when asked by Trooper First Class K. Mott #7053. The test was conducted at the North East Barrack on instrument #011750 with a breath alcohol concentration of .00 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 1644 hours.  2. Interview of Arresting Officer  On Wednesday, September 6, 2023, at approximately 1650 hours, I, TFC. M. Hughes #7111 responded to the North East Barrack in reference to an impaired driver. The duty officer, Cpl. J. Kim #6166, advised TFC. Mott was requesting a DRE for a possible DRE evaluation.   Shortly after, I arrived on scene (2433 W. Pulaski Hwy, North East, Maryland 21901), and made contact with TFC. Mott. TFC. Mott notified me of the breath test results. He then proceeded to advise me that he was dispatched to Perrylawn Drive  Turnpike Drive, Port Deposit, Maryland 21904, in reference to a two-vehicle collision. Once on scene, TFC. Mott made contact with the at fault driver who was identified as Christopher Raymond Kearns DOB: 03/15/1972. Kearns reportedly rear ended another vehicle which was stopped at a steady red signal at the aforementioned intersection.   TFC. Mott reported during his collision investigation, he noticed the following indictors which led him to believe Kearns was impaired:     Kearns was disoriented and uncoordinated as he was observed to be unsteady on his feet, having trouble standing up.  Kearns speech heard as slurred.  Kearns observed having trouble keeping his eyes open.   TFC. Mott said when asked, Kearns reported to him that he took prescription medication at approximately 1100 hours.   Due to the above observations, TFC. Mott asked Kearns if he would be willing to participate in standardized field sobriety tests. Kearns agreed to take the tests, and was subsequently arrested due to observations made by TFC. Mott during the tests.   3. Preliminary Evaluation/First Pulse  I made contact with Kearns, who located in North East Barracks intox. room. Kearns was observed seated in a slouched back like position. He appeared to be overtly relaxed, and drowsy with droopy eyelids and a flushed face.   I asked Kearns if he would participate in a DRE evaluation. Kearns advised that he was willing to talk to me and go through an evaluation. I proceeded by retrieving an MSP Form 180 (Advice of Miranda Rights). At approximately 1713 hours, I read the Form 180 to Kearns and asked him after each of these rights if he understood the right while having him initial next to each right stating that he understood them. Kearns then signed his name on the acknowledgement line. I further explained the waiver of Miranda Rights and that Kearns could invoke his rights at any time and stop participating. Kearns advised he understood and signed on the waiver line.   During the preliminary evaluation of Kearns, was heard having a slow, thick slurred speech.   Kearns gave the following answers to the following questions I asked:  What have you eaten today? Nothing. What time did you eat?  N/A. What have you been drinking and how much? (1) 12 ounce can of Pepsi. What time was your last drink? At approximately 1100 hours. What time do you believe it is now? 1700-1730 hours (actual time 1724 hours). When did you last sleep and for how long? This morning between the approximate hours of 0100 and 1100 (10 hours).  Are you sick or injured? No. Are you diabetic or epileptic? No. Do you take insulin? No. Do you have any physical defects? No. Are you under the care of a doctor or dentist? Yes (Dr. Debo  (410)300-7102).  Are you taking any medication or drugs? Yes (Klonopin, Effexor, Nexium, Flomax, Lipitor, Aspirin  an inhaler for Asthma).  Pulse #1: 88 beats per minute at 1737 hours (within the DRE normal range of 60-90 beats per minute. Due to Kearns having an extremely faint pulse in his left wrist, which he advised was due to scar tissue caused by a prior suicide attempt, his pulse rates were taking on right wrist.   4. Examination of the Eyes  During this examination, Kearns advised he does wear glasses which he had on. I asked Kearns if he had any blindness that he was aware of which he reported he did not.  Utilizing a pen as a stimulus, I advised Kearns to look at and follow the stimulus with his eyes only, keeping his head still. I asked Kearns if he understood my instructions which he stated that he did.While checking Kearns eyes, I observed his eyes as bloodshot with droopy eyelids. Kearns eyes had no resting nystagmus, and he had equal pupil size with equal tracking of the stimulus.   During the examination of the eyes, the following was observed:     Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present.  Maximum Deviation  Present.  Angel of Onset  25 degrees.  Vertical Gaze Nystagmus  Present.  Lack of Convergence  Eyes did not converge.   HGN: 6 of 6 clues.  5. Divided Attention Tests  All of the following divided attention tests were conducted in the Troopers room located inside the North East Barrack. The floor was level and free from any debris. All of the tests were explained and demonstrated to Kearns. Prior to asking Kearns to perform the tests, I asked if he understood my instructions. Kearns advised he understood all instructions provided with demonstrations. Kearns was wearing Chuck Taylor shoes during these tests.  Modified RombergBalance  During this test, I observed Kearns swaying in a circular motion which was approximately 1 inch in all directions. Kearns estimated 30 seconds of time in 19 seconds (outside the DRE normal range of plus or minus five seconds).   Walk and Turn Test  During the walk and turn test, Kearns displayed such poor coordination as he almost fell over, he was advised to stand and watch me during the instructions; therefore, he would not fall and get injured. After almost falling over, Kearns stated I have a bad knee. Kearns then remained in a semi-instructional stance with his feet not connected in a heel-to-toe position during the remainder of the instructions and demonstration.   Instructional Phase:  Could not maintain balance during instructions.  Walking Phase (1st Nine):  Stepped off line: steps one and five (towards his left  he took step one twice after almost falling over after the first attempt of step one). Missed heel-to-toe: steps two, three and four. Raised arms more than six inches from sides for balance.  Turn:  Performed satisfactorily as instructed and demonstrated.  Walking Phase (2nd Nine):  Stepped off line: steps two and six (towards his left).  Missed heel-to-toe: steps three, four, seven and eight. Stopped walking: step one (long pause after turn). Raised arms more than six inches from sides for balance. Incorrect number of steps: ten steps.  During this test, Kearns almost fell over several times as he took very slow and sluggish steps displaying an unsteady and uncoordinated walk.  WAT: 6 of 8 clues.  One Leg Stand (Raised Right Foot)  Swayed while balancing. Raised arms more than six inches from sides for balance (used chair to maintain his balance to prevent himself from falling). Puts for down on his count 10.  Kearns counted 11 seconds in the 30 seconds.  OLS: 3 of 4 clues.  One Leg Stand (Raised Left Foot)  Swayed while balancing. Raised arms more than six inches from sides for balance. Puts for down on counts 8, 11 and 12. Hopped.  Kearns counted 13 seconds in the 30 seconds.  OLS: 4 of 4 clues.  Finger to Nose  Due to Kearns complaining about being unable to stand, I offered he take this test from a seated position. Kearns elected to do so.    width:624px"&gt;          border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Hand Told to Use     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Spot on Face Touched     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Portion of Finger Used     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;Miscellaneous           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Left     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Left Nostril, then Tip of Nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;Double Tap           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Right     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Tip of Nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Left     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Left Nostril, then Tip of Nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;Trace           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Right     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Tip of Nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Right     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Tip of Nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Left     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Left Nostril, then Tip of Nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;Trace         6. Vital Signs/Second Pulse  Blood Pressure: 108/84 mmHg (below the DRE average range of 120-140/70-90 (hypotension))  reported he takes blood pressure medication. Pulse #2: 92 beats per minute at 1757 hours (with the DRE normal range of 60-90 beats per minute). Temperature: 95.6 (below the normal DRE range of 98.6 +/- 1 degree Fahrenheit (hypothermia)).   7. Dark Room Examination   width:624px"&gt;          border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:79px" valign="top"&gt;Pupil     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:154px" valign="top"&gt;Room Light    (2.5 - 5.0)     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:242px" valign="top"&gt;Near Total Darkness    (5.0 - 8.5)     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:148px" valign="top"&gt;Direct Light    (2.0 - 4.5)           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:79px" valign="top"&gt;Left     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:154px" valign="top"&gt;4.0 mm     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:242px" valign="top"&gt;6.0 mm     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:148px" valign="top"&gt;2.5 mm           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:79px" valign="top"&gt;Right     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:154px" valign="top"&gt;4.0 mm     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:242px" valign="top"&gt;6.0 mm     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:148px" valign="top"&gt;2.5 mm        Kearns pupil sizes were observed normal. Rebound Dilation: Not observed. Pupillary Reaction to Light: Slow.  Nasal Area Observations:  Clear.  Oral Cavity Observations:  Pink glazed like coating on tongue observed utilizing a UV light.    8. Muscle Tone Examination  Kearns muscle tone was normal in both arms.  9. Injection Site Examination/Third Pulse  No puncture marks observed.   Pulse #3: 88 beats per minute at 1816 hours (with the DRE normal range of 60-90 beats per minute).  10. Observations and Subject Statements  During the evaluation, Kearns was extremely cooperative. When asked what drugs or medications he was taken, Kearns reported he took the following medications today while at home:  (1) 1mg Klonopin at approximately 1100 hours. (1) 75mg Effexor at approximately 1100 hours. (2) 20mg Nexium at approximately 1100 hours. (1) 10 or 15mg Flomax at approximately 0000 hours. (1) 85mg Lipitor at approximately 0000 hours.  Kearns did report he used to be addicted to crack cocaine and cannabis; however, hes been clean from these drugs since November of 2022 shortly after moving to California in April of 2022.  11. Opinion of Evaluator  I, TFC. M. Hughes #7111, an IACP/NHTSA certified Drug Recognition Expert, conducted an IACP/NHTSA approved 12 Step Drug Influence Evaluation on Kearns and I am of the opinion that Kearns is under the influence of central nervous system depressant. Kearns is impaired and is unable to operate a vehicle safely.  My opinion is based on the following signs of impairment:     Kearns observed with bloodshot eyes.  Kearns observed having droopy eyelids.  Kearns observed being disoriented.   Kearns observed with drowsiness.  Kearns observed having a drunk like behavior while being uncoordinated.  Kearns observed having an unsteady walk with issues balancing.  Kearns heard having a slow, thick slurred speech.  Kearns observed with slow, sluggish reactions.  Kearns poor perception of time.  Kearns blood pressure being 108/84 mmHg (below the DRE average range of 120-140/70-90 (hypotension)).  Kearns body temperature being 95.6 degrees Fahrenheit (below the normal DRE range of 98.6 +/- 1 degree Fahrenheit (hypothermia)).  Kearns pupillary reaction to light being slow.  Kearns statements and admission to consuming medications.  Kearns being the at fault driver in a vehicle collision into a stopped vehicle.  Kearns displayed psychophysical impairment during psychophysical tests.   12. Toxicological Exam  I asked Kearns if he would consent to a blood test for drugs and I explained the sanctions of agreeing or disagreeing to take the test. Kearns agreed to the blood test for drugs signing the DR15. Kearns was then transported to Christiana Care Union Hospital (106 Bow Street, Elkton, Maryland 21921) by myself.  At approximately 1912 hours, I witnessed RN Robert administer the blood test for drugs. I then completed the paperwork and sealed the Blood-Kit for submission to the Maryland State Police Chemical Testing Alcohol Unit (CTAU).  After the blood test for drugs, Kearns was transported back to the North East Barrack where he was released.  13. Miscellaneous  Body-worn-camera activated capturing the DRE evaluation. MSP Blood-Kit #F-209 utilized for the blood test for drugs. Kearns was extremely polite and cooperative throughout this entire process.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 20:09:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 20:10:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4976</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hughes</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7111</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>