<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-029606</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/21/2023 21:57:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/21/2023 21:57:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/21/2023 21:34:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/21/2023 21:34:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Accident/ DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/21/2023 21:57:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5932</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/19/2023 15:37:55</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>705145</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/21/2023 21:57:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 08:35:44</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>705145</AddressId>
         <StreetName>MD-781</StreetName>
         <City>Elkton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21921</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>DR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.790602</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.608076</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/21/2023 21:57:34</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/21/2023 21:57:34</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/16/2023 01:59:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/21/2023 21:57:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:03:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police North East Barrack. Unmarked Patrol F-27 is equipped with a mobile recording device. SFST was captured on mobile recording device.  Defendant: Bertram Hodges Date of Birth: 12/11/1938 B/M Time of Arrest: 2156 hours MD DL# MD-10273283802 DUI # 23-119  TRAINING CERTIFICATES: I am trained by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. I received A.R.I.D.E. (advanced roadside impaired driving enforcement) training.   VEHICLE IN MOTION No vehicle in motion due to single vehicle collision.  PERSONAL CONTACT I, TFC Pepe of the North East Barrack contacted Bertram at approximately 2144 hours, who was standing outside his vehicle which was in a ditch approximately 20-30 feet off the roadway. Bertram was leaning on the rear of his vehicle for stability. Bertram advised that he was traveling from Ocean City, Maryland. Bertram on his own accord advised that he had a few drinks. Bertram then advised that he had two (24 ounce) bottle of Corona beer that he consumed before driving.   PRE-ARREST SCREEN The evaluation was performed on a flat level concrete sidewalk which was free of debris and no interferences.  I asked Bertram the following questions: Medical Conditions  None; does wear glasses. Injuries  None Medications  Did not advise   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Bertrams eyes. Bertram was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Bertram could not follow the tip of pen and was repeatedly told to do so during the test. Bertrams pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.  During the test the following clues were observed: 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (8/8 CLUES OBSERVED) Prior to Bertram performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Bertram was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Bertram was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Bertram was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. Bertram was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Bertram was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Bertram was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Bertram was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Bertram if he understood the test, and he said he did.  During the test the following clues were observed: Instructional Stage: Could not maintain balance; Started test too soon. 1st Walking Stage: Stopped walking, missed heel to toe, stepped off-line, and raised arms. Turn: Completed unsatisfactory. 2nd Walking Stage: Stopped walking, missed heel to toe, stepped off-line, and raised arms.  ONE LEG STAND (4/4 CLUES OBSERVED) Prior to Bertram performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Bertram was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Bertram was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he said he did.  During the test the following clues were observed: Instructional Stage: Started too soon. Balance and Counting: Could not maintain balance; Did not count out loud. Seconds 1-10: Put foot down, used arms for balance, swayed, hopped. Seconds 11-20: Put foot down, used arms for balance, swayed, hopped. Seconds 21-30: Put foot down, used arms for balance, swayed, hopped.  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Bertram was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:   Single vehicle collision.  Eyes watery and bloodshot  Slurred speech  Strong odor of alcoholic beverage from Bertrams breath  Trouble walking and talking on scene.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Clues during SFSTs: 6/6 HGN; 8/8 WAT; 4/4 OLS  I concluded Bertram had been driving under the influence and unable to safely operate a vehicle. At approximately 2156 hours on August 21, 2023. I placed Bertram under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. Bertram was transported to the Maryland State Police North East Barrack for processing.  At 2205 hours, Bertram was read his DR-15 Advise of rights form and decided to submit to the intoximeter test. The results of the test was 0.11 BrAC.Bertram was polite and cooperative during the entire process.  Bertram was given all copies of pertinent paperwork.Bertram was given a relay to his home address at 21 Transom Court, Elkton MD 21921. Bertram was informed not to drive for 12 hours.  All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland. Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/30/2023 17:47:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7054</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 21:22:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kim</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6166</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pepe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7054</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519054</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/21/2023 21:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 08:37:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7054</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 08:37:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>84</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 08:05:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7230</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/21/2023 06:12:09</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386409</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>HODGES</LastName>
               <FirstName>BERTRAM</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>CARLISLIE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/11/1938 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.67323715E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>08/29/2023 08:04:38</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H322</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B636</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>HODGES</LastName>
               <FirstName>BERTRAM</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>CARLISLIE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/11/1938 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.67323715E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>H322</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B636</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/29/2023 08:04:38</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>21</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Transom</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Elkton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21921</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6253</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.789279</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.611632</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 08:05:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 08:05:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 08:37:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7054</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 08:37:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156574</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/30/2023 12:26:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7054</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/30/2023 12:26:42</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FADP5DU1HL118419</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ECP</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>15648CH</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>