<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-019023</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/28/2023 02:02:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/28/2023 02:02:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/28/2023 01:20:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/28/2023 01:20:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI; vehicle crash, use of force. Drug arrest, criminal arrest, 2nd degree assault.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:02:34</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4913</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/12/2023 14:20:58</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>133 DOCK ST,ANNAPOLIS</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>695546</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:02:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 17:03:24</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>695546</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Craig</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Annapolis</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21401</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.485377</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.977745</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/28/2023 02:02:32</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/28/2023 02:02:32</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/06/2023 21:25:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:02:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:53:52</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Incident recorded on my Body-worn camera. DUI NARRATIVE Nathaniel Hitch 7051  DUI INFORMATION Defendant: DUNN, EVAN MATTHEW Date of Birth: 06/30/1998 License Number: MD - D500238589517 Date of Arrest: 05/28/2023 CC#: 23-MSP-019023 (Annapolis Barrack) Time of arrest: 0202 hours.  Training and Awards Recipient of the Maryland Highway Safety Offices DUI award for 2021. Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Trained in administering the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Trained in A.R.I.D.E. (Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Attended the MSP Enhanced DUI class provided through the Maryland State Police SPIDRE Team. Attendee of the 2022 Ocean City DUI conference.   Vehicle in motion:  N/A  Personal Contact:  On 05/28/2023 at approximately 0146 hours I, TFC. Hitch #7051 was on duty in downtown Annapolis city assisting Annapolis City Police Department with crowd control. During this time I walked onto Prince George St. off Craig St. and observed a tan Toyota Camry bearing a South Carolina registration plate of TFL624 that had crashed into an unoccupied parked vehicle (MD - 4FC6586; blue Honda CR-V) on Prince George St. I observed that the registered owner of the vehicle was standing outside his vehicle yelling while several police officers stood around him.  I later identified the driver of the Camry by his Maryland Drivers license as Dunn, Evan Matthew (MD - D500238589517; DOB - 06/30/1998; White Male). Dunn was slurring his speech, had bloodshot and glassy eyes, and the strong odors of both marijuana and an alcoholic beverage emanated off his breath and person. Dunn was behaving erratically, yelling over the questions of officers, and repeatedly asking to go into his vehicle. Dunn had physical injuries that were consistent with a vehicle collision. His lip was bleeding, and he had blood on his face and shirt. His hands appeared to have cuts on them as well. I would later observe injuries on his hands and fingers during routine handcuffing. Also, I would later observe bruising on Dunns chest, possibly caused by a seat-belt or other collision related impact.    I spoke with Annapolis City Police officer Vennekotter #6148, who advised me that it appeared from Dunns statements that he was traveling too fast around the corner and drove into the rear of the parked Honda SUV.    During this time, Dunnappeared emotionally unstable. He talked almost non-stop and would shift from aggressive behavior (yelling, cursing, demanding behavior) to softer sad manic behavior (crying). He would sit down, then demand to stand up, and he continued insisting that he needed to grab his vehicles registration and insurance.    OFC Vennekotter spoke to Dunn and asked him if he would like to be seen by a medic, Dunn replied no I would not. Dunn then began talking about how the vehicle damage would be out of pocket, Dunn then stated because I wanna speed, because I wanna speed. Dunn continued erratic and aggressive behavior throughout this time.    I stepped in and spoke to Dunn, telling him to stop and sit down due to his erratic behavior. Dunn stood in my face and stated take me to jail. He repeated this statement several times. I asked Dunn how much he had to drink that night, Dunn stated in total or since when. I clarified from 1700 on. Dunn stated I started in Waugh Chapel, I had twomichelob ultras, two blue moons. I went, uh, chicken wings, sobered up, came out to Baltimore, Im fine. I asked Dunn how much he had drank since he was in Annapolis, Dunn ignored that question.   I advised Dunn that I could see that his eyes were red, Dunn replied yeah cause I smoke a lot of weed man. I asked Dunn when he had smoked marijuana last, Dunn stated all the time, every day, I have problems man. I again asked Dunn how much he had to drink since being in Annapolis that night, Dunn replied only two beer. Dunn then began stating that he was fine and that he was upset. Dunn then stated Im high, off marijuana. Throughout all of this interaction, Dunn was slurring his words significantly, and the strong odor of both marijuana and an alcoholic beverage emanated off his breath and person as he moved. Dunn was unable and unwilling to stand still or remain silence for any period longer than a few seconds.  EMS personnel came over to Dunn and asked him if he wanted to be seen by EMS, Dunn stated no and signed a medical form advising of his choice. The EMS report number is 202336768.  Due to the odor of marijuana and alcohol emanating off of Dunn, his admission to being high and drinking alcohol that night, and due to the nature of the vehicle collision, I suspected that Dunn was impaired by an intoxicating substance. Dunn agreed to submit to the Standardized Field Sobriety tests.  Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3) The evaluation was performed in on the sidewalk next to Dunns vehicle. The roadway was lit by streetlamps. The evaluation was performed on a dry and debris-free surface.  I asked Dunn the basic medical questions as they relate to the Standardized Field Sobriety Test. His answers are located in the below text: Are you wearing contacts  No. Do you have any head, neck, back, or leg injuries  Yes. Dunn declined to answer what the nature of his injuries were. Do you take any medications  No.  Do you have any medical issues I need to be aware of  No.  The weather conditions were cool and dry. Dunn appeared to be in good physical condition.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6 clues observed)  The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Dunns pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking and no resting Nystagmus was observed.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus  Present in both eyes.  Lack of Convergence test:   The LOC test was completed on Dunn immediately after the HGN test due to Dunns difficult behavior. The test showed significantly Lack of Convergence as my stimulus approached the bridge of Dunns nose.   Throughout the HGN test, Dunn becoming increasing verbally combative. He would stop the test repeatedly, back away from me, or ignore my instructions. Dunn repeated that he knew I wanted to take him in, and stated on one occasion that he wasnt even looking at my stimulus for the HGN test. Due to his combative nature, I believed that continuing the Walk and Turn and One Leg Stand tests would be extremely difficult and possibly dangerous if Dunn became physically combative.  Walk and Turn  Test terminated.  One Leg Stand Test terminated.  Preliminary breath test  Not offered.   After completing part of the SFSTs unsatisfactorily and continuing to be irate and verbally combative, I placed Dunn under arrest for DUI at 0202 hours for the following reasons.   The nature of Dunns vehicle collision.    Dunns verbally combative behavior.         Dunns erratic emotional state.   Bloodshot eyes.   Slurred speech   Admission to currently being high on Marijuana and smoking Marijuana throughout the day.   Admission to drinking throughout the day, and specifically two beers since he had been in Annapolis that night.  Once Dunn was arrested, he became further irate and verbally abusive. Dunn also became physically combative, and would jerk away from me while he was in handcuffs. Dunn was spitting while in handcuffs and making erratic movements. At one point, Dunn planted his feet, and jerked away from me with his full body, I believed Dunn was trying to resist being lawfully arrested and was trying to pull away from me. I then pulled Dunn to the ground backwards to stop his physically combative behavior. I made sure that Dunn was placed on the ground in a manner as to prevent injury, as my intention was simply to stop his physically resistant behavior. Once on the ground, Dunn continued to be verbally abusive, but eventually stood up again with my assistance. Dunn also stated that he did not feel well and wanted EMS. Another police officer that was assisting me stated to Dunn that he would still go to jail afterwards. Dunn then changed his mind, and began screaming take me in. I asked Dunn if he still wanted EMS, Dunn just continued repeating take me in.  Dunn was placed in Annapolis Police Officer A. Nettas (#7059) patrol vehicle in order to escort him to my car. Dunn began to resist being put inside the vehicle. I remained patient with Dunn, but eventually physically placed him inside Nettas patrol vehicle due to him stalling. I gently pushed Dunn onto the passenger seat and physically place his left leg inside the vehicle. Due to this behavior, Officer Netta agreed to transport Dunn to the Anne Arundel County Detention center with me driving behind her. During the ride, Dunn spat on Nettas uniform and computer, and bit Nettas computer. Dunn continued to be verbally combative and abusive.  Once at the detention center, a search of Dunn revealed CDS not Marijuana of suspected Alprazolam (XANAX) in his groin area. Dunn had to be dragged to a holding cell due to his uncooperative and combative behavior.   Due to Dunns behavior, the DR-15 form was not able to be read to him before he was placed in a holding cell. Dunns prior behavior was too erratic and dangerous to allow for me to safely process him. Therefore, the forms were noted that he was unable to sign, and he was left copies of the DR-15 and DR-15A at the Detention center.   TFC. Tyler #6787 responded to the detention center to assist me. He took possession of the suspected CDS and transported it back to the barrack for processing. It was logged on a chain of custody log and a property held record prior to being placed in the Barrack J CDS locker.   All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 08:08:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 15:26:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tyler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Marlyn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6787</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gerber</LastName>
            <FirstName>Elix</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5226</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Netta</LastName>
            <FirstName>A.</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7059</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hitch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7051</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gerber</LastName>
            <FirstName>Elix</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5226</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hitch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7051</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hitch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7051</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508457</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 02:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:22:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 16:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508457</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 01:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:27:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 16:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508457</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0600</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 01:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0600</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:27:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 16:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508457</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1416</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 01:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1416</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:28:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 16:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508457</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 01:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:29:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 16:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508457</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 01:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:31:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 16:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508457</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 02:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:32:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 16:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508457</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 02:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:32:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 16:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508457</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 02:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:33:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 16:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508457</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 01:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:36:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 16:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508457</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>12</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 01:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 13:06:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 16:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:22:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:55</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>105365</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dunn</LastName>
               <FirstName>Evan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Matthew</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/30/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.1353527E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2016 16:18:36</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dunn</LastName>
               <FirstName>Evan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Matthew</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/30/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.1353527E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>D500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2016 16:18:36</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>999</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>CROUSE MILL</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>KEYMAR</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.21080122020238</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.60308038201738</Latitude>
               <SubBeat>566</SubBeat>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>313</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>BEAUMONT </StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>CATONSVILLE</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21228</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.746885</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.278791</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>510</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6752</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 17:00:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 17:00:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 17:00:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:43:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378217</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Netta</LastName>
               <FirstName>A</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 07:41:48</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A000</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Netta</LastName>
               <FirstName>A</FirstName>
               <SLastName>N300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A000</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 07:41:48</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>199</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>TAYLOR</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>ANNAPOLIS</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.50570035603062</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.979178863995635</Latitude>
               <SubBeat>659</SubBeat>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>693</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2781</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 16:59:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 16:59:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:24:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 07:24:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153495</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:48:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 07:48:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>4T1BD1FK1DU065283</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CAM</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>TAN</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>TAN</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>SC</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>TFL624</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 07:50:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 07:50:13</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One glass pill bottle containing suspected Alprazolam (XANAX). </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249516</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>O</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>66</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>