<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-016514</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/09/2023 11:50:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/09/2023 11:50:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/08/2023 09:21:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/08/2023 09:21:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>1st Degree Assault, Collision, Reckless Endangerment</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/09/2023 11:50:25</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0392</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/21/2023 10:37:19</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>RKE</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>RT. 5 / SURRATTS RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>693376</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/09/2023 11:50:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/13/2023 20:24:50</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>693376</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>0</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Branch</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Clinton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20735</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.879525</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.751097</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/09/2023 11:50:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/09/2023 11:50:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/21/2023 10:36:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/09/2023 11:50:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:40</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Unmarked Car L-32: Due to the nature of this incident, there is no in-car camera footage available.  Body Worn Camera: Body-worn camera available - Cpl. A Oleyar #6495  Assisting Troopers/Officers: First Sergeant Wiesemann #5573 - Body-worn camera available.   Case Number: 23-MSP-016514  Date: 5/08/2023  Time: 0922 hours  Location: N/B Rt 5 N/O Surratts Rd    ATTACHMENTS:        MVA Print Outs      ACRS report      Application for charges      Witness Statement       VICTIM / COMPLAINANT:    Colby Celine Charissa Oliver / DOB 7/5/2000 / 1/F  9703 Digby Ct, Clinton, MD 20735  301-710-4211    When I met her at the Forestville Barrack, Ms. Oliver was seated in the front lobby. Oliver was very emotional and, initially, had difficulty providing a statement. After taking some time to calm down, Oliver was able to explain that she had just merged onto northbound MD RT 5 from Surratts Road when her vehicle was struck from behind. Oliver continued to state that both her and the other vehicle then pulled to the shoulder and began the process of exchanging information. Oliver continued to state that at one point the other driver became irate and attempted to make entry into her vehicle and was successful for a brief moment. Oliver then stated that she rolled her windows up and locked her doors. She then advised that the other driver became more angry and began to strike her vehicle with her hands and feet and threatened to shoot her. At this point, Oliver advised that she feared for safety and quickly left the scene. Oliver stated that the other driver immediately gave chase causing at least one more minor collision in the process. Oliver seemed convinced that, aside from the initial collision, all further collisions were intentional. Oliver continued to state that while fleeing, the other driver pulled alongside her vehicle, rolled down her window, and pointed a reflective silver colored handgun at her. Oliver finalized her statement by explaining that shortly afterward the two vehicles lost contact and she made her way to the Forestville Barrack. Oliver completed a witness statement form that can be found attached to this report.  WITNESS / NEIGHBORHOOD CHECKS:    Due to the nature of this incident, no neighborhood checks were completed and no witnesses were identified.    SUSPECT:    Breanna Ray-Shane Louis / DOB 11/13/1998 / 1/F  4813 Kempair Dr, Woodbridge, VA 22193  571-513-9186   The suspects statement is detailed in the narrative found below.    SCENE PROCESSING:    While on scene, I used my MSP issued body camera to record the damage done to Olivers vehicle. I had Oliver complete an MSP 076 witness statement form. Lastly I watched approximately five short videos that Olvier had taken while attempting to flee from Louis. I watched all of those videos so that my body camera would capture the footage presented. From these videos I was immediately able to determine how hostile Louis was on the scene of the collision, I was able to get a good photo to use for identifying Louis, and I was able to get a description of Louis vehicle, to include her registration number.    NARRATIVE:    Upon arriving at the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack at approximately 0945 hours, I made contact with the victim, Ms. Oliver. Oliver was clearly upset and still shaken from the events that had occurred. She was accompanied by her mother and father, Rollia and Robert Oliver. Ms. Oliver provided me with the statement detailed above. During my interview with Oliver, she was able to show me approximately five videos that she took during the altercation. Oliver advised that the incident occurred on Branch Avenue at Surratts Road, and continued, for the duration, in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  I then took the vehicle information that I was able to pull from one of Olivers videos, and ran it through METERS/NCIC and determined that the vehicle owner was Breanna Ray-Shane Louis. Utilizing TLO I was able to verify that Ms. Louis date of birth was 11/13/1998 and was given five possible phone numbers for Louis. The first number I called (571-513-9186) was Louis phone number, but did not answer. The second number (404-412-5696) was a deactivated number. The third number (808-421-9712) was Louis mother. Louis mother advised that the first number that I had called, was in fact, Breanna Louis number. I then asked Louis mother what kind of vehicle Louis drives. She verified that Louis owns a blue Chevrolet. I then asked if she knows if Louis is the sole owner/operator of that vehicle. Louis mother advised that Louis is the only person who drives that blue Chevrolet. I then called Louis number again without making contact and left a voicemail.   On May 13th, 2023 at approximately 1630 hours, I made contact with Louis at the above listed number. Louis confirmed her name and date of birth. I then asked if she recalled the events that occurred on May 8th in the area of MD RT 5 at Surratts Road. Louis advised that she recalled the events and stated that as she was traveling northbound on MD RT 5, another vehicle struck her vehicle as it entered the roadway from Surratts Road. She then stated that her and the other vehicle both pulled to the shoulder, and attempted to exchange information. Louis then continued to state that after approximately 20 minutes of waiting and attempting to facilitate that exchange, the other driver fled the scene of the collision. She then continued to state that she quickly chased after the vehicle. At this time I notified Louis of the accusations lodged against her, namely that she had pointed a firearm at Ms. Oliver. Louis initially denied this. I then asked if she possesses any firearms whatsoever. Louis advised that she has a black Smith and Wesson handgun and nothing else. Discussing these allegations seemed to agitate Louis, who stated that she would then like to press charges on Oliver for fleeing the scene of the collision. At this time, I advised Louis I would certainly look into that for her, continuing to state that Oliver had taken numerous videos of the events that occurred and that while investigating if I discovered that Louis did brandish a firearm, I would take action against her. Upon hearing this, Louis was very quick to change her mind and decided not to pursue charges against Oliver. Due to the fact that Louis was at work when we spoke, she was unable to provide me with her insurance information. I then called Louis back at approximately 1800 hours on May 13th, 2023. While speaking with Louis I informed her that I had just met with Oliver and watched the videos and could clearly see a silver handgun in her hand in one of the videos. Even though I had not seen that in any video up to that point, Louis became quiet. I then asked if, at any point during the altercation, she was holding a handgun, to which she responded yes. I then asked what kind of handgun it was. Louis advised that it was the same gun that she mentioned earlier, a Smith and Wesson handgun. I then clarified, asking if the gun was silver rather than black as she mentioned earlier. Louis confirmed that this was true. I then asked why she brandished the handgun, to which Louis stated that she was scared. I then asked Louis if she pointed the gun directly at Oliver, to which she indicated that she had not. The entirety of this phone interview with Louis was conducted over the recorded line at the Forestville Barrack Duty Office. An ACRS report (23MSP016514) has also been completed and can be found attached to this report.   Due to the above stated information, I have applied for a warrant for the arrest of Breanna Ray-Shane Louis for the following charges:  * First Degree Assault - CR 3-202  * Second Degree Assault - CR 3-203  * Reckless endangerment - CR 3-204 (a)(1)  * Handgun in vehicle - CR 4-203    All the above events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.    Case open pending warrant/summons service. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/13/2023 20:53:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6495</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 16:54:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wiesemann</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5573</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Landis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dwayne</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5082</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0392</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oleyar</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6495</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505936</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>01</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1420</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/08/2023 09:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/13/2023 20:29:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6495</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 17:36:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505936</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>01</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1425</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/08/2023 09:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/13/2023 20:37:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6495</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 17:36:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505936</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>01</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4D</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/08/2023 09:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 17:36:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6495</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 17:36:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505936</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>01</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0175</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/08/2023 09:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 17:38:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6495</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 17:38:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/13/2023 20:45:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:03</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>376953</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Louis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Breanna</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ray-Shane</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/13/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/13/2023 20:44:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Louis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Breanna</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ray-Shane</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/13/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/13/2023 20:44:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4813</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Kempair</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Woodbridge</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>22193</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.3479638499599</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.658749042665924</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>571</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>513</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9186</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/13/2023 21:01:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/13/2023 20:50:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:57</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>376954</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Oliver</LastName>
               <FirstName>Colby</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Celine Charissa</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/05/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/13/2023 20:49:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>O416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C410</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Oliver</LastName>
               <FirstName>Colby</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Celine Charissa</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/05/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>O416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C410</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/13/2023 20:49:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9703</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Digby</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Clinton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20735</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.850776</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.757362</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>710</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4211</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 17:38:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 17:38:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6495</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 17:38:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152972</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>VI</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/13/2023 20:51:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6495</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/13/2023 20:51:05</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1G4GB5G30FF322676</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>BUIC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>LAX</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9CK5300</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152971</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/13/2023 20:51:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6495</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/13/2023 20:51:54</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1G1PF5S93B7225442</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SEDAN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>UFE5588</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/18/2023 11:27:05</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/18/2023 11:27:05</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/21/2023 10:36:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 11:27:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:40</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 8/18/2023 at approximately 1105 hours, I, Corporal Oleyar, checked the status of the warrant issued in this case. As of this date and time the warrant issued for Breanna Ray-Shane Louis is still active and has not been served. As Louis lives out of state, I request this case be considered closed and to be reopened upon service of her warrant.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6495</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 11:28:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6495</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 11:31:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0392</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oleyar</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6495</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>