<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-037913</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/28/2023 02:10:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/28/2023 02:10:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/28/2023 01:39:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/28/2023 01:39:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Suspect was arrest for suspected of driving under the influence of alcohol.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 02:10:26</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1865</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 14:32:34</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>711277</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 02:10:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/28/2023 06:44:09</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>711277</AddressId>
         <StreetName>St Johns</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Hollywood</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20636</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.60081</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.32135</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>43030-43217 (MEREDITH CT)</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/28/2023 02:10:22</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/28/2023 02:10:22</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/18/2023 00:53:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 02:10:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 20:22:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Body Camera Worn Operational  Defendant: Young, Tamika Rochelle Date of Birth: 01/02/1986 Date of Arrest: 10/28/2023 Time of Arrest: 0211 MD-Soundex#: Y520785744007 DUI #: 23-112  Narrative: On October 28, 2023 at approximately 0140 hours, I, Trooper Oliva Flores #7668, was on duty in full uniform operating marked patrol vehicle T-24. I responded to a single vehicle collisionat St. Johns and Meredith Court, Hollywood, St. Marys County, Maryland 20636.  Upon arriving on scene, I observed a black Jeep Wrangler, bearing Maryland registration of 1ER0563. I observed the vehicles roof scattered on the southbound lane of St. Johns. I then observed the black jeep to be in the northbound lane of St. Johns sitting on all four wheels with multiple airbags deployed and all glass on the vehicle to be shattered. I then observed two occupants standing out to the rear of the vehicle. I observed that one of the occupants, who was subsequently identified, verbally and by MVA photo, as George Wayne Armiger Jr (W/M DOB: 11/03/1977), had blood all over his face and his right arm, his right arm had large swelling and bruising. Trooper Hersh provided medical assistance and Emergency Medical Services were dispatched. I then made contactwith the operator, who was subsequentlyidentified, verbally and by MVA photo,as Tamika Rochelle Young (B/F DOB: 01/02/1986). I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholicbeverageemanatingfrom Youngs breath and person. I also observed Young to have bloodshot and glassy eyes, her speech to be slurred, and she was also stumbling as she stood upright. Young stated that she was coming from picking up Armiger from the Last Drop bar. Young advised that she consumed a shot of an alcoholic beverage prior to the collision. Young advised verbally stated she was the operator the vehicle at the time of the collision.    Vehicle in motion (Phase 1):   Based upon the totality of the circumstances, vehicle in motion is not applicable. Personal Contact (Phase 2):  I made contact with Young, who was standing at the rear of the black Jeep. I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Youngs person. I advised Young of her Miranda Rights, which she voluntarily waived. Young advised that she was coming from the Last Drop bar located in Leonardtown, Maryland before subsequently crashing her vehicle. Young advised that she had only had consumed one shot of an alcoholic beverage. It should be noted that Young then advised me that she had consumed two shots of orange whiskey. As I spoke with Young, I made the following observations:   Young had slurred speech.  Youngs breath was emitting a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage.  Youngs eyes were bloodshot and glossy.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Young could not keep balance while standing up.   Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3):  The evaluation was performed behind the vehicle collision and was captured on my body camera. The surface was level and free of any debris. The weather was clear and there was no standing water/ice in the immediate area. Lighting conditions consisted of multiple patrol vehicles headlights and outdoor street lighting. I asked Young if she was wearing any contacts, Young answered No. I proceeded to ask Young if she has taken any medications prior to our encounter, Young answered Yes. Young advised she takes Ibuprofen for tooth pain. Young did not specify exactly when she took the Ibuprofen. Young appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any limps or any limb ailments. Young was wearing Blue jeans, a black pullover hoodie, and black tennis shoes.  ** Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus ** (6/6 Clues)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Youngs eyes and slightly above eye level. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes only. Youngs pupils were equal in size, showed equal tracking, and no resting nystagmus. I asked Young if she understood the directions, and she stated Yes.    Young displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   Young displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Young displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  Additional Observations:  Vertical gaze nystagmus was observed in both eyes during the test. Youngs eyes were blood shot and glossy.  ** Walk and Turn ** (6/8 Clues) Prior to Young performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be completed. Young was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Young was instructed to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in the starting position until told to begin. I advised Young to take nine (9) steps on the yellow solid yellow line on the pavement, touching heel to toe on every step. Young was told to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Young was demonstrated and explained to keep her front foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around in a counterclockwise direction. During the demonstration, I demonstrated three (3) of the nine steps, both before and after the turn. Young was instructed once she began the test, she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look down at her feet and count every step out loud. After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Young if he completely understood the instructions, and she stated, Yes. Instructional stage:  Young could not stay balanced during the instructional phase. Young could not remain in the starting position without losing her balance, as the walk and turn test was being demonstrated. Walking Stage (1st Set of Nine):     Young missed heal to toe on the following steps: 1,2,3,4,5,6, and 8.   Young stepped off-line on the following steps: 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8 and 9  Young used her arms for balanced. Young raised her arms almost parallel to the ground to maintain balance.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Young stopped during the test.  Turn:  Completed unsatisfactorily. Young pivoted on her right heal to complete the turn, while doing so Young lost balanced and raised her arms almost parallel to the ground to regain her balance. Walking Stage (2nd Set of Nine):    Young missed heal to toe on the following steps: 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8 and 9.   Young stepped off-line on the following steps: 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8, and 9.   Young used her arms for balance. Young raised her arms almost parallel to the ground to maintain balance.  Young stopped during the test.   ** One Leg Stand ** (0/4 clues): Young refused to complete one leg stand.  Primarily Breath Test (PBT) Results: Young refused to take PBT.  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Young was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:    Statements and observations made on scene.  Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Youngs breath and person.  Youngs eyes were glassy and bloodshot.  I observed signs of impairment as Young performed SFST.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Young had slurred speech.   Arrest: 0211 hours        Young was placed under arrest at 0211 for driving under the influence. After placing Young in handcuffs, she started to become agitated and yell at me and Trooper Hersh when we did not provide her with a direct answer as to if Armiger was ok. I placed Young in the front right passenger seat of T24 patrol vehicle. I fastened the seat belt for young and once fastened inside T24 patrol vehicle, I started to play the English audio version of the DR-15, Advise of Rights. As I started to drive off the scene of the single vehicle collision and head towards the Maryland State Police Leonardtown Barrack T, Young started to become agitated and began to yell at me to see if Armiger was ok. Young agreed to submit to intoximeter testing and signed the DR-15 indicating the same (0320). The intoximeter test was administered at St. Marys County Sheriffs Office Headquarters station by SGT. S. Kerby #242. It should be noted that when transporting Young to St. Marys Sheriffs Office Headquarters Station, she became very agitated and started to yell. Young as well started to kick T24 patrol vehicles dash and passenger side door repeatedly. I had to constantly advised Young that Armiger was fine and being transported to a hospital. It should be noted that Young seemed to have trouble remembering when being advised that Armiger was ok. While SGT. Kerby was preparing the intoximeter test, Young fell asleep on the bench. Youngs intoximetertest results were 0.21 BrAC. Young was then transported to St. Marys Hospital to be medically seen and cleared due to making statements when she initially arrived at the Barrack that her thumbs were broken. It should be noted that medical treatment was offered multiple times to Young, but she constantly refused. Upon arrival at St. Marys Hospital, the hospital staff medically cleared Young. She was then transported to the St. Marys County Detention and RehabilitationCenter.While Young was being processed, she blurted out that she had drank a lot of alcoholic beverages and that she was very drunk. Young was issued the following traffic citations TA 21-902(a1I) Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol, TA 21-902 (b1i) Driving a Vehicle while Impaired by Alcohol, TA 21- 901.1 (b) Negligent Driving, TA 16-101 (a1) Driving motor vehicle on highway without required license, and TA 21-902 (a1ii) Driving under influence of alcohol per se.  All events occurred in St. Marys County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7668</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 09:03:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7668</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/10/2023 23:13:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hersh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Taylor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7443</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5920</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Olivaflores</LastName>
            <FirstName>Denis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7668</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>527377</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/28/2023 01:39:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7668</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 06:52:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7668</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/28/2023 06:52:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>527377</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/28/2023 01:39:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7668</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 06:53:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7668</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/28/2023 06:53:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>527377</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/28/2023 01:39:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7668</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 06:54:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7668</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/28/2023 06:54:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7668</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 06:55:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7668</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/28/2023 09:27:46</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>247186</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Young</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tamika</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rochelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/02/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/29/2019 14:55:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>Y520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Young</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tamika</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rochelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/02/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>Y520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/29/2019 14:55:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>40304</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sunnyside</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Loveville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20656</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2010</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.6824405</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.3350972</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>561</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5537</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/29/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7668</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 09:27:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7668</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 09:27:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7668</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 06:56:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/28/2023 06:56:17</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>337123</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Armiger</LastName>
               <FirstName>George</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/03/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>03/12/2022 01:01:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Armiger</LastName>
               <FirstName>George</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/03/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>A652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/12/2022 01:01:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>40390</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Coonhunters</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Mechanicsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.6783805</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.385604</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>577</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8864</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/12/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PA</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7668</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 06:56:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7668</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 06:52:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7668</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/28/2023 06:52:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158454</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AC</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7668</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 06:59:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7668</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/28/2023 06:59:15</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C4PJXDN6RW108966</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2024</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>WRG</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>LL</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1ER0563</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>6</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>