<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-041183</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/20/2023 19:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/20/2023 19:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/20/2023 18:56:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/20/2023 18:56:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was involved in a motor vehicle collision. The suspect was subsequently arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/20/2023 19:54:39</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/07/2023 14:27:17</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>714412</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/20/2023 19:54:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/28/2023 00:57:59</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>714412</AddressId>
         <StreetName>E/B MD 140 @ Leidy </StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21157</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.962492</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.557263</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/20/2023 19:54:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/20/2023 19:54:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/07/2023 11:10:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/20/2023 19:54:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on BWC.  Defendant: Pedro Nolasco Portillo Date of Birth: 07/06/1989 Date of Arrest: 10/02/2023 Time of Arrest: 1948 Maryland Drivers License: MD-10272838415 DUI #: 23-175  Officers Training/Experience * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police. * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police.  *Repeat Offender*No  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) Not observed.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)    On 11/20/2023 at approximately 1856 hours, I (TFC J. Reid #7215) responded to the area of Eastbound Baltimore Blvd (MD 140) in the area of Leidy Rd for the report of a motor vehicle crash. Upon my arrival, I located a blue Nissan Sentra with all around damage to the vehicle, and air bag deployment, resting against the guardrail on the left side of the roadway. The vehicle was unoccupied at the time. I ran the vehicles Maryland registration 5DP4265 which showed the vehicle was registered to an individual named, Pedro Nolasco Portillo (H/M DOB: 07/06/1989). I was advised by the MSP Westminster barrack that the caller who reported the crash stated his name was Pedro. I called the caller on the number he initially called 911 on. The caller advised he walked over to the Chevrolet dealership across the street and was on his way back to the accident scene. A short time later, I observed a Hispanic male walking from the parking lot of the Chevrolet dealership towards the scene of the motor vehicle crash. I was able to positively identify the male by the photograph on his Maryland drivers license as the registered owner of the vehicle, Nolasco Portillo. I asked Nolasco Portillo what happened. Nolasco Portillo has a very thick accent and was difficult to understand, however, he advised he was driving Eastbound in his vehicle when another vehicle struck him and spun his car out and into the guardrail. While I was speaking with Nolasco Portillo, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his breath, I observed his eyes to be bloodshot and watery, and I observed him to be swaying back and forth slightly while he was standing.  I asked Nolasco Portillo if he recently consumed any alcoholic beverages, and he stated no. I asked Nolasco Portillo where he was coming from and due to his heavy accent, I was not able to understand what he said. Due to the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his breath, his eyes being bloodshot and watery, and him swaying, I asked Nolasco Portillo if he was willing to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and he agreed. Prior to conducting the test I requested the assistance of a Spanish interpreter to translate my instructions to Nolasco Portillo, however, I was advised by the MSP Westminster barrack that, neither the county sheriffs office, or the Westminster City Police had a Spanish interpreter working. Despite having a heavy accent, and there being a mild language barrier, Nolasco Portillo appeared to understand everything I was saying and asking him.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   The test were conducted in lane 1 of Eastbound MD 140. The roadway was level and the immediate area was free from any debris. Prior to conducting the tests, I asked Nolasco Portillo the following questions:   Medical Conditions  None.  Prescription Medication  None.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Recent Injuries  He stated his knee hurts.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed):  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. Prior to the test being performed, I explained the test to Nolasco Portillo. I asked Nolasco Portillo to stand with his heels and toes together and to place his arms flat at his sides. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus for this test. The stimulus was held approximately 12-15 inches from Nolasco Portillos eyes. I advised Nolasco Portillo I was going to move the stimulus back and forth. I asked Nolasco Portillo if he understood the test, and he nodded his head yes, and stated, Yea.  Nolasco Portillos pupils were equal in size and showed no resting nystagmus. Nolasco Portillo had equal tracking in both eyes.  Lack of smooth pursuit  Present in both eyes Distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation  Present in both eyes Onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees  Present in both eyes Vertical Nystagmus  Not observed.    WALK AND TURN (2/8):   The next test was the Walk and Turn Test. The ground where the test was performed was level and free from any debris. Prior to Nolasco Portillo performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I asked Nolasco Portillo if he could imagine a straight line directly in front of him and he stated, Yes. I then explained and demonstrated to Nolasco Portillo to place his left foot on this imaginary line and to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot touching heel-to-toe. Nolasco Portillo had to be told multiple time to get into and stay in that position. Once Nolasco Portillo was in the instructional position, I told his to stay in that position and not to begin the test until I instructed him to begin. While Nolasco Portillo was in the instructional position, I explained and demonstrated how the rest of the test was to be performed. I advised Nolasco Portillo when I instructed him to begin, he was going to take nine heel to toe steps down the imaginary line. I advised Nolasco Portillo he was to keep his arms flat at his sides, look down at his feet, and to count each step out loud. I advised Nolasco Portillo when he got to his ninth step, he was to keep his lead foot planted and to use his rear foot to take a series of small steps to turn completely around to the left. I then explained and demonstrated to Nolasco Portillo that he was to take a second series of nine heel to toe steps identical to the first nine. I asked Nolasco Portillo if he understood the test and my instructions and he said yes.  Instructional Stage:   Nolasco Portillo pulled out his phone and began using his phone while I was explaining and demonstrating the test.  Walking (First 9):   Nolasco Portillo took 21 steps instead of 9.  Nolasco Portillo missed heel to toe on step 8 and 16  Turn:   Not performed.  Walking (Second 9):   Not performed.  ONE LEG STAND (1/4 clues observed):    The next test was the One Leg Stand test. Prior to Nolasco Portillo performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test was to be performed. I instructed Nolasco Portillo to stand with his heels and toes together and to place his arms flat at his sides, and he complied. I explained and demonstrated that when I instructed him to begin, Nolasco Portillo was to raise the foot of his choice approximately six inches off the ground, point his toe, look down at his foot, and to start counting out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand two, etc.).  Balance and count:   Nolasco Portillo put his foot down on second 2, 9, 19, and 24   Nolasco Portillo switched feet on second 24.   ARREST  Based on the following,Ihad reason to believe Nolasco Portillo was driving a motor vehicle under the influence:  1) Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his breath 2) Bloodshot and watery eyes 3) Swaying while standing 4) Clues during field sobriety testing    Preliminary breath test - .15 BrAC   Due to my numerous observations, I concluded Nolasco Portillo had been driving under the influence, and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 1948 hours, I placed Nolasco Portillo under arrest for driving under the influence. Nolasco Portillo was placed in the front seat of my patrol car with his hands handcuffed behind his back per MSP policy. A search incident to arrest revealed the keys to the crashed vehicle in Nolasco Portillos pocket. Nolasco Portillo was then transported back to the MSP Westminster barrack for processing.  While at the Westminster barrack, Nolasco Portillo was played the Spanish version of the DR-15 advice of rights audio and given a copy in Spanish to read over. Nolasco Portillo signed the DR-15 at 2017 hours, and agreed to submit to a preliminary breath test.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  ***.13 BrAC***  Nolasco Portillo was charged with Driving Under the Influence, and all other appropriate traffic related charges in reference to the accident.  Nolasco Portillo was given copies of all pertinent paperwork and released into the custody of a sober driver.  An accident report was completed via Delta Plus.  All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 01:11:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/28/2023 02:53:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Frye</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7198</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Karas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5562</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reid</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7215</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>530653</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/20/2023 18:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>530653</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/20/2023 18:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>530653</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/20/2023 18:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>530653</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/20/2023 18:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>530653</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/20/2023 18:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 01:07:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/28/2023 03:04:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>394010</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Nolasco Portillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Pedro</FirstName>
               <DOB>07/06/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/28/2023 01:06:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N421</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P360</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Nolasco Portillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Pedro</FirstName>
               <DOB>07/06/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>N421</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P360</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/28/2023 01:06:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7007</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Fieldcrest </StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>2</SubNumber>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21215</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.708314</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.364318</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>531</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0472</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 03:04:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 03:04:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/28/2023 00:59:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>