<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-039009</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/05/2023 01:47:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/05/2023 01:47:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/05/2023 01:31:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/05/2023 01:31:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Accident, DUI, DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/05/2023 01:47:58</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 09:37:50</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>SANDY SPRING RD/ SWEITZER LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>591426</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/05/2023 01:47:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 02:40:19</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>591426</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Sandy Spring</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Laurel</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.89948</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.09879</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>6100-6196 SANDY SPRING RD / 0-0 SWEITZER LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>6100-6196 SANDY SPRING RD / 6300-6309 SWEITZER LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>6198-6198 SANDY SPRING RD / 6300-6309 SWEITZER LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/05/2023 01:47:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/05/2023 01:47:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/15/2023 22:16:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/05/2023 01:47:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Patrol Vehicle Q-34 is equipped with an in-car camera. Incident was captured on in-car and body worn camera. (Times may be affected by Day Light Savings Time)   Crime: Driving Under the Influence Defendant(s): Catryna Marie Lewis DOB:03/15/1990  Ian Dakota Bledsoe DOB: 07/20/1992 Date of Arrest: 11/05/2023 DUI #: 23-269, 23-270 Accident Involved: YES  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:  * I am trained to administer standardized field sobriety tests. (Eastern Shore Criminal Justice Academy 2019, National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, Maryland State Police Academy 2023) * I am trained to administer the Preliminary Breath Test. (Eastern Shore Criminal Justice Academy 2019, Maryland State Police Academy 2023) * I am a trained RADAR/LIDAR operator (Snow Hill Police Department, Worcester County Sheriffs Office 2019, Maryland State Police 2023) * I am trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (Maryland State Police, A.R.I.D.E., 2023)  NARRATIVE:  Phase #1 - Vehicle In Motion:   On November 05, 2023 at approximately 0131 hours I, Trooper Crystal Merritt #7665, of the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack was dispatched to the area of Eastbound Sandy Spring Road (RT198) at Sweitzer Lane in reference to a serious motor vehicle collision. I was operating Maryland State Police Marked Ford Explorer Q-34. Upon arrival to the area I observed a black Honda Civic (Vehicle 1), bearing Maryland registration 5EE1230, up against the center concrete median in lane one, with heavy front end damage. I was advised by passer-bys on scene that the second vehicle (Vehicle 2) involved was off of the right shoulder and into the wooded area.   Phase #2 - Personal Contact    Upon approach to vehicle one, I observed the operator, later identified as Catryna Marie Lewis [hereinafter identified as Lewis] still seated in the divers seat of the Honda, placing her in mechanical control of the vehicle. I observed Lewis to be suffering from serious injuries sustained as a result of the motor vehicle collision. I observed Lewis to appear visually agitated and screaming, while punching the steering wheel. While maintaining an approximate five foot distance from the vehicle I could detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. Prince Georges County Emergency Medical Personnel were on scene and attempting to provide medical aid to Lewis. Lewis was uncooperative with the Emergency Personnel on scene and initially was refusing to exit the vehicle or receive medical treatment. Due to the extent of her injuries, Emergency Personnel had to assist Lewis from the vehicle by pulling her out. After Lewis being removed from the vehicle she continued to be disorderly with Emergency Personnel and stated that she did not want to go to the hospital. I observed an empty case of White claw (alcoholic beverage(s)) that had fallen out of the vehicle. I observed (one) open canned Margarita (alcoholic beverage) open in the drivers door pocket. I observed (two) Patrone (alcoholic beverage(s)) open, and still containing alcohol in the passenger floor.   Upon approach to vehicle two, I observed a blue Nissan Altima, bearing Maryland registration 9FA8459 off of the roadway to the right, with rear and front end damage. Upon making contact with the operator, later identified as Ian Dakota Bledsoe [hereinafter identified as Bledsoe] still seated in the drivers seat placing him in mechanical control of the vehicle. Bledsoe was slumped over, leaning out of the drivers seat, almost falling out of the car. Bledsoe was advised that he was being audibly and visibly recorded. Bledsoe stated that he was driving and observed a vehicle approaching at a high rate of speed from behind him. Bledsoe stated he changed lanes in attempts to get out of the way and the vehicle rear-ended him, causing him to lose control of his vehicle. While speaking with Bledsoe I could detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his vehicle. When asked if he had anything to drink, Bledsoe stated that the odor must have come from alcohol being spilt on him during the collision. During my contact with Bledsoe, I observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot, his speech to be slurred, and his movements to be slow and lethargic. I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from Bledsoes breath and person.   I made contact with Lewis in the back of Ambulance 812. Lewis two Aunts were also present. I advised Lewis that she was being audibly and visibly recorded. Upon entrance to the ambulance I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage present in the ambulance. When asked, Lewis stated that she did not know what happened. When asked what she had to drink, Lewis stated that she had nothing to drink. At this point Lewis became uncooperative. When asked what her phone number was, Lewis stated 911.While speaking with Lewis I could detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emmiting from her breath and person. Lewis asked me who I was approximately three times after being advised initially. During our conversation, I observed Lewis eyes to be glassy and bloodshot, her speech to be slurred and her movements to be exaggerated. On numerus occasions, Lewiss Aunts apologized for her behavior and stated that she was drunk. Lewis Aunt stated that they were all drinking at Lewis house and that they told Lewis to stay home and not drive. Lewis was transported to Johns Hopkins Suburban Hospital (EMS# 2311050026).  Bledsoe initially refused medical transport. When advised of my intention to run Bledsoe through SFSTs, Bledsoe requested an Ambulance respond back to the scene and transport him to the hospital. Bledsoe was transported to Laurel Regional Medical Center (EMS# 2311040026).  Both vehicles were removed by Hoffmans towing.   Phase #3 - Pre Arrest Screening  N/A   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus  N/A    Walk and Turn   N/A   One Leg Stand  N/A  Preliminary Breath Test  Not offered    Arrest and Transport  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Lewis was driving a motor vehicle under the influence: *Condition of motor vehicle and operator upon my arrival *Eyes glassy and bloodshot *The presence of open alcoholic beverage(s) *Odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from her vehicle *Odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from her breath and person * Lewis family members statements that they were all drinking together    I responded to Johns Hopkins Suburban Hospital at 0320 hours. Lewis was found to be medically intubated and unconscious due to her injuries sustained in the accident. Upon arrival to the Emergency Room, there was an odor of an alcoholic beverage present, Lewis was the sole patient occupying the room. Due to Lewis condition, implied consent was expressed. RN Jonathan Spires of Johns Hopkins Suburban Hospital executed the blood draw, utilizing blood kit Q-379, in my presence at 0510 hours. Lewis was left with copies of pertinent paperwork.   Based on the following, I had reason to believe Bledsoe was driving a motor vehicle under the influence: *Condition of motor vehicle and operator upon my arrival *Eyes glassy and bloodshot *The admittance of the presence of open alcoholic beverage(s) in the vehicle *Odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his vehicle *Odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his breath and person   I was assisted by Trooper K. Woodworth #7681, Tpr. Woodworth responded to Laurel Medical center to meet with Bledsoe. Bledsoe was played and provided a copy of the DR15 and agreed to the blood draw at 0235 hours. RN Tania Blake of Laurel Regional Medical Center executed the blood draw, utilizing blood kit Q-378, in Tpr. Woodworths presence at 0312 hours. Bledsoe was left with copies of pertinent paperwork.  All events did occur in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 10:02:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 21:53:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>2</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> On December 2, 2023 the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack received the completed results of the blood-kit completed on Bledsoe, resulting in a .21 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of blood.  On December 12, 2023, at approximately 1120 hours I, Trooper C. Merritt #7665, of the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, met with Ian D. Bledsoe at the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack located at 10100 Rhode Island Avenue College Park, Maryland 20740. Bledsoe was served with his copy of the blood kit results. Bledsoe was issued his appropriate copies of all paperwork, and was issued citations. Bledsoes Maryland Drivers License was seized.  All events did occur in Prince Georges County Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 13:55:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 21:57:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Merritt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Crystal</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7665</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Merritt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Crystal</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7665</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Merritt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Crystal</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7665</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528475</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/05/2023 01:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:52:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 13:53:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528475</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/05/2023 01:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:52:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 13:53:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528475</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/05/2023 01:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:52:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 13:53:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528475</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/05/2023 01:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:52:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 13:53:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528475</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/05/2023 01:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:52:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 13:53:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528475</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/05/2023 01:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:52:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 13:53:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:52:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/09/2023 09:59:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392322</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lewis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Catryna</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/15/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 01:55:22</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C365</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lewis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Catryna</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/15/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C365</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 01:55:22</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>14117</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pear Tree</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>42</SubNumber>
               <City>Aspen Hill</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20906</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.069172</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.089274</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:59:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/09/2023 09:59:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:59:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/09/2023 09:59:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:53:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/09/2023 09:58:40</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392326</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bledsoe</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dakota</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/20/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 02:21:43</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B432</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bledsoe</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dakota</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/20/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B432</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 02:21:43</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5842</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Wyndham</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Columbia</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21044</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.869884</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.211663</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:58:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/09/2023 09:58:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 09:58:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/09/2023 09:58:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 13:52:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 13:52:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158728</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 10:01:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/09/2023 10:01:23</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1hgcr2f55fa078294</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CIV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5EE1230</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158729</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7665</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 10:01:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7665</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/09/2023 10:01:49</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1N4BL4BV4LC234425</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9FA8459</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/24/2023 18:22:04</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/24/2023 18:22:04</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/15/2023 22:16:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/24/2023 18:22:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 11/05/2023, at approximately 0207 hours, I responded to Laurel Regional Medical Center to make contact with Ian Dakota Bledsoe (1/M DOB: 07/20/1992), who was involved in a motor vehicle collision. Bledsoe was arrested for driving under the influence by Trooper Merritt #7665 at 0222 hours based on her observations at the scene of the collision.  Upon arrival at the hospital, I made contact with Bledsoe in his hospital room and identified him by his Maryland Drivers License. At approximately 0227 hours I began playing the English Audio version DR 15 Advise of Rights from the Maryland Motor Vehicle Association website and provided Bledsoe with a paper copy to read along with. At approximately 0235 hours, Bledsoe signed the DR-15 Advise of Rights, consenting to the evidentiary blood draw. At approximately 0312 hours, I witnessed Tania Blake, RN, use blood kit #Q-378 for the evidentiary blood draw. I processed and packaged the blood kit per Maryland State Police policies and procedures and the blood kit was sent to the Maryland State Police Chemical Testing for Alcohol Unit via United States Postal Service mail.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/24/2023 18:23:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7681</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 13:52:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Woodworth</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kory</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7681</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>