<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-004238</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/03/2023 00:52:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/03/2023 00:52:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/03/2023 00:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/03/2023 00:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/Single Vehicle Collision/2nd deg assault (no injuries/not witnessed) DUI Q-23-025</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 00:52:19</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 01:22:36</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>682980</AddressId>
      <City>MDC182</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 19:15:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 19:25:52</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>682980</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>I-95</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.88818</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.10277</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/03/2023 00:52:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/03/2023 00:52:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/21/2023 21:00:42</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 00:52:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 01:22:36</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The incident was captured on body worn camera. MSP marked vehicle Q-29 is not equipped with a mobile recording device.   DEFENDANT:  Dameion Lamar Woodard Date of Birth: 12/29/1977 MD DL#: W-363-135-488-993 Date of Arrest: 02/03/2023 Time of Arrest: 0219 hours (2:19 AM) DUI #: 23-025 (College Park Barrack)   TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:  * I am trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA). * I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor. * I am a Preliminary Breath Test Instructor. * I am a certified EC/IR II Intoximeter operator. * I am trained and certified RADAR/LIDAR operator through Baltimore County Police. * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training. *I have successfully completed and graduated with distinction from the 15th session of the University of Marylands Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies (DUI Institute). * I have apprehended more than 350 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.   NARRATIVE:  On February 3, 2023 at approximately 0029 hours, I, Cpl. McGee #6675 and Tpr. Gonzales #7442 of the Maryland State College Park Barrack were dispatched to a single vehicle collision on N/B I-95 in the area of MD-198, Prince Georges County, MD. While being dispatched to the call, we were advised over the radio that the driver of the vehicle involved in the collision was being subdued by witnesses.  Upon my arrival, I observed EMS and witnesses on scene. A blue Nissan Maxima was observed with the rear of the vehicle resting along the guardrail on the right shoulder with the vehicle perpendicular to the travel lanes with heavy frontend damage. The weather at the time was clear nd the road surface was dry. It was later determined that the Nissan was a rental bearing NY registration KUW6763. The driver of the Nissan was observed detained while seated on the ground along the drivers side rear of the vehicle next to the guardrail. The driver, Dameion Lamar Woodard, was later positively identified by his Maryland drivers license. Woodard was handcuffed by off-duty Officer Alexander Warren #2852 of Metropolitan Police Department 4th District after an alleged assault occurred. Alexander Warren and two other witnesses, Roy Simmons and Mary Cameron, stated they were attempting to provide aid to the passenger, David Woodard (father of Dameion Woodard), when they were assaulted by the driver Dameion Woodard. Tpr. Gonzales was advised to gather witness statements and anything related to the alleged assault.  I approached the driver, Dameion Woodard, and asked if he was injured. He advised that he was. I then identified myself and advised him that he was being audibly and visually recorded. Woodard stated that his father told him that he had to turn to get off the Interstate, he banged a right, and that is when the collision occurred. While speaking with Woodard, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. His speech was observed to be thick, slurred, and he mumbled at times. I advised Woodard that I was going to help him up and let EMS check him out. While Woodard was standing, he appeared off balance and at one point stumbled back into me. Woodard was seated on the stretcher and I removed the cuffs. Woodard was very agitated and was complaining that the witnesses rubbed his face in the dirt. EMS eventually moved Woodard into the back of the ambulance at which time I checked on the front passenger (David Woodard). David Woodard was intoxicated and stated, Right now Im drunk. I observed an empty bottle of Paul Masson Brandy on the front passenger floor (see photo). An empty can of Steel Reserve was located in the front drivers side by Tpr. Gonzales (see photo). David Woodard was taken into the care of EMS and transported to Howard Medical Center. Dameion Woodard was transported by Medic #841 to UMD Shock Trauma. I followed the medic unit to the hospital to gather more information about what occurred. Tpr. Gonzales remained on scene and continued to gather information from the witnesses.  Upon arrival at the hospital, medical staff began to evaluate Dameion Woodard. When given the opportunity after their initial evaluation, I began discussing with Woodard what occurred. He again stated that his father told him to turn and then the collision occurred. Woodard stated he was not sure what he hit. I asked Woodard where he was coming from and where he was headed. He stated that he dropped his coworker off in DC and was going back to Baltimore. Dameion Woodard confirmed on several occasions that he was driving when the collision occurred. Woodard advised after the collision that witnesses approached, one being the off-duty police officer. Woodard stated that the off-duty officer identified himself as a police officer. Woodard stated that he was pulled out of his car. I asked Woodard how many alcoholic beverages he drank earlier. He advised that he had two (2) Heinekens at 2:45 PM. He advised he had the drinks at his fathers house and his last drink when he got to DC.   ARREST:  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Woodard was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  - Single vehicle collision into the guardrail. - Taking a right to exit the highway where no exit was. - Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. - Glassy and bloodshot eyes. - Thick, slurred, and mumbled speech. - Stumbled back. - Empty alcoholic beverage can and bottle in vehicle. - Admitting to consuming alcoholic beverages.  Due to the number of observations, I concluded Woodard was driving under the influence and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0219 hours (2:19 AM), Woodard was deemed to be under arrest for Driving While Under the Influence of Alcohol.The DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to Woodard utilizing the MVA website recording. Woodard was provided with the DR-15 to read over. At 0243 hours (2:43 AM), Woodard consented to take the blood test to measure his blood alcohol concentration. He advised that he was unable to sign the DR-15.  Woodards blood was drawn at 0341 hours (3:41 AM) by an on duty registered nurse, Norma Filleti, employed by UMD Shock Trauma, using Blood Test Kit #R-835. Woodard was unable to sign the Consent (to draw blood) Form provided in the blood kit. I witnessed the Blood Test Kit being administered. The Blood Test Kit was then packaged, sealed, and mailed per Maryland State Police policy for further analysis.  Woodard was provided with his copy of the DR-15 and was released to the care of UMD Shock Trauma staff. Woodard was polite and cooperative with me throughout the incident.  At this time, I request the case remain open pending Blood Test results and issuance of traffic related charges. All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 00:55:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6675</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 20:53:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Long</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5477</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493621</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/03/2023 00:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 19:15:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6675</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 19:34:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493621</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>08</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/03/2023 00:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 19:30:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6675</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 19:34:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493621</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>08</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/03/2023 00:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 19:32:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6675</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 19:34:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 19:15:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368102</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Woodard</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dameion</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lamar</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/29/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/04/2023 07:25:52</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W363</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D550</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Woodard</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dameion</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lamar</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/29/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W363</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D550</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/04/2023 07:25:52</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>488</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2999</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 19:38:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 19:38:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 19:30:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6675</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 19:30:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150021</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 19:51:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6675</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 19:51:18</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1N4AA6CVXNC504448</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MAX</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLU</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>NY</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>KUW6763</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/04/2023 00:55:41</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/04/2023 00:55:41</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/21/2023 21:00:42</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 00:55:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 01:22:36</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On February 3, 2023, at approximately 0029 hours I, Trooper Gonzales #7442 of the Maryland State Police operating marked Maryland State Police cruiser Q-23 was responding to a call for service for a vehicle collision. I responded to the area of northbound I-95 past MD-198 and observed a blue Nissan Maxima bearing New York registration KUW6763. The Nissan was facing southwest and in the right shoulder of northbound I-95 past MD-198. I observed fire board and several bystanders by the right shoulder. I also observed an African-American male subsequently identified as Dameion Lamar Woodard (B/M DOB: 12/29/1977) through his MD SDX (W-363-135-488-993) seated and handcuffed against the guardrail on the right shoulder. Woodard was handcuffed by Alexander Taylor Warren, an off-duty Metropolitan Police Department 4th District officer #2852, who was on scene initially to render aid to the occupants of the Nissan after it was involved in a single vehicle collision. Warren identified himself as a police officer when he first arrived at scene. Roy Junior Simmons (AL SDX: 7120048) and Mary Jaylor Cameron (AL SDX - 8246262) were also on scene as bystanders to render aid to the occupants of the Nissan. I spoke with all bystanders to understand what transpired as Warren stated that when he and Simmons approached the car to render aid when Woodard exited the Nissan and physically prevented Woodard and Simmons from aiding the passenger of the Nissan. The passenger of the Nissan was subsequently identified as David Lorenza Woodard, Dameion Woodards father, (B/M DOB: 08/171955) through his MD SDX (W-363-135-546-643). Warren, Simmons, and Cameron all stated they heard Woodard Sr. yell out that hes been hit three times in the mouth by Woodard Jr. As Warren and Simmons attempted to help Woodard Sr. out the car, Woodard Jr became more agitated and physically struck Warren and Simmons. Woodard Jr. attempted to push Warren and Simmons into the roadway in an effort to prevent them from aiding Woodard Sr. All bystanders stated they heard Woodard Jr. scream out fuck my father! He can die! prior to Woodard Jr physically assaulting Warren and Simmons. Warren and Simmons were able to restrain Woodard Jr prior to my arrival on scene. Fire board was able to treat both Woodward Sr. and Jr. and both were transported to Howard Medical Center and UMD Shock Trauma respectively. I remained on scene to call for a tow for the Nissan and to collect witness statements from all bystanders present.  On February 3, 2023, at approximately 2354 hours I contacted Simmons and Cameron via telephone (256-371-3005) and spoke to them regarding pressing charges for 2nd degree assault and their rights as victims. Simmons and Cameron declined to press charges being that they are currently in Oregon and would have difficulties in returning to Maryland to see the Prince Georges County Commissioner to press charges. I emailed them the appropriate information such as the MD Crime Victims and Witnesses pamphlet and case number as well.  On February 4, 2023, at approximately 0008 hours I contact Warren via telephone (256-613-6617) and spoke to him regarding pressing charges for 2nd degree assault and his rights as a victim. Warren wished to pressed charges and will return to Maryland to see a Prince Georges County Commissioner to do so. I emailed Warren the appropriate information such as the MD Crime Victims and Witnesses pamphlet and case number as well.  On February 4, 2023, at approximately 0025 hours I contacted Woodard Jr. via telephone (443-488-2999) to provide him the same information as I did with the others but no contact was made.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 00:57:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7442</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 02:18:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gonzales</LastName>
            <FirstName>Javier</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7442</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Long</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5477</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gonzales</LastName>
            <FirstName>Javier</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7442</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/05/2023 17:23:02</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/05/2023 17:23:02</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/07/2023 12:43:16</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5657</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 17:23:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 01:22:36</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Blood Kit Results have returned, 0.19.  Results have been forwarded to Cpl McGee #6675 to be served to the defendant.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5657</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 17:24:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/05/2023 17:25:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heath</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4437</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Parsons</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5657</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/05/2023 00:27:13</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/05/2023 00:27:13</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/12/2023 01:22:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/05/2023 00:27:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 01:22:36</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 5/4/2023 at 2345 hours, I, Cpl. McGee #6675 served the defendant, Dameion Lamar Woodard, with his blood test results at 3705 Woodridge Rd, Baltimore, MD 21229. The test results indicated that Woodard had a blood alcohol concentration of 0.19 grams of alcohol per 100 milliliters of blood. A DR-15A was completed while on scene. Woodard was issued all appropriate citations and received copies of all pertinent paperwork.  I request this case be closed. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6675</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/05/2023 00:33:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6675</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/05/2023 00:38:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heath</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4437</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>