<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013480</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/16/2023 03:33:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/16/2023 03:33:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/16/2023 03:14:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/16/2023 03:14:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>A vehicle was stopped for speeding, further investigation found the driver to Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 03:33:48</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5162</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 10:48:19</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>562274</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 03:33:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/16/2023 05:05:08</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>562274</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Solomons Island</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Prince Frederick</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20678</Zip5>
         <Zip4>2067</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.537507</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.499871</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/16/2023 03:33:45</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/16/2023 03:33:45</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/28/2023 09:17:54</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 03:33:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:40</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This stop was audibly and visually recorded using the Axon Digital Video Camera System installed in Maryland State Police Vehicle U-13.    Defendant: Nasja Christine Onye Green Date of Birth: 07/30/2002 Date of Arrest: 04/16/2023 Time of Arrest: 0332 hours DUI #: 23-034   CERTIFICATION  TRAINING  * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)   On April 16, 2023, at approximately 0314 hours, I, TFC A. Smith of the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick Barrack, was on road patrol in the area of northbound Solomons Island Road and Old Field Lane, Prince Frederick, Calvert County, Maryland. While on patrol, I observed a silver Honda Accord traveling southbound in lane 1 at 67 miles per hour in a posted 45 mile per hour zone utilizing RADAR installed in marked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle U-13 serial number 50008262. After observing the vehicle, I made a u-turn at Old Field Lane, caught up to the Honda, and observed the vehicle traveling at 76 miles per hour in a posted 55 mile per hour zone utilizing the front RADAR in U-13. At this time, I positioned myself behind the vehicle and activated my emergency equipment to conduct a traffic stop.   PERSONAL CONTACT   I made contact with Nasja Christine Onye Green (B/F DOB: 07/30/2000), identified by her name and date of birth, who was seated in the driver seat of the vehicle. I introduced myself and advised her the reason for the traffic stop. Immediately after advising her the reason for the stop and asked Green for her license and registration. While speaking with her I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her inside the vehicle. Green advised she did not have her license in her possession and provided her registration and proof of insurance. Greens identity was confirmed via MVA photograph. I asked Green where she was coming from, she stated from a birthday party at her friends house in Prince Frederick. I asked Green how many alcoholic beverages she consumed prior to driving, she advised one. I asked Green to exit her vehicle and to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Test. Green agreed and exited the vehicle.    PRE-ARREST SCREENING  Green was asked the following before beginning: Injuries/Physical limiters  None. Medical Conditions  None Glasses/ Contacts  None  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS 6/6 CLUES OBSERVED   The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The lighted tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12-15 inches from Greens eyes. Green was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Greens pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Green was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results.   Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes  Onset Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes   WALK AND TURN 6/8 CLUES OBSERVED   Prior to Green performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Green was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary line. Green was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Green was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Green was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Green was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to the left to turn completely around. Green was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Green was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Green if she understood the test and she advised she did.  Instructional Stage:    Broke instructional position twotimes.   Began the test before being instructed to, once.   Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Missed heel-to-toe on steps 3, 5, and 8.  Stepped off line on step 6.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Incorrect number of steps. Total taken 7.  Stopped walking on step 6.  Turn:  Nothing to report.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):     margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Missed heel-to-toe on step 3.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Stepped off line on step 3.    ONE LEG STAND (2/4) Prior to Green performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. I instructed Green to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Green was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she advised she did. Green raised her left leg.  Seconds 0-10:  Nothing to report  Seconds 11-20: Nothing to report.  Seconds 21-30:    Swayed on second 28.  Put foot down on second 28.    PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST Green was offered to take a Preliminary Breath Test and agreed. Results: 0.13 BRaC.  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Green was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: *Observed traffic violation, speeding 76mph in a posted 55mph zone.  *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath. *My observed signs of impairment as Green performed field sobriety tests. *Admitting to consuming alcohol prior to driving. *Glassy eyes. *Slurred speech. *Bloodshot eyes.  Due to the number of observations, I concluded Green was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. Green was placed under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at 0332 hours.   20 Minute Observation   For the 20-minute observation period, I did not observe Green regurgitate, vomit, or put anything in his mouth. Green was read the DR-15 Advice of Rights and given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights in English to read and follow along with. Green refused to submit to a chemical breath test at 0357 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  Intoximeter results: Refused.  Green was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to her grandmother.  All events occurred in Calvert County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6945</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 05:46:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6945</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 09:55:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Newman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3029</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6945</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502887</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 03:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6945</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 05:05:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6945</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/16/2023 05:05:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>20</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6945</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 05:10:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374429</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Green</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nasja</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christine Onye</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/30/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.12655302E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/16/2023 05:09:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G650</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Green</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nasja</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christine Onye</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/30/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.12655302E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>G650</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/16/2023 05:09:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>331</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Clubhouse</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lusby</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20657</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.421002</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.343392</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>404</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8615</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6945</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 05:10:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6945</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 05:10:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6945</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 05:10:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6945</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 05:05:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6945</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/16/2023 05:05:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152018</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6945</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 05:14:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6945</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/16/2023 05:14:12</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1HGCR2F33HA185118</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ACCORD</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4FG5509</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>