<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020211</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/06/2023 00:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/06/2023 00:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/05/2023 23:53:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/05/2023 23:53:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Single Vehicle Reconstruction</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 00:08:22</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3321</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 13:40:05</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>PHILADELPHIA RD/ MOUNTAIN RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>61257</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 00:08:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 21:15:14</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>61257</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Mountain</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Joppa</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21085</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.34472</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.43824</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 MOUNTAIN RD / 900-910 PHILADELPHIA RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 MOUNTAIN RD / 0-0 PHILADELPHIA RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 MOUNTAIN RD / 1000-1012 PHILADELPHIA RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/06/2023 00:08:19</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/06/2023 00:08:19</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>06/07/2023 02:03:43</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 00:08:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3321</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 13:39:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>**************ACRS IN DELTA PLUS************** </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7283</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/07/2023 01:41:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7283</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/07/2023 01:50:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whittenberg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6095</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>O'Donald</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jesse</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7284</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sander</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5948</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Neal</LastName>
            <FirstName>Emily</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7283</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/09/2023 08:45:21</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/09/2023 08:45:21</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/15/2023 13:39:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 08:45:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3321</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 13:39:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Detailed Crash Investigation Report  (For review by the MSPCrash Team)       Section I. - Introduction: On June 05, 2023, at approximately 2353 hours, Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack Troopers responded to an overturned single vehicle collision with suspected serious life-threatening fatal injuries. The collision occurred on Philadelphia Road (MD Route 7) and Joppa Forest Drive, in Joppatowne, Harford County, Maryland.  I, TFC Pepe #7054 of the Maryland State Police North East Barrack, responded to the scene with TFC Mott #7053 as the Advanced Collision Investigators (ACI).  The collision involved a 1984 SAAB hatchback, operated by Thomas C. Thurlow of Edgewood, Maryland. The SAAB was traveling westbound on Philadelphia Road prior to Joppa Forest Drive at a high rate of speed when it lost control, and began to drive off the road. The Porsche struck a raised curb at the intersection of Joppa Forest Drive, and began to go airborne. The SAAB then struck multiple marked roadway signs and a white plastic fence. The SAAB then entered a retention basin and began to overturn. The SAAB continued overturning until striking multiple trees. Thurlowwas ejected and ultimately entrapped underneath the SAAB when it came to rest.  As a result of the collision, it was determined that Thomas Thurlow sustained serious injuries, at which time Joppa Fire/EMS responded and attempted life-saving measures to remove Thurlow from under the vehicle. At the same time, MSP-Trooper 1 Aviation responded for transport to Shock Trauma Center, Baltimore City Maryland. Due to arriving on scene after Thurlow was transported, Joppa Fire/EMS advised me that Thurlow had suffered serious facial injuries as well as low extremities being severely damaged.   Section II. - Scene Description: (The following descriptions are based on the area where the collision occurred.)  Primary Roadway:MarylandRoute 7 (Philadelphia Road) Maryland Route 7 was a State of Maryland maintained roadway that consisted of two total lanes; one lane east and one lane west. The east and west lanes were divided by a solid double-yellow paint line. The right edge of the roadway was marked with a single solid white fog line. The right edge of each shoulder was lined with grass and dirt. The collision occurred on the curved section of Philadelphia Road intersecting with Joppa Forest Drive.  The posted speed limit on Maryland Route 7 was 40 miles per hour. The asphalt road surface at the time of the collision was on a flat level surface that was dry, contained no defects, and was free from debris and or foreign objects.  Environmental Conditions: The only ample lighting was produced by streetlights that were at the intersection of Joppa Forest Drive, as well as a business being fully illuminated nearby the scene of the collision. The weather was clear, calm, humid and with a temperature of approximately 70 degrees Farenheit.  Section III. - Scene Evidence: Approaching the scene from the west and working east, a dark-colored 1984 SAAB hatchback was located off of the roadway in the wood line on its drivers side. There was numerous debris scattered across the roadway and continuing off the westbound shoulder, and in the water retention basin. Several pieces of vehicle plastic, metal, glass and liquid were located spilled in the water retention basin, woodline and nearby the overturned vehicle. There were multiple tire track marks, as well as impact points, leading to the final resting position of the SAAB.  There was visible damage to the white fence that belonged to Forest View condominiums, as well as damage to the raised curb where the vehicle had struck initially. The wooden post that held the state marked sign for overweight vehicle warnings was completely destroyed, being removed from the dirt/grass it was posted in before the collision.  Several articles of clothing, such as boots, a hat, and other personal belongings were scattered throughout the entire scene. Digital photographs were taken of the scene and roadway evidence, and the vehicles final rest was marked with orange florescent spray paint.  Section IV. - Vehicle(s) Involved:  Vehicle #1: 1984 SAAB Hatchback Registration: JUT780 (Alaska) VIN: YS3AT35L1F1001962 Owner: Thomas C. Thurlow Opertaor: Thomas C. Thurlow Address: 908 Hawthorne Road, Edgewood Maryland 21040  Examination: The SAAB Hatchback was examined at its final resting position stationary on its drivers side off of the westbound shoulder in the wood line of Maryland Route 7. There was significant damage to the entire front of the vehicle to include bumper, hood, grill, frame, and fenders. The front axle, to include the wheel wells were completely crushed and turned outward, consistent with striking the raised curb. All the windows of the vehicle were shattered out. The front windshield was still intact but completed shattered.  Section V. - Person(s) Involved:  Person #1: Name: Thomas C. Thurlow Date of Birth: 12/12/1986 OLN: T640792108944 (Maryland)  Witness #1: Name: Aiden McIntosh Date of Birth: 09/04/2002 Phone: 202-820-1248  Synopsis: McIntosh stated, I saw a car come around the bend and smash through the fence and fly into the woods. The car flipped multiple times. I immediately called 9/11 and walked over.  Section VI. - Follow-up Investigation:  Date: June 07, 2023 I, TFC Pepe of the North East Barrack contacted Shock Trauma Center, Baltimore City for an update to Thurlow. Which they advised he was still in the ICU prepping for multiple surgeries.  Date:June 07, 2023 I, TFC Pepe of the North East Barrack responded to Best Friends Fur Ever located at 1009 Philadelphia Road, Joppatowne Maryland 21085 to obtain video surveillance of the collision. I obtained video surveillance from the night of the collision which was obtained and stored on a 2GB hard drive.  Date:June 08, 2023 I, TFC Pepe of the North East Barrack contacted Baltimore Shock Trauma Center, Baltimore City to conduct a follow-up for Thurlow who was injured in the collision. Staff advised that Thurlow had made it through surgery and would be recovering in the ICU department due to the injuries sustained.  Date: August 11, 2023 I, TFC Pepeof the North East Barrack contacted Baltimore Shock Trauma Center, Baltimore City to conduct a follow-up for Thurlow who was injured in the collision.Staff advised that Thurlow was released from hospital care on June 23, 2023. Section VII. - Analysis of Electronic Control Modules: None at this time.  Section VIII. - Speed Analysis: No speed analysis completed   Section IX. - Crash Dynamics: The SAAB operated by Thomas Thurlow was traveling westbound on Maryland Route 7 in the area of Joppa Forest Drive, at a high rate of speed. The vehicle struck a raised curb, struck a marked sign and left the roadway into a water retention basin. The vehicle then began to overturn striking the grass embankment multiple times through the duration of the collision. Tire tracking marks as well as vehicle impact points were located on the grassy shoulder, and retention basin along the westbound shoulder. The vehicle then struck shrubbery and trees, and continued to overturn, until finally striking a large tree coming to a complete stop.  Thurlow, who was not wearing his seat belt, and was ejected out of the vehicle, and he would be thrown underneath the vehicle. The vehicle would ultimately come to a rest where it would come to rest on Thurlows lower extremities causing him to become entrapped until Fire/EMS could provide life-saving measures to remove him from underneath the vehicle.   Section X. - Attachments that were included in for this report:  The following items were attached to this report: 1. ACRS report  Conclusion: On Monday, June 5, 2023, at approximately 2353 hours Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack Troopers responded to an overturned single vehicle collision with suspected life-threatening injuries. The collision occurred on westbound Maryland Route 7 and Joppa Forest Drive, Joppatowne Maryland 21085. I, TFC Pepe #7054 of the North East Barrack, responded to the scene as the North East Barrack Advanced Collision Investigator (ACI). The collision involved a 1984 SAAB Hatchback style vehicle, operated by Thomas C. Thurlow of Edgewood, Maryland. The SAAB was traveling westbound on Philadelphia Road prior to Joppa Forest Drive at a high rate of speed when it lost control, and began to drive off the road. The SAAB struck a raised curb at the intersection of Joppa Forest Drive, and began to go airborne. The SAAB then struck multiple marked roadway signs and a white plastic fence. The SAAB then entered a retention basin and began to overturn. The SAAB continued overturning until striking multiple trees, ejecting Thurlow. The SAAB then landed on Thurlow entrapping him under the vehicle.  As a result of the collision, it was determined that Thomas Thurlow sustained serious/life-threatening injuries and was transported by Joppa Fire/EMS to their helicopter pad nearby, where Thurlow would be transported by MSP- Trooper 1 to the Shock Trauma Center in Baltimore City, Maryland.  These collision events were a result of Thomas Thurlow failed to obey a traffic control device, and failing to control his vehicle to avoid a collision.  Due to Thurlow ultimately not suffering any life-altering injuries I request this case be closed via ACRS and charges will be referred to the initial Trooper.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.  Trooper First Class Joseph A Pepe #7054 Advanced Collision Investigator Maryland Department of State Police North East Barrack F 2433 Pulaski Highway North East MD 21901 joseph.pepe@maryland.gov (410) 996-7800 (410) 996-7878 </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 21:21:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7054</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 11:01:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CT</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Menchey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3321</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pepe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7054</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509645</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>MSP1004</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 23:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 11:51:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7054</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/21/2023 11:51:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>36</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/11/2023 13:04:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/11/2023 13:04:25</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384895</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Thurlow</LastName>
               <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/12/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/11/2023 13:04:13</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Thurlow</LastName>
               <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/12/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/11/2023 13:04:13</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>908</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hawthorne</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Edgewood</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21040</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/11/2023 13:04:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>20</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 10:33:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 10:33:45</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385119</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>U</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mcintosh</LastName>
               <FirstName>Aiden</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/04/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/14/2023 10:33:32</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M253</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A350</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mcintosh</LastName>
               <FirstName>Aiden</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/04/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M253</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A350</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/14/2023 10:33:32</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3615</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Clayton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21085</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.337058</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.451103</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>820</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1248</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 10:33:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155884</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AC</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7054</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 10:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7054</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 10:49:45</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>YS3AT35L1F1001962</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>1984</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>SAA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>AK</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>JUT780</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>