<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025587</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/17/2023 19:46:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/17/2023 19:46:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/17/2023 19:46:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/17/2023 19:46:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Accident / DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 20:24:35</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/10/2023 13:44:27</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I97 / CRAIN HWY S</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>588598</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 20:24:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 12:09:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>588598</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I97</StreetName>
         <City>Glen Burnie</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>HWY</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <CrossStreetSuffixCode>S</CrossStreetSuffixCode>
         <Longitude>-76.64122</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.12805</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11907-12000 I97 / 8076-8094 CRAIN HWY S</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11801-11900 I97 / 0-0 CRAIN HWY S</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11961-12200 I97 / 8050-8074 CRAIN HWY S</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11951-11960 I97 / 8050-8074 CRAIN HWY S</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11901-11906 I97 / 8096-8098 CRAIN HWY S</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11901-11906 I97 / 8076-8094 CRAIN HWY S</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/17/2023 20:24:31</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/17/2023 20:24:31</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/10/2023 13:44:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 20:24:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/10/2023 13:44:27</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI #: # P-23-089  CASE #: 23-MSP-025587  DEFENDANT: Stephanie Kay Gould (ID CARD MD G430777461523)  WITNESS/VICTIM: Jichelle Asha Jones (MD J520414072422)  *MOTOR VEHICLE COLLISION*  *THIS INCIDENT WAS RECORDED ON MY IN-CAR AND BODY WORN CAMERA SYSTEMS*  NARRATIVE:   On 07/17/2023, at approximately 1946 hours I, Senior Trooper Bartch #5301 responded to a two-vehicle accident on southbound I-97 @ New Cut Road in marked MSP patrol vehicle P-24. Upon my arrival, I observed two vehicles, one silver Toyota on the left shoulder and another silver Nissan off to the left shoulder in the grassy area. I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with both drivers to make sure no one was injuried. I first made contact withJichelle Asha Jones who was operating thesilver Toyota bearing Maryland registration 3EZ4255. She advised she was okay but was very concerned for the other driver that struck her. She advised she was going to leave due the fact they only bumped mirrors, but she was concerned for the other driver due to the fact the other driver seemed confused and possibly drunk. I then made contact with the driver of the second vehicle, which was identified by its Maryland registration bearing 8CL9877. Which at that time Anne Arundel County Officer and A.A. County EMS had made contact with her, and they advised she had refused any medical treatment.  Upon contact the driver seemed confused and her movements and speech were extremely slow. I asked if she was okay and if she had been drinking or under the influence of anything, and she stated no. I then asked for her drivers license. The driver was holding a pink zip up wallet which was open, and I could clearly see her license in one of the clear pockets of the pink wallet. The driver slowly looked through the pink wallet and finally gave me her debt card. I told the driver that she handed me her debt card and I asked her what would I need that for, and she stated In case I wanted to buy something. I then gave the debt card back and again asked for her license. Once again she was confused and could not see her ID card that was clearly in front of her in the pink wallet in a clear pocket which she was holding. She then reached over to the passenger seat and started to search through her purse for her ID. I then had to point and show her that her license was right in front of her inside the wallet she was holding. After a few moments she finally was able to take the ID out. She was identified by her Identification Card as Stephanie Kay Gould. I asked Gould to retrieve her insurance and registration card while I went to speak with the other driver.  I had Gould exit her vehicle and come to the front of my patrol vehicle. While she exit her vehicle and made her way over to the shoulder Gould had to grab a hold of her vehicle to keep from falling over. Once balanced she then took another step and again lost balance but was able to stay on her feet.   Based on my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, I suspected Gould was impaired by alcohol/CDS/ and or Medication and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. Gould agreed to submit to standardized field sobriety testing. The tests were performed on the left shoulder of southbound I-97 Prior to New Cut Road in an area that was level and free of debris and the weather was clear. Gould did advise me that she was on medications such as xanax but had no present injuries. Gould also confirmed that she could see my stimulus (pen) in front of her face.  STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS  Instructions: Gould was told to stand with her feet together and her arms down at her side. A stimulus (ink pen) was held approximately twelve to fifteen inches from Goulds face, and she was asked to follow the stimulus with her eyes only and to not move her head. Prior to beginning the test, I asked Gould if she understood the instructions. Gould answered yes. Gould had trouble following the pen and would several times close her eyes to where she would nod off. Several times I had to remind Gould to keep her eyes open and follow the pen with her eyes only. I was unable to determine if Gould had nystagmus or not due to the entire time she would not follow the pen and nob off by closing her eyes.  WALK AND TURN  Instructions: Gould was told to stand with her right foot in front of her left foot in a heel to toe manner. Gould was told to stay in that position and keep her arms at her side until being told to begin the test. I asked Gould if she understood, and she answered yes. I began explaining and demonstrating the test. Gould was instructed to take nine heel to toe steps in a straight line. On the ninth step, she was instructed to leave her lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn 180 degrees. Gould was told to then take an additional nine heel to toe steps back down the same straight line. She was told to gaze down at her feet, count the steps out loud, keep her hands at her side, touch heel to toe on every step, and to not stop walking until the test is complete. I asked Gould if she understood the instructions before beginning and Gould answered yes.  Results: 8/8. Narrative  Gould could not stay in the instructional phase. Gould could not keep balance and had to use her arms to balance. During entire phase of instructions Gould would nod off, and once she lost balance she would then open her eyes again. On the first series of nine heel to toe steps Gould took 11 steps. Gould attempted to complete the turn but turned the wrong way, and while doing so Gould lost balance and caused myself to almost grab her, so she wouldnt fall down, but she was able to keep standing. When she turned the wrong way her arms raised more than 12 inches to help her keep balance and helped her to not fall down. The second series of nine heel to toe steps after her first step she stepped off-line losing balance and stopped. Gould began again and on her 6 step she lost balance and stepped off-line. Gould finished the second series at 14 steps. During the entire test Gould did not perform heel to toe steps.  ONE LEG STAND  Instructions: Gould was instructed to stand with her feet together and her hands at her side while I explained the instructions and demonstrated the test. Gould was told to raise either foot of her choice approximately six inches off the ground while keeping it parallel to the ground. She was told to begin to count, one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-threeetc. Gould was instructed to continue counting until I told her to stop, she was told to gaze down at her feet, to count out loud, to keep her arms at her side, and to not put her foot down. I then asked if Gould understood the instructions. Gould answered yes. Results: 4/4. Narrative  O/L   During the entire time Gould could not keep balance. Gould was swaying back and forth and raised her arms more than 12 inches to try to keep balance. Gould dropped her foot on count 2. I advised her to count out loud. Gould then began counting from the beginning. Gould dropped her foot on count 4,6,14, and 15. Due to safety reasons I stopped the test. I did not want Gould to lose her balance and fall and hurt herself. Based on my observations and my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, Gould was placed under arrest for Driving Under the Influence at approximately 2014 hours. I secured Gould in my patrol vehicle and transported her to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie barrack for processing.     While transporting Gould back to the barrack, she asked what was wrong with her car, I told her that she was involved in an accident and I asked if she knew, she was in a car accident, and she stated no. I again told her she was involved in an accident, and she said no I was on Church Street hanging out. I asked her when was she at Church Street, and she stated on the day of the accident. I asked to confirm if it was this accident she was referring to, and she then began to nob off to sleep. During the entire ride to the barrack Gould was barely able to keep her eyes open and for most of the ride Goulds eyes were closed. I would ask Gould if she was okay, and she stated yes she was just tired.  We arrived at the barrack at approximately 2026 hours. I escorted Gould into the barracks DWI room, and she was provided a copy of her DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along as a audio version was read to her out loud in its entirety. I asked Gould if she understood the form, and she answered yes. At approximately 2044 hours, Gould consented to submit to the intoximeter test. Anne Arundel County Police Officer Cpl. Dean #2359 a certified intoximeter operator, administered the test. At 2107 hours .00 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath were collected. Gould was asked to submit to a DRE (drug recognition expert) and refused. Gould was issued the proper paperwork and citations.  DISPOSITION  At approximately 2200 hours, Gould was released to her mother. Gould ID Card was not confiscated.    All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 11:39:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 09:42:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Logsdon</LastName>
            <FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2064</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wiest</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4939</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bartch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5301</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515030</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/17/2023 20:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 11:41:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 11:41:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 12:01:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:16</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382830</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gould</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stephanie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kay</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/02/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 12:00:12</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gould</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stephanie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kay</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/02/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 12:00:12</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2807</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sudberry</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>bowie</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20715</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>924</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4024</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 21:23:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 21:23:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 21:23:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 21:23:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 11:41:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 11:41:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>