<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-001096</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/10/2023 01:42:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/10/2023 01:42:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/10/2023 01:10:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/10/2023 01:10:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>CR 5-601(A)(1) CDS: Not Marijuana</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 01:42:51</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/19/2023 10:10:30</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>WASHINGTON RD/ KATE WAGNER RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>602694</AddressId>
      <City>MDC249</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 01:42:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 03:46:23</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>602694</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Washington</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.994525</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.53761</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1323-1326 WASHINGTON RD / 64-67 KATE WAGNER RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1222-1314 WASHINGTON RD / 0-0 KATE WAGNER RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/10/2023 01:42:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/10/2023 01:42:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/12/2023 02:03:36</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 01:42:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:49</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-001096  Incident: CR 5-601(A)(1) CDS: Not Marijuana  Date/ Time: 01/10/2022, 0108 hours  Location of Offense: E/B Kate Wagner Rd at Gist Rd, Westminster, Carroll County, MD.  Incident recorded on AXON digital recording system assigned to G-39 and Body Worn Camera assigned to M/Tpr Fair.  Training  Qualifications:  -Maryland State Police Academy (June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007)  -I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through NHTSA and the Maryland State Police (MSP Academy, June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007).  -I am trained and certified to operate a Kustom Golden Eagle II, set # G-39. All records are kept on file at the MSP Electronic Services Division and Westminster Barrack, the unit was found to be in working order prior to and following the stop, and was used in accordance to MSP policy, my training, and the manufacturers guidelines. My training and certification for the RADAR unit are non-expiring.  -I have attended and graduated from the University of Maryland University College Advanced DUI College (UMUC January 7-11, 2013).  -Street Narcotics Investigation for Road Patrol (MPCTC, 05/22/2015)  -I have attended and completed training Enhanced DUI Enforcement: The Complete Arrest (MPCTC, 05/11/2016).  -A.R.I.D.E.: Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (MPCTC, 03/29-03/30/2017)  -Cannabis Impairment Detection Workshop (MPCTC, 09/29/2021)  Driver:  MD DL MD10273297680 BRANDON TAVON COLE ONEAL 6608 EBERLE DR, Apt 102 BALTIMORE, MD 21215 1/M, DOB 01/03/1986 443-400-9784  Scene Processing:  I conducted a detailed search of the vehicle, based on the odors of raw and burnt marijuana emanating from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I recognized the odors to be those of marijuana (a Controlled Dangerous Substance of Schedule 1) based on my training, knowledge, and experience with the Maryland State Police. The following items were located and seized:  A. two plastic baggies containing dried mushrooms, suspected CDS psilocybin mushrooms, 6.9 grams (including baggies) B. one box labeled to contain and containing one 10 milliliter syringe containing psilocybe cubernsis mushroom spores C. one clear plastic baggie containing green plant matter, suspected CDS marijuana, 6.5 grams (including baggie) D. one black container, labeled to contain cannabis/ THC, formerly containing item E E. green plant matter, suspected CDS marijuana, 1.8 grams F. two hand rolled cigarettes containing green plant matter, suspected CDS marijuana, 3.1 grams  Item A was located in the rear center seat cup holder/ armrest storage compartment. Item B was located in the vehicle glove box. Item C was located in the drivers door map pocket. Item D (containing item E) was located in the center console/ armrest storage compartment between the drivers seat and front passenger seat. Item F was located in the front passenger door: one cigarette in the removable ashtray in the front passenger door map pocket, and the other in the front passenger door inside handle.  I recognized the substances to be Controlled Dangerous Substances through my training and experience with the Maryland State Police. The items were seized, packaged and sealed, and captured on MSP Form 67 and 63 (P-323228), and placed in the MSP Westminster Barrack Evidence locker in accordance with MSP policy and procedure.  Neighborhood Check:  None completed due to the nature of the incident.  Narrative:  Reason for contact:  On 01/10/2023, at approximately 0108 hours, I was in uniform, on duty, operating a marked MSP Patrol vehicle: G-39. I was traveling W/B Kate Wagner Rd, W/O Gist Rd, Westminster, Carroll County, MD. I observed a vehicle traveling E/B Kate Wagner Rd, at what appeared to be above the posted speed limit of 40 mph. I executed a U-turn and was able to get behind the vehicle with the RADAR unit assigned to my vehicle activated in same direction moving mode (front antenna). The vehicle was the only vehicle in the field of influence, and the only other vehicle on the road at the time. The speed for the vehicle (which is described as a blue Chevy Malibu with Maryland temporary registration T1135680) captured on RADAR at 54 mph in the posted 40 mph zone on Kate Wagner Rd at Gist Rd, Westminster, Carroll County, MD. I initiated a traffic stop on the vehicle at Kate Wagner Rd at MD 32. The vehicle stopped on MD 32, immediately S/O Kate Wagner Rd, Westminster, Carroll County, MD. I was able to observe that the vehicle had two occupants: driver and front passenger. The weather was clear and approximately 32 degrees Fahrenheit.  Contact:  I made contact with the driver, identified myself, advised the stop was being recorded, and stated the reason for the stop. The driver provided the vehicles temporary registration card, as well as his Maryland drivers license. While speaking with the driver, I detected the strong odors of raw and burnt marijuana emanating from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I recognized the odors to be those of marijuana ( a Controlled Dangerous Substance of Schedule 1) based on my training, knowledge, and experience with the Maryland State Police. The driver was identified by his MD DL to be BRANDON TAVON COLE ONEAL, the registered owner of the vehicle.  I had the driver exit the vehicle to separate him from the odors emanating from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I continued to detect the odor of burnt marijuana about the drivers person and breath. The driver admitted to consuming (smoking) marijuana in the vehicle approximately 3 hours prior. The driver advised he is not in the Maryland Medical Cannabis program. I administered the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Based on my observations, I determined the driver was not currently impaired.  I conducted a detailed search of the vehicle, based on the odors of raw and burnt marijuana emanating from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I recognized the odors to be those of marijuana ( a Controlled Dangerous Substance of Schedule 1) based on my training, knowledge, and experience with the Maryland State Police. The driver also did admit that there was marijuana within the vehicle. The following items were located and seized:  A. two plastic baggies containing dried mushrooms, suspected CDS psilocybin mushrooms, 6.9 grams (including baggies) B. one box labeled to contain and containing one 10 milliliter syringe containing psilocybe cubernsis mushroom spores C. one clear plastic baggie containing green plant matter, suspected CDS marijuana, 6.5 grams (including baggie) D. one black container, labeled to contain cannabis/ THC, formerly containing item E E. green plant matter, suspected CDS marijuana, 1.8 grams F. two hand rolled cigarettes containing green plant matter, suspected CDS marijuana, 3.1 grams  Item A was located in the rear center seat cup holder/ armrest storage compartment. Item B was located in the vehicle glove box. Item C was located in the drivers door map pocket. Item D (containing item E) was located in the center console/ armrest storage compartment between the drivers seat and front passenger seat. Item F was located in the front passenger door: one cigarette in the removable ashtray in the front passenger door map pocket, and the other in the front passenger door inside handle.  I recognized the substances to be Controlled Dangerous Substances through my training and experience with the Maryland State Police. The items were seized, packaged and sealed, and captured on MSP Form 67 and 63 (P-323228), and placed in the MSP Westminster Barrack Evidence locker in accordance with MSP policy and procedure.  The driver was issued the traffic citation for the speed violation, the Notice to Appear, the Notice to Right of Counsel, and criminal citation for CR 5-601(A)(1) CDS: Not Marijuana. Per the agreement with the CCSAO, the driver was not charged with the marijuana violation. At all times the driver was polite and cooperative.  All events did occur in Carroll County, MD.  Case closed on criminal citation.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:44:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/11/2023 01:34:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490474</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/10/2023 01:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:47:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 03:47:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:52:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365720</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>O'NEAL</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRANDON</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>TAVON COLE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/03/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 03:51:44</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>O540</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>O'NEAL</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRANDON</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>TAVON COLE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/03/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>O540</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 03:51:44</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6608</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Eberle</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>102</SubNumber>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21215</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.709887</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.354252</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>400</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9784</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:56:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:56:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:56:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:47:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 03:47:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148467</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:56:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 03:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1G11A5SL7FF267995</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MAL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>T1135680</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:58:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 03:58:12</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>PSILOCYBIN MUSHROOMS</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>241172</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>K</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>6.9</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:59:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 03:59:54</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>GREEN PLANT MATTER (MARIJUANA) AND HANDROLLED MARIJUANA CIGARETTES</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>241173</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>11.4</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>