<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002930</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40P</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/24/2023 09:59:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/24/2023 09:59:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/24/2023 09:59:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/24/2023 09:59:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>PWID</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 09:59:45</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5467</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 09:46:48</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>2113 WEST FAIRMOUNT AVE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>681627</AddressId>
      <City>MDC103</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 09:59:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 08:56:07</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>681627</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2113</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Fairmount</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/24/2023 09:59:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/24/2023 09:59:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40P</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/13/2023 09:46:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 09:59:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:20:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Tuesday, January 24th, 2023, at approximately 0750 hours I, Trooper First Class (TFC) Chrzanowski #6836 of the Maryland State Police (MSP)-Delivery Systems Parcel Interdiction Initiative (DSPII) was working a drug interdiction assignment at the UPS sorting facility, located at 3901 Vero Rd, Baltimore, MD 21227 when I observed a parcel displaying characteristics of a drug laden parcel. The parcel is a brown cardboard box with a shipping label attached bearing the following information:  UPS Tracking # 1Z A72 98B01 0157 9875   Sender:  Marvin Dunn  1510 Ridge Way  Medford OR 97504   To: Tanya Campbell   2113 W Fairmount Ave   Baltimore MD 21223   It should be noted that I know, as a result of my training, knowledge and experience in the area of controlled dangerous substance (CDS) and parcel interdiction investigations, that persons involved in narcotics trafficking frequently utilize the various private courier companies such as UPS to transfer CDS from one person/place to another. I conducted a track of the aforementioned parcel utilizing the UPS mobile application. I discovered that the parcel was in fact shipped from Oregon. Im aware that Oregon is a source state for CDS.  A closer examination of the parcel revealed that the parcel was excessively taped. Ive learned during the course of parcel interdiction investigations, that persons who utilize the various parcel delivery companies to mail CDS frequently heavily tape the parcel seams in an effort to conceal the odor of the CDS, and to ensure contents are not exposed during transit to its intended destination.  In an effort to further this investigation, I had the parcel scanned utilizing a narcotics detection canine, Mia #3191. As a result of the scan, Canine Mia positively alerted to the odor of a narcotic.  Narcotics detection canine Mia is trained and certified to alert to the odor of controlled substances. These substances include marijuana, cocaine and heroin. Upon location of one of these controlled substances, Mia is trained to sit/lay at the source of the odor. This is called an alert. This alert may also indicate items recently contaminated with the odor of one or more of the controlled dangerous substances listed. Canine Mia is assigned to Sergeant Murphy #2936 of the Maryland State Police.  Canine Mia and Sergeant Murphy receive monthly training in order to maintain Mias reliability in the detection of controlled dangerous substances.  I then seized the parcel, and authored a search and seizure warrant for the parcel. The search and seizure warrant was reviewed, and authorized by the Honorable Judge C. Campbell of the Cecil County District Court. A search of the parcel pursuant to the search and seizure warrant revealed the following:  Six (6) heat/vacuum sealed bags containing marijuana  The contraband was secured in DSPII temporary storage. A controlled delivery couldnt be completed in a timely, safe and efficient manner. I then completed the administrative requirements of the search and seizure warrant.   DSPII Investigators will be monitoring this address for future deliveries.   I respectfully request this case be closed.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6836</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 09:02:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6836</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 09:02:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40P</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Massoni</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5467</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40P</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stephen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Chrzanowski</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6836</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492313</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0233</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>A</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/24/2023 09:59:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>A</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6836</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 08:56:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6836</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 08:56:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6836</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 08:56:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6836</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 08:56:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>1</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6836</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 08:57:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6836</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 08:57:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242194</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>6.8</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>LB</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>