<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-021682</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/16/2023 19:26:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/16/2023 19:26:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/16/2023 18:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/16/2023 18:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>CDS Possession</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 19:26:39</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 08:45:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>698010</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 19:26:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 10:02:44</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>698010</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>51</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I70 Wb</StreetName>
         <City>Frederick</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.45939</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.40385</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/16/2023 19:26:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/16/2023 19:26:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/20/2023 08:45:38</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 19:26:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>I am not assigned a body or in-car camera. The following interaction was audibly and visually recorded by body cameras of TFC Brown, TFC White, and S/T Hopkins  Attachments: MSP 67 MSP 63 Criminal Citations Traffic Warning Photographs of Evidence  Complainant: TFC Potvin 6852 MSP Frederick Barrack 110 Airport Dr E Frederick, MD 21702 301-600-4151  Suspect: Larry Lee Hull 574 Back Creek Valley Road Hedgesville, WV 25427 304-806-8504  Madalina Paula Ciobanita 19424 Longmeadow Road Hagerstown, MD 21742 240-329-8379  Scene Processing: Due to the presence of several criminal indicators, a k9 scan was conducted of a vehicle that was stopped on I-70 westbound in the area of the 51 mile marker. This scan resulted in a positive alert to the odor of narcotics emanating from the vehicle and a search of the vehicle was conducted.  In a backpack that was found in the front passenger seat area was a black plastic magnetic storage box. In this box was one clear gel capsule containing suspected heroin and fentanyl, three plastic straws, and one glass smoking device. A search of the passenger who was seated closest to the bag revealed an additional 13 gel capsules containing suspected fentanyl and heroin on her person, hidden in her hair tie. In total, 14 gel capsules weighing 6.8 grams were recovered and attributed to Ciobanita.  On the ground next to my patrol car where Hull was standing were 5 gel capsules containing suspected heroin and fentanyl, weighing 4.4 grams.  The evidence was seized and transported to the MSP Frederick Barrack where it was counted, weighed, and packaged in a heat-sealed kpak bag. The evidence was documented on MSP form 67 (chain of custody) and form 63 (property form). The evidence was secured in the MSP Frederick Barrack evidence room pending laboratory analysis.  All of the above was done in accordance with MSP policy and procedure.  Narrative: On June 16th, 2023 at approximately 1820 hours, I was stationary in a crossover on I-70 in the area of the Linganore Road overpass, monitoring westbound traffic. I was operating my assigned unmarked Impala, CE-143. Directly next to me in the crossover were two marked MSP patrol vehicles, both overtly labeled K9 Patrol. I observed a Honda Accord approach my location in lane two. As the vehicle passed, I observed three occupants. The driver was sitting rigidly with both hands on the steering wheel and staring straight ahead. The rear passenger was slouched down, as though he was trying not to be seen. I did not see any signs of conversation between the occupants. I entered I-70 westbound and caught up to the Honda, which was displaying Maryland registration 6EM1910.  I continued to follow the vehicle as we approached the interchange for US-340. I was in lane two following behind a tractor trailer truck. The Honda was in lane three. The Honda made a sudden lane change into lane two, positioning the vehicle between myself and the tractor trailer truck. This maneuver caused the Honda to only be approximately one car length (approximately 16 feet) behind the truck in front of it. The Honda continued to follow behind the truck at this distance while traveling at approximately 60 miles per hour for over one mile. Knowing this following distance to be unsafe, I activated my vehicles emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop.  I approached the front passenger window. As I did, I observed the female passenger lighting a cigarette. I identified myself to the vehicles occupants and asked the driver if he had a drivers license with him. He stated that he did not, but that he did have his West Virginia identification card. I requested that he exit the vehicle and wait for me by the front of my vehicle, to which he complied. While he did so, I asked the passengers for identification as well. The front passenger initially told me that the vehicle belonged to her but later stated that it actually belonged to her father. While looking for her identification, she told me that they had traveled to Baltimore City to pick up the drivers girlfriend. She was unable to tell me the name of this woman, where in Baltimore they were getting her, or what she had been doing there. She further stated that they never actually picked her up because she decided she wanted to stay and that they were only in Baltimore for around 30 minutes. The passenger eventually produced a Maryland drivers license, identifying her as Madalina Paula Ciobanita (W/F; DOB 06/10/1992).  The rear passenger did not have any identification, but would provide his name and date of birth identifying himself as Larry Lee Hull (W/M; DOB 10/09/1972). While speaking with Ciobanita, Hull remained silent. His breathing was heavy and he avoided eye contact. Hull continued to slouch in his seat as though making himself smaller.  I returned to the front of my patrol vehicle to speak with the driver. He presented a West Virginia identification card, which identified him as Rodney Vaughn Wolfe Jr (W/M; DOB 03/23/1980). While reviewing Wolfes identification, I asked him about their travels. He stated that they had gone to Baltimroe to pick up his girlfriend. Wolfe stated that they were there for several hours, that he was unable to find her, and that they eventually left. When I asked why the other two passengers were with him, he stated that it was because he did not have a reliable form of transportation.  I requested TFC White, who was already on scene with his narcotics detection K9, conduct a scan of the vehicle. While he conducted this scan, I returned to my vehicle to advise the MSP Frederick Barracks Emergency Dispatcher of the identities of the occupants and to begin writing a warning to Wolfe for the unsafe lane change and following too closely. Prior to finishing writing the warning, the scan resulted in a positive alert to the odor of narcotics emanating from the vehicle.  I advised the three vehicle occupants of their rights under Miranda, which all three indicated they understood. I then began conducting a search of the vehicle, while TFC Brown stood with the three occupants. Shortly thereafter, I was called over by TFC Brown, who had located 5 gel capsules containing suspected heroin and fentanyl on the ground near Hull. I conducted a brief field interview with Hull, who admitted to dropping the gel capsules in an attempt to hide them from law enforcement.  I resumed the search of the Honda. In a backpack that was found in the front passenger seat area was a black plastic magnetic storage box. In this box was one clear gel capsule containing suspected heroin and fentanyl, three plastic straws, and one glass smoking device. A search of Ciobanita, who was seated where the bag was found, revealed an additional 13 gel capsules containing suspected fentanyl and heroin on her person, hidden in her hair tie. In total, 14 gel capsules weighing 6.8 grams were recovered and attributed to Ciobanita.  Ciobanita and Hull were both issued criminal citations for the possession of a schedule II controlled dangerous substance. Cibanita was released from the scene along with Wolfe. A check of Hull through NCIC revealed an active warrant for his arrest. This warrant was confirmed and I placed Hull under arrest. I transported Hull to the Frederick County Adult Detention Center, where he was transferred to the custody of a Frederick County Sheriffs Office Deputy for service of the warrant.  The evidence was transported to the MSP Frederick Barrack where it was processed according to MSP Policy and Procedure.  I have been a Trooper with the Maryland State Police for approximately six years and am currently assigned as an investigator to the Criminal Enforcement Division  Western Region. I have undergone a 6-month training academy, during which I received 40 hours of drug identification and detection training. I have also received additional training from MSP PACE team, HIDTA, the Multijurisdictional CounterDrug Task Force Training Center, Triple I Solutions, DEA, FBI, and other organizations. During my time as a Maryland State Trooper, I have been involved in several hundred seizures of Heroin and Fentanyl. I have been involved in several hundred seizures of other types of CDS.  I know through this training, knowledge, and experience that heroin is a schedule I controlled substance and that fentanyl is a schedule II controlled substance.  Charges: 1 1111 CR, 5 601(a)(1) : CDS: POSSESS-NOT MARIJUANA  Case Status: Case closed by criminal citation and arrest.  All events occurred in Frederick County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:56:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6852</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 14:31:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brown</LastName>
            <FirstName>Shawn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5330</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brendan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7132</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ingram</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jasmine </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6663</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hopkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Douglas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6060</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Potvin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Noah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6852</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511118</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 18:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:03:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6852</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 10:03:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>50</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:07:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:17</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380284</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hull</LastName>
               <FirstName>Larry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/09/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.3531044E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/19/2023 10:06:49</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hull</LastName>
               <FirstName>Larry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/09/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.3531044E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>H400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/19/2023 10:06:49</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>574</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Back Creek Valley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hedgesville</City>
               <StateCode>WV</StateCode>
               <Zip5>25427</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6416</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-78.1598947</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.3911123</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>304</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>806</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8504</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:21:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:21:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:21:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:11:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>101139</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ciobanita</LastName>
               <FirstName>Madalina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Paula</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/10/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16532822E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>05/17/2016 14:14:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C153</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M345</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ciobanita</LastName>
               <FirstName>Madalina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Paula</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/10/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16532822E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>C153</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M345</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/17/2016 14:14:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>19424</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Longmeadow</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hagerstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21742</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.693979</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.682607</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>329</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8379</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:20:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:20:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PA</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:20:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:20:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>43</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:12:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:57</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>311443</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>WOLFE</LastName>
               <FirstName>RODNEY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>VAUGHN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/23/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2021 14:05:30</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W410</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R350</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>WOLFE</LastName>
               <FirstName>RODNEY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>VAUGHN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/23/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>W410</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R350</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2021 14:05:30</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1256</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Broad</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Falling Waters</City>
               <StateCode>WV</StateCode>
               <Zip5>25419</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3531</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.843873</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.577355</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>302</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1759</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/29/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:12:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:03:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6852</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 10:03:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:13:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6852</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 10:13:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>14 gel capsules containing suspected fentanyl/heroin</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>250752</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>D</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>6.8</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:13:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6852</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 10:13:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>6 gel capsules containing suspected fentanyl/heroin</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>250753</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>D</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>4.4</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:15:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6852</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 10:15:28</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Plastic smoking devices</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>100</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>250754</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>4</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:15:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6852</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 10:15:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Black magnetic box</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>100</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>250755</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6852</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 10:15:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6852</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 10:15:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Hair tie</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>510</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>250756</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>GRY</PrimaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>