<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-024543</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/09/2023 03:25:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/09/2023 03:25:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/09/2023 02:49:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/09/2023 02:49:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/CDS</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/09/2023 03:25:15</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/29/2023 19:25:43</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>W/B 50 at Lottsford Vista Road</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>531861</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 02:38:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/10/2023 02:40:10</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>531861</AddressId>
         <StreetName>MD 50</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.827346</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.946954</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/09/2023 03:25:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/09/2023 03:25:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/21/2023 21:59:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/09/2023 03:25:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:51</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI Report Marked Car # Q-16 equipped with an in-car camera and body camera.  MARYLAND STATE POLICE  SUMMARY Defendant: Timothy Ekenedilchuk Onyiuke Date of Birth: 12/20/1980 Date of Arrest: 07/09/2023 Time of Arrest: 0321 Maryland Soundex: O-520-793-199-964 DUI #: 23-145 MSP Case # 23-MSP-024543  OFFICER TRAINING/EXPERIENCE   I am trained and certified in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration  Trained and certified to conduct preliminary breathalyzer tests by the Maryland State Police.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On 07/09/2023 at approximately 0250 hours, I, Trooper Stallings #7589 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, was dispatched to the report of a disabled vehicle partially in the roadway on westbound John Hanson Highway at Lottsford Vista road. Upon my arrival at 0302 hours, I observed a black Mercedes sedan bearing Maryland registration 3EX2957 parked on the right shoulder, partially blocking lane 4.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the vehicle on the passenger side of the vehicle and made contact with the driver, later identified asTimothy Ekenedilchuk Onyiuke (DOB: 12/20/1980). I observed Onyiuke to be asleep in the driver seat with the front zipper of his pants undone. This lead me to knock on the window multiple times in an attempt to wake Onyiuke, these attempts failed. I then opened the front passenger door of the vehicle in order to wake Onyiuke and check on his well-being. After approximately 20 seconds of trying to communicate withOnyiuke, he finally woke up. Once awake,Onyiuke confirmed that he was okay. I also observed a plastic water bottle on the center console with a yellow liquid inside, most likely urine. I then asked the driver to provide me with his license and registration for the vehicle. While searching for the registration for the vehicle, Onyiuke gave me an unrelated paper which was not what I asked for. I also asked Onyiuke how many drinks he had that night, he replied with none. Onyiuke failed to provide the registration for the vehicle, so I then asked him for his license a second time. While searching in his wallet for his license, he pulled out a red MasterCard credit card and tried to hand it to me. I had to advise him that what he tried to hand me was in fact not his license. Shortly after this, he then provided me with his Maryland drivers license. While speaking to the driver I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle and driver. The drivers movements were very lethargic and his speech was very slurred, struggling to even talk in full sentences. Based on my observations, I had reason to believe the driver was possibly under the influence of an alcoholic beverage. The driver was asked to exit and asked to step to the front of their vehicle for testing. While Onyiuke exited the vehicle, I observed there to be large wet spots on the front and back of his pants in his groin and buttocks region, this was most likely from Onyiuke urinating on himself. I also observed his belt to not be on properly and half of the belt was dangling from his waist. Onyiuke proceeded to stand in the roadway next to his vehicle and struggle to put his belt on properly, even after my many requests for him to step to the front of the vehicle. I asked Onyiuke 3 times to walk to the front of his vehicle, which he failed to do. Onyiuke was then guided to the front of his vehicle by myself and Trooper Fleming.I asked the driver to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to which he agreed.Note that my emergency lights were deactivated and the driver was placed in a position not to be affected by passing motorists lights. The surface was flat and level, and the weather conditions were dry.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) Testing was performed on the right shoulder of John Hanson Highway at Lottsford Vista road. It was dry and the road was level and free from any debris. The driver was asked and provided answers to the following questions:  Medical Conditions- None Injuries- None Medication: None Glass/Contacts: N/A  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS(6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus. It was held approximately 12-15 inches from Onyiuke s eyes, slightly above his eye level.Onyiuke was instructed to follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes without moving his head. Onyiuke s eyes were equal in size and showed equal tracking.  The driver displayed the following clues:  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes 4) Vertical Nystagmus - Not tested for  *The driver was observed to have difficulty following the stimulus, he had to be reminded many times to look at the tip of the pen*  WALK AND TURN(8/8 clues observed) The test was explained and demonstrated.Onyiukewas instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe in a straight line.Onyiukewas then instructed to place his hands down by his sides and remain in that position until told to begin.Onyiukewas advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot planted, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn,Onyiuke  was instructed to complete the second series of nine (9) steps in the same heel to toe fashion.Onyiukewas instructed to keep his hands down by his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, count every step aloud, and once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I askedOnyiuke if he understood the test and he confirmed that he did.  Onyiuke completed the test wearing tennis shoes.  INSTRUCTIONAL PHASE    Onyiukefailed to maintain the instructed position by separating his feet  Onyiuke attempted to start the test early, multiple times  Walking Stage (1st Nine)    Onyiukestepped off-line on steps 3,4, and 9  Onyiuke missed heel to toe on steps 6,7, and 8  Onyiuke raised his arms away from his body on step 4  Onyiuke stopped walking 3 different times and had to be reminded each time to continue  Onyiuke took 13 steps instead of 9  Turn Onyiuke forgot he had to turn and had to be reminded, once he did the turn he did it improperly by not keeping his lead foot planted. Onyiuke also took 3 steps backwards after the turn instead of walking forward in the direction he came from.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine)    Onyiukestepped off-line on steps 6 and 8  Onyiuke missed heel to toe on steps 5 and 9  Onyiuke stopped walking after step 6 and had to be reminded to continue  Onyiuke took 11steps instead of 9  Onyiuke restarted his count after step 6.  ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed) The test was explained and demonstrated.Onyiuke was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, etc) and to not put his foot down until the end of the test. I askedOnyiuke if he understood the test and he confirmed that he did.  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Onyiuke dropped his foot 3 times Onyiuke swayed to try and keep his balance Seconds 11-20: Onyiukedropped his foot 4 times Seconds 21-30: Onyiukedropped his foot 4 times Onyiuke swayed to try and keep his balance  During the one leg stand test,Onyiuke would count to 20 seconds and then switch the leg he was balancing on. He did this 3 different times and restarted his count each time he started balancing on a different leg.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) The driver was asked to submit to a preliminary breath test. The driver was informed that it was not admissible in court. The driver did not elect to take the test. I am certified to operate this instrument.   ARREST As a result of my observations, I had reason to believe the driver was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of an alcoholic beverage in excess of 0.08 BrAC. I felt that the driver was also unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0321 hours, I placed the driver under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. The driver was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy. Onyiuke was then provided with a copy of the DR-15 advice of rights and was played an english audio recording of the rights via the MVA website. At the conclusion of the reading, the driver elected to refuse the test of breath. The driver was then transported to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack for processing.  The vehicle was towed by Alley Cat towing due to it being partially in the roadway.  Controlled Dangerous Substance The below listed item of evidence was located in Onyiukes front, right pants pocketduring a search incident to arrest:    One blue plastic CDS straw with suspected cocaine residue  The below listed item of evidence was located during a search of the vehicle within reach of the drivers seat in the center console:    One metal tin containing a crushed up white substance suspected to be cocaine  The evidence was later packaged, processed, and stored under Property Number P-341206 at the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack per MSP policy.Onyiuke was issued a criminal citation (142003398283).  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  CASE STATUS:Closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 03:45:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/14/2023 14:12:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fleming</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sierra</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7439</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>PERIS</LastName>
            <FirstName>BRYAN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7511</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stallings</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7589</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stallings</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7589</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stallings</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7589</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513983</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/09/2023 03:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 02:42:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/10/2023 02:56:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513983</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/09/2023 03:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 02:42:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/10/2023 02:57:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513983</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/09/2023 03:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 14:28:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/14/2023 14:28:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513983</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/09/2023 03:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 14:29:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/14/2023 14:29:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513983</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/09/2023 03:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 14:29:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/14/2023 14:29:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>42</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 02:42:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:50</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382028</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>A</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Onyiuke</LastName>
               <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ekenedilchuk</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/20/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/09/2023 06:55:07</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>O520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Onyiuke</LastName>
               <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ekenedilchuk</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/20/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>O520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/09/2023 06:55:07</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>14812</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Saddle Creek</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Burtonsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20866</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3141</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.918728</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.098908</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>347</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>596</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3959</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 03:00:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 03:00:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 03:00:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 02:42:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/10/2023 02:42:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154988</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 03:12:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/10/2023 03:12:14</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MERZ</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ECLASS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4D</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3EX2957</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 03:06:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/10/2023 03:06:33</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Metal tin of white powder</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>251580</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>XX</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/10/2023 03:08:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/10/2023 03:08:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One Blue Plastic CDS Straw</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>999</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>251581</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLU</PrimaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>