<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020145</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/05/2023 14:12:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/05/2023 14:12:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/05/2023 13:43:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/05/2023 13:43:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect stole items from Walmart and had an active warrant for her arrest. While effecting the arrest, the suspect assaulted an officer. A search incident to arrest revealed CDS: Not Marijuana.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 14:13:02</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3143</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 12:18:29</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>THS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>13487</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 14:13:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 09:19:33</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>13487</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>45485</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>MIRAMAR</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>CALIFORNIA</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20619</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.502602</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.293011</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WALMART</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WALMART - MAX DEPLOYMENT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SMART STYLE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/05/2023 14:12:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/05/2023 14:12:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/09/2023 10:11:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 14:13:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-car camera and body worn camera operational (T-16).  SCENE PROCESSING:      One MSP Form 030, Notice Not to Trespass. One CD containing video surveillance. One Itemized receipt. Two digital photographs of the suspect, which were attached to this report and uploaded to Veripic. A search incident to arrest revealed the following; One (1) zip lock bag containing one metal smoking device containing suspected cocaine. One (1) zip lock bag containing one clear baggie containing suspected Cocaine.  PHYSICAL EVIDENCE:  As a result of the investigation, the following items were seized and are available for presentation to the court;  ITEM A- One (1) CD containing video surveillance  Refer to the Maryland State Police Form #67 for complete Chain of Custody.  Two digital photographs of the suspect.  One Itemized Receipt. Total Value Stolen: $46.81 Total Value Recovered: $46.81  ITEM A-One (1) zip lock bag containing one metal smoking device containing suspected Cocaine. Listed on P-344496  Weight- Residue  ITEM B-One (1) zip lock bag containing one clear baggie containing suspected Cocaine. Listed on P-344496  Weight- 5.1 grams with package  The above listed CDS is being held under Property Record P-344496. Refer to the Maryland State Police Form #67 for complete Chain of Custody. The above evidence will be stored at the Maryland State Police, Leonardtown Barrack T Property Room pending trial.  NARRATIVE:  On June 5, 2023, at 1343 hours, while on duty, I responded to the Walmart located at 45485 Miramar Way California, St. Marys County, Maryland 20619 for a reported theft. The St. Marys County Emergency Communications Center (ECC) advised that Ashley Renee Harvey (B/F DOB 05/03/1994) stole items from Walmart and was now walking on foot away from the Walmart.  Upon my arrival, I made contact with Harvey at the Checkers Restaurant located at 45500 Miramar Way California, St. Marys County, Maryland 20619. I identified Harvey by her MVA photograph. While on my way to the scene, PCO H. Frankel #7711 conducted a wanted check of Harvey through NCIC which revealed she had an Active Warrant #62822 through MSP Leonardtown Barrack T for Theft less $100. Upon approaching Harvey, I informed her she had an active arrest warrant and that she is under arrest. She became very agitated and starting yelling curse words at myself and Tpr Hersh. We both attempted to deescalate the situation by talking to Harvey in a calm and clear voice. Harvey was sitting on a table. While I was holding her right wrist, I gave her verbal commands to stand up. Harvey got agitated and angry towards us. Harvey yelled at us stating she wanted to stand up on her own, without us holding onto to her. As part of our de-escalation, I let go of Harvey and stood in front of her to prevent her from running away. Harvey then stood up on her own.  Harvey began to actively resist arrest after standing up from the table, I gave verbal commands to Harvey to place her hands behind her back. Harvey attempted to walk away from me so I used my left hand to grab Harveys left elbow and my right hand to grab Harveys left wrist. Harvey immediately jerked her arm forward in attempt to break the hold I had on her left arm. I used a muscling technique to place her left arm and hand behind her back. Once her left hand was placed behind her back, I placed her hand into handcuffs. While this was happening, Tpr Hersh was on Harveys right side. Tpr Hersh used a muscling technique to place Harveys right hand behind her back, once her hand was placed behind her back, I then used my right hand and placed it on Harveys right wrist and then placed her hand into handcuffs. While I was placing her right hand into handcuffs, Harvey turned towards Tpr Hersh and spit on Tpr Hershs body and face. At that time, both of Harveys hands were handcuffed behind her back. I then placed my right arm underneath her left arm and placed my right hand on her back. I then lifted my arm up, forcing Harveys body to bend forward at the waist and she was escorted to the front hood of my patrol vehicle and placed face down against the vehicles hood to prevent her from spitting on more officers. Once Harvey was against the vehicles hood and not offering active resistance, all force stopped.  Tpr Hersh responded back to the Walmart and made contact with the complainant, who was identified by his MVA photograph as Flor Cruz (H/M DOB 12/31/1975). Cruz is the loss prevention officer at Walmart, he advised that Harvey took multiple items off the shelves and placed them into her personal bag. One Harvey passed all points of sale, Cruz confronted Harvey about the items in her bag. Harvey was unable to provide a receipt for the items in her bag. Cruz advised they got into a verbal altercation, after several minutes Harvey admitted to taking items off the shelfs and did not pay for them. Harvey took the items out of her back and Cruz was able to recover the items. Harvey then left the store and Cruz contacted Law Enforcement. Tpr Hersh obtained and reviewed the surveillance which confirmed the sequence of events. PCO H. Frankel #7711 conducted a wanted check of Cruz through NCIC which revealed he had an Active Warrant #61468 through MSP Leonardtown Barrack T for failure to appear for driving while suspended. Cruz was placed under arrest and transported by Tpr Hersh to the St. Marys County Detention and Rehabilitation Center, pending a bond review with the District Court Commissioner.   Harvey was placed under arrest at 1408 hours, and placed in the back seat of Deputy Hills #381 patrol vehicle. Deputy Hill transported Harvey to the St. Marys County Detention and Rehabilitation Center, pending a bond review with the District Court Commissioner. Upon arrival to the detention center, medical personnel refused to accept Harvey due to having a feed tube coming out of her stomach which was a preexisting medical condition. It should be noted the detention center wanted Harvey to go to the Hospital to make sure her feeding tube was working properly. Deputy Hill transported Harvey to the St. Marys County Hospital. While Harvey was at the hospital, I completed an application of charges. The District Court Commissioner issued a warrant for Harvey for 2nd degree assault, theft less than $100, and resisting arrest. Harvey was cleared by the Hospital staff and her feeding tube was working properly. I transported Harvey to the detention center.  Upon arrival of the detention center, a search conducted of Harvey by Correctional Officer Barrow #879. Officer Barrow located one metal smoking device containing suspected Cocaine and one clear baggie containing suspected Cocaine, located in Harveys pants in her crotch area. Through my training, knowledge and experience from the Maryland State Police Academy and previous drug arrest, I identified the controlled dangerous substance as Cocaine, a schedule II narcotic.  Harvey was served with all active warrants and served an MSP Form 030, Notice Not to Trespass, and charged with CR 5-601 CDS: Possession Not Marijuana, CR 5-619 CDS: Possession of Paraphernalia, and CR 9-412a3 Possession of Contraband in Place of Confinement.  All events occurred in St. Marys County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:36:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 09:34:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hersh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Taylor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7443</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5920</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7350</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509579</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0521 23C</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>12</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 13:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0521 23C</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:00:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:00:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509579</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0600</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>12</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 13:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0600</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:02:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:02:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509579</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>12</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 13:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:03:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:03:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509579</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>15</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 13:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:04:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:04:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509579</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>5 3550</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>15</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 13:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>5 3550</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:05:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:05:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509579</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1835</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>15</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 13:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1835</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:05:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:05:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509579</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19761</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>12</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 13:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19761</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:44:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:44:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:07:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>97140</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Harvey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Renee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/03/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/14/2016 14:50:31</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Harvey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Renee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/03/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/14/2016 14:50:31</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>45249</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Coledorall</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>California</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20619</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.509293</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.289744</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>21735</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cabot</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.463701</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.264233</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>880</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6541</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/14/2016 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>466</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2631</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/14/2016 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:07:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:07:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:07:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:18:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379116</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hersh #7443</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trooper</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 11:16:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T616</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hersh #7443</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trooper</FirstName>
               <SLastName>H620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T616</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 11:16:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>23200</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Leonard Hall Drive</StreetName>
               <City>Leonardtown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20650</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.631365</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.305941</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>310</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>475</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8955</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:46:36</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>47</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:45:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:04</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>239795</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cruz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Flor</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Angel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/04/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F460</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cruz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Flor</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>NMN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/28/2019 05:50:28</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F460</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>CRUZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>FLOR</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/31/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F460</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cruz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Flor</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Angel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F460</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/04/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cruz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Flor</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>NMN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F460</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/28/2019 05:50:28</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>CRUZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>FLOR</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/31/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F460</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>45485</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Miramar</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>California</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20619</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.502038</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.293736</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>19877</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Three Notch</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.403901</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.213353</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>20536</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Ridge</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.406897</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.231997</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>20536</StreetNumber>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.4068976</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.2319972</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>496</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1925</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/05/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>808</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0224</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/01/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:45:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:45:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:45:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:04:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:04:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240005527</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>Walmart</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:19:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:19:09</UpdatorDate>
         <BusinessAddress>
            <AddressId>93303</AddressId>
            <StreetNumber>45485</StreetNumber>
            <StreetName>Miramar</StreetName>
            <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
            <City>California</City>
            <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
            <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
            <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            <Longitude>-76.502602</Longitude>
            <Latitude>38.293011</Latitude>
            <BusinessPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>BUS</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>737</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4420</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/25/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </BusinessPhone>
         </BusinessAddress>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>7</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:22:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:22:34</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>The suspect stole multiple items, to include a watch, necklace, and deli chicken. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>999</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>46.81</PropertyValue>
         <Value>46.81</Value>
         <SerialNumber>N/A</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249980</Property_ID>
         <Make>N/A</Make>
         <Model>N/A</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:30:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:30:51</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Item A- One zip lock bag containing one metal smoking device containing suspected Cocaine. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>100</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>N/A</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249982</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>SIL</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>SIL</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>N/A</Make>
         <Model>N/A</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:32:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:32:16</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Item B- One zip lock bag containing one clear baggie containing suspected Cocaine. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249984</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>4.1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 11:34:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 11:34:59</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Item A- One CD containing video surveillance of the theft. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>819</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>N/A</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249985</Property_ID>
         <Make>N/A</Make>
         <Model>N/A</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>