<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-035887</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/13/2023 03:14:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/13/2023 03:14:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/13/2023 02:32:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/13/2023 02:32:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop for suspended registration. Observed indicators consistent with CDS involvement. Requested for K9 which ultimately scanner the vehicle resulting in a positive alert. Probable cause search revealed a small amount of loose crack cocaine.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 03:14:38</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4792</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/02/2023 08:50:16</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN HWY/ MARKET LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>531134</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 03:14:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 03:28:47</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>531134</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Princess Anne</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.689114</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.168018</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10221-10454 OCEAN HWY / 0-0 MARKET LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10218-10455 OCEAN HWY / 0-0 MARKET LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10953-11073 OCEAN HWY / 10900-10992 MARKET LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10819-10952 OCEAN HWY / 10900-10992 MARKET LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 OCEAN HWY / 0-0 MARKET LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/13/2023 03:14:35</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/13/2023 03:14:35</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/31/2023 15:44:46</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 03:14:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 16:26:58</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Trooper J. Hicks # 7576 Maryland State Police BK: X Date of incident: 10/13/2023 CC # 23-MSP-035887  BWC: This incident was captured via my MSP issued body worn camera and front facing patrol vehicle camera.   Suspect/Offender/Driver Name: Kevin John Spears DOB: 10/29/1971 MD SDX:S-162-465-429-832  Victims Name: State of Maryland  Officers Training/Experience:   *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Eastern Shore Criminal Justice Academy and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA). 2015.   Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).2022.   Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police.   NHTSA certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E).   CDS detection, recognition, packaging, distribution, classification and indicator training from ESCJA police academy (2015) and Maryland State Police Academy (2022).      Gangs 101  Basic SWAT School (2017)   IED (Improvised Explosive Device) detection, recognition, familiarization and scene management procedures. (2017).   *MPCTC Basic Instructor (general instructor/ defensive tactics)   Numerous CDS arrests and convictions in Wicomico County, Maryland Courts as a previous Police Officer/ Detective with the Salisbury Police Department.   Seven (7) years as a Salisbury City, Maryland Police Officer/ Detective. Lead investigator/Assisted in numerous high-profile cases to include: Thefts, robberies, burglaries, homicides, fraud, prohibited firearm possession, firearm possession, assaults, sexual assaults etc. Written/Assisted with numerous search and seizure warrants. Interviewed numerous suspects charged with various crimes. Numerous convictions in the District and Circuit Courts for Wicomico County, Maryland.   Processing/Property:    MSP 67   MSP PH form   margin-left:8px"&gt;Heat sealed bag containing loose crack cocaine. Trace amount.  Assignment: On 10/13/2023, I was working my regular scheduled night shift patrol assignment in Somerset County, Maryland. I was utilizing vehicle X-30 as my regular assigned patrol vehicle was being receiving maintenance.  Narrative: This report has been prepared based upon the observations of this trooper and/or those of other troopers relative to the offense(s). The facts contained herein are intended solely to give the prosecuting authority a basic understanding of the facts pertaining to this case. The facts contained herein are not intended to be an exhaustive recitation of the facts pertaining to pretrial or trial issues. Instead, this trooper anticipates that during the pretrial proceedings in this case, the prosecutor will take the opportunity to interview this trooper in order to ascertain any and all relevant facts which might be the subject of this troopers testimony during court proceedings.  Narrative/ Statement of events:   On 10/13/2023 at approximately 0232 hours, I was conducting roving traffic enforcement patrol in the area of N/B US RT 13 in the area of Market Lane. At the listed time, I observed a white, 2016 Mazda CX5 bearing Maryland registration: 2EW8802 traveling at approximately 45 mph in a 55 mph zone. An MVA search of the listed registration revealed that it was SUSPENDED.  I then activated my emergency equipment (front and rear facing lights) and conducted a traffic stop on the listed vehicle. The vehicle came to a stop on N/B US RT 13 just north of Market Lane. Upon making contact with the driver and sole occupant of the vehicle, I requested the drivers license and vehicle registration card. The driver produced his Maryland Drivers License and I identified him as Kevin John Spears (DOB: 10/29/1971). Spears was hesitant to reach into his glove-box and advised he was just stopped by the police a few days prior, and did not have the registration card at that time. While speaking with Spears, I observed his forehead to be covered in sweat. It should be noted at the time of this stop, It was approximately 50 degrees Farenheit outside. It should be noted Spears did not have the heat activated in his vehicle at the time of this stop. I further observed Spears to appear nervous and staring straight ahead when speaking to me failing to make eye contact on several occasions when asking him routine questions related to the traffic stop. Based on my training knowledge and experience as a police officer, I know the above behaviors displayed by Spears to be consistent with someone that is involved in criminal activity.  Based on the above observations, I requested for a K9 to respond. Somerset County Sheriffs Office (SCSO) Deputy Wahlbert arrived on scene a short time later. Deputy Wahlbert utilized his K9 partner to conduct an outer air sniff around the exterior of Spears vehicle. This resulted in a positive alert for the odor/presence of narcotics within Spears vehicle. Based on this, I conducted a probable cause search of said vehicle. During the search, I located several small pieces of Crack Cocaine in the seams of the driver side front seat along and underneath the driver side front seat. I knew this to be Crack Cocaine a schedule II controlled dangerous substance through my training knowledge and experience as a police officer.These pieces of Crack Cocaine were seized as evidence at 0301 hours.    While searching the vehicle, Spears was standing in front of my patrol vehicle complaining of the temperature outside being cold, however as stated above his forehead was covered in sweat. After locating the Crack Cocaine, I showed same to Spears and informed him that it would be sent to the MSP crime lab for chemical testing. Spears was informed if the substance is in-fact revealed to be Crack Cocaine that I would be completing an application for charges against him. He advised that he understood and had no questions. I then provided Spears with his traffic citations related to this traffic stop. Spears was released from the scene upon receiving his traffic documents.    A warrant check on Spears revealed no active warrants. His license to drive status through the State Of Maryland was VALID. The above Crack Cocaine was processed and submitted into MSP property in accordance with MSP policy and procedure. I respectfully request this case remain open pending the return of the CDS chemical testing results from the lab.    All events occurred in Somerset County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7576</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 03:43:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7576</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/29/2023 22:38:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Darby</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kaitlyn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7115</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hicks</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7576</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525347</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>08</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/13/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7576</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 03:30:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7576</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 03:30:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7576</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 03:39:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 03:39:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390273</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Spears</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/13/2023 03:37:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S162</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Spears</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
               <SLastName>S162</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/13/2023 03:37:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8541</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Fontaine</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westover</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21871</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.755915</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.116428</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>000</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>000</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0000</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7576</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 03:39:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7576</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 03:39:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7576</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 03:30:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7576</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 03:30:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7576</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 03:41:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7576</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 03:41:20</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Loose crack cocaine pieces. Trace amount located under the seat of suspect vehicle. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255209</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>