<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012387</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/07/2023 12:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/07/2023 12:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/07/2023 12:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/07/2023 12:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>CDS/WARRANT ARREST OF JAMES ANTHONY DENNIS JR.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 12:48:17</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 14:59:29</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ MAIDEN FOREST RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>640204</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 12:48:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 14:37:37</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>640204</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Vienna</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21869</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.882219</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.513331</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/07/2023 12:48:13</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/07/2023 12:48:13</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/24/2023 14:19:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 12:48:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:30</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>CASE NUMBER: 23-MSP-012387 INVESTIGATING TROOPER: Trooper First Class M. Mowbray #7119 NATURE OF INCIDENT: CDS Possession / Warrant Service SCENE PROCESSING: Scene processing was conducted with the following results;   One (1) MSP Form 67  Chain of Custody  One (1) MSP Property Record  P-344951  Two (2) State of Maryland Uniform Criminal Citation(s)  One (1) copy of State of Maryland Uniform Traffic Citation(s)  One (1) copy of District Court of Maryland Bench Warrant  Vehicle Search Report submitted on DeltaPlus  Seven (7) digital photographs of evidence - uploaded to VeriPic  One (1) clear plastic bag containing trace amounts of a white powder; cocaine  One (1) clear glass smoking device containing a trace amount of burnt cocaine  One (1) multicolored smoking device containing a trace amount of burnt cocaine   INCIDENT FOOTAGE: INCIDENT CAPTURED BY A MOBILE VIDEO RECORDER (MSP I-39) Traffic Stop Dash Camera: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:#0563c1; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=bef5af7abff1441e8eacd28248a51861partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 In-Car Camera: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:#0563c1; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=b45da759422c4c22a9c47869ff7e3848partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 INCIDENT CAPTIRED BY BODY WORN CAMERA Trooper M. Mowbray #7119 Body Worn Camera: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:#0563c1; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=acc49e7465364e5a8d69153eef8467e9partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 CAMERA SYSTEM / CAD SYSTEM The camera system is manufactured by Axon. The in-car; outward facing camera is activated when the emergency lights are activated in the patrol car or if manually activated by the user. The camera will go back in time and start the recording thirty (30) seconds before the camera is activated. This event is called a 30 second pre-record. The body worn camera (BWC); attached to the front of the Trooper, is also activated when the emergency lights are activated or manually by its user. The camera will record the previous sixty (60) seconds prior to the camera activation. The camera system does not have a date and time stamp on the video itself. The system records the date and time in the metadata. The time only records the hour and minute when the camera starts the recording. Therefore, the timeline below will start with a time that was recorded from the cameras metadata and then show the duration of the video. The in-car camera and body worn camera footage remains the best depiction of the events surrounding the traffic stop. However, in order to obtain an exact time of a specific event, the reader will have to add the length of duration from the start of the video that was recorded in the metadata. Although times are recorded by other means such as the Delta Plus system that prints a time stamp on the warning, citation or safety equipment repair order this time is only when the traffic enforcement button is activated by the Trooper. This date/time is usually started shortly after making contact with a violator and upon return to the patrol vehicle. Other programs such as Caliber RMS incident and CAD reports will show a timestamp, but this time depends on when the Police Communications Operator or Trooper activates the incident within the CAD system. The two aforementioned examples of the recording of time will almost always be different than the in-car camera system due to all of the systems utilizing different internal clocks.  INTRODUCTION: On April 7, 2023 I, Trooper First Class M. Mowbray #7119 of the Maryland State Police, conducted a traffic stop on U.S. Route 50 (Ocean Gateway) at Maiden Forest Road, Vienna, Dorchester County, Maryland for a traffic violation. While conducting the business needs of the traffic stop I detected numerous criminal indicators originating from the occupants of the vehicle, a black Acura TL bearing Virginia registration UAX6734. While making contact with the driver; who was identified by his Virginia identification card as Carl Kenneth Prioleau, the passenger; later identified as James Anthony Dennis Jr., provided me with a false name. After obtaining the identity of Dennis, it was learned that he had an active bench warrant originating from the Montgomery County Police Department. While placing Dennis into custody I located and seized one (1) clear plastic bag containing trace amounts of cocaine, one (1) clear glass smoking device containing burnt cocaine and one (1) multicolored smoking device containing a trace amount of burnt cocaine. Dennis was taken into custody and issued a State of Maryland Uniform Criminal Citation and released after being heard by a District Court Commissioner. Prioleau was issued the appropriate traffic related citations and released from the scene. The evidence was seized and transported to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack for processing.   ASSIGNMENT: On Friday, April 7, 2023, I, Trooper First Class M. Mowbray #7119, of the Maryland State Police, was assigned to road patrol duties at the Easton Barrack in Dorchester County, Maryland. The Easton Barrack is responsible for enforcing and investigating all criminal and traffic related crime within Talbot, Dorchester and Caroline counties respectively. My duties include but are not limited to: enforcing the criminal and motor vehicle laws of the State of Maryland, issuing traffic citations and warnings, investigating traffic accidents, investigating and completing criminal investigations, interviewing witnesses, victims and suspects and writing field reports.  THE TRAFFIC VIOLATION: On Friday, April 7, 2023 at approximately 1206 hours I, Trooper First Class M. Mowbray #7119 of the Maryland State Police was on patrol operating my marked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle I-39; a 2021 Ford Explorer, parked within the crossover on U.S. Route 50 (Ocean Gateway) near the Nanticoke River Memorial Bridge, Vienna, Dorchester County, Maryland 21869. While monitoring westbound traffic I observed a black 2014 Acura TL bearing Virginia registration UAX6734 traveling westbound in lane one passing by my location. As the vehicle passed directly in front of me I observed the validation tabs on the license plate to depict that the registration expired on September of 2022. I proceeded to follow the Acura and conducted an initial check of the registration status via the National Crime Information Center (NCIC) and Maryland Electronic Telecommunications Resource System (METERS) system on my mobile data terminal. The check revealed that the Virginia registration UAX6734 had expired effective September 2022 and the registered owner; identified by Virginia drivers license as James Anthony Dennis Jr. (DOB: 05/01/1975) [hereinafter identified as Dennis] had an active bench warrant out of Montgomery County, Maryland for CR 7-104: Theft: $100 To Under $1,500 (District Court Bench Warrant #: D-06-CR-22-060002-3). I then initiated a traffic stop of the vehicle by activating my emergency equipment which consists of red, blue, and white strobe lights and siren. The vehicle then pulled over to the right shoulder of westbound U.S. Route 50 near Maiden Forest Road, Vienna, Dorchester County, Maryland 21869.  THE TRAFFIC STOP: After the Acura came to a stop, I exited my patrol vehicle and approached the passengers side of the vehicle. I made contact with the driver; identified by Virginia identification card as Carl Kenneth Prioleau (DOB: 08/05/1987) [hereinafter identified as Prioleau], by introducing myself, informing him for the reason for the traffic stop and informing him that the incident was being audibly and visually recorded. I then requested the driver to retrieve the appropriate documents (i.e. drivers license, vehicle registration, etc.). While Prioleau was retrieving the documents I asked him who the registered owner of the Acura was, to which he turned his head towards the passenger and nodded in his direction and mumbled him. The passenger, who I later positively identified as Dennis, immediately stated; Hes not here. Prioleau the provided me with the registration card at which time I inquired again who the registered owner was to which the passenger again stated; Yeah, hes not with us right now.   I then returned to my patrol vehicle and relayed all pertinent information to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack Emergency Dispatcher.  METERS/NCIC CHECKS: After conducting checks of Prioleau via the National Crime Information Center (NCIC) and Maryland Electronic Telecommunications Resource System (METERS); it was learned that he only possessed a valid identification card through the State of Virginia and did not have a license or privilege to drive in any state.  After conducting checks of Dennis via the National Crime Information Center (NCIC) and Maryland Electronic Telecommunications Resource System (METERS); it was learned that he had the following active warrant; WARRANT NUMBER: D-06-CR-22-060002-3 TYPE: BENCH WARRANT  FAILURE TO APPEAR CHARGE(S): CR 7-104: THEFT: $100 TO UNDER $1,500 COUNTY: MONTGOMERY COUNTY AGENCY: MONTGOMERY COUNTY POLICE DEPARTMENT   I then provided the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack Emergency Dispatcher with the information, and obtaining a State of Virginia DMV photograph of Dennis, I returned to the Acura to advise Prioleau that he did not possess a valid drivers license and attempt to positively identify the passenger. After speaking with Prioleau, I asked the passenger to provide me with his name and/or identification to which he provided the name of Gary Dennis Davis (DOB: 05/06/1986) I then returned to my patrol vehicle and began to conduct a check of the name provided by Dennis which yielded no results. I then conducted a check of Dennis via a law enforcement database and obtained several mugshots of Dennis from various Virginia law enforcement agencies.   ARREST: I then returned to the Acura and confronted Dennis, who I could positively identify based on the various photographs, about his identity. After a long pause, Dennis stated Yeah, its me. I then requested that he exit the vehicle to which he complied. While Dennis was exiting the vehicle, I observed him attempt to conceal an item within the void space where the seat back meets the seat portion. Dennis then placed a blue/white box labeled Magnum True Airless Project Paint Plus on top of the seat to further conceal the item. I then instructed Dennis to turn around at which time I conducted a search of his person. While running my hand over his left front pocket, I felt what I could identify as a glass pipe with a broken edge concealed within the pocket. I then opened the pocket which revealed a glass smoking device that contained trace amounts of a burnt substance; which I can identify through my training, knowledge and experience as a Maryland State Police Trooper as drug paraphernalia used to inhale a Controlled Dangerous Substance. I then placed Dennis into custody and seized the evidence at 1232 hours. I then read aloud the Maryland State Police Form 180  Advice of Miranda Rights to Dennis, at which time he acknowledged them and waived his right to counsel and freely and voluntarily agreed to speak with me. I then asked Dennis what substance was within the glass smoking device to which he stated; Crack cocaine. I then continued to search his person and located one (1) clear plastic bag containing trace amounts of a white powder which I could also identify as a Controlled Dangerous Substance; Schedule II, cocaine.  SEARCH INCIDENT TO ARREST: After securing Dennis within my patrol vehicle I conducting a search of the area in which Dennis was seated. I immediately observed a multicolored smoking device containing a trace amount of burnt cocaine. During this time I conversed with Prioleau about the circumstances. I inquired with Prioleau as to the origination of the multiple boxes of the Magnum True Airless Project Paint Plus. Prioleau advised that the items were picked up for his sister due to her starting a painting business. I then issued Prioleau the appropriate traffic related citations and released him from the scene.  After completing the search I retrieved the evidence, ended the search and placed the seized evidence in my marked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle I-39.  ARREST PROCESS: I then transported Dennis to the Maryland State Police Cambridge Detachment; located at 829 Fieldcrest Road, Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland, and processed him per Maryland State Police policy. Dennis was issued two (2) State of Maryland Uniform Criminal Citations for; CR 5-601 (A)(1): CDS POSSESSION  NOT CANNABIS (202001812261) CR 5-619 (C)(2): CDS POSSESSION  PARAPHERNALIA (202001812272)  Dennis was then released on an unsecured $500 bond on the active warrant after being heard by a State of Maryland District Court Commissioner.  POST ARREST INVESTIGATION: At approximately 1625 hours on April 7, 2023, I arrived at the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack and processed the evidence per Maryland State Police policy. The total weight of the Controlled Dangerous Substances seized from Dennis all were deemed to be trace amounts. The weight and trace amounts were verified by First Sergeant J. Choma #5331 of the Maryland State Police. Total Weight Seized: TRACE The evidence was packaged and placed into the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack evidence storage locker.  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Dorchester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/21/2023 14:55:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 05:38:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4539</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mowbray</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7119</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501790</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 12:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>TRACKING #: 202001812261</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:38:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 14:38:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501790</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>5 3550</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 12:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>TRACKING #: 202001812272</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>5 3550</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:38:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 14:38:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501790</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 12:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #:4QV0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:41:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 14:41:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501790</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16626</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 12:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4QW0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16626</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:41:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 14:41:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501790</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 12:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4QX0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:42:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 14:42:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>47</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:43:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373684</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dennis</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/01/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.28454782E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 13:30:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dennis</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/01/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.28454782E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>D520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 13:30:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>375</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Reynolds</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>1116</SubNumber>
               <City>Alexandria</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>22304</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4521</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.130225</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.808915</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>571</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>276</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6543</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:43:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:43:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PA</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:43:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:43:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:47:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373689</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Prioleau</LastName>
               <FirstName>Carl</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kenneth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/05/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>9.1720316E7</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 14:46:30</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C640</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Prioleau</LastName>
               <FirstName>Carl</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kenneth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/05/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>9.1720316E7</SSN>
               <SLastName>P640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C640</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 14:46:30</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1632</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Valencia</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Reston</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20190</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.331388</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.960732</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>375</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Reynolds</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>1116</SubNumber>
               <City>Alexandria</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>22304</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4521</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.130225</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.808915</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>571</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>417</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9899</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:47:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:47:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:47:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:38:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 14:38:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:52:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 14:52:32</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) clear plastic bag containing a white powder substance; cociane</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246854</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.001</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:54:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 14:54:04</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) clear glass smoking device containing a burnt substance; cociane.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>100</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246855</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>MUL/COL</PrimaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 14:55:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 14:55:00</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) multicolored smoking device containing a burnt substance; cocaine.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>100</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246856</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>MUL/COL</PrimaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>