<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006263</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/17/2023 23:40:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/17/2023 23:40:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/17/2023 23:05:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/17/2023 23:05:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/CDS POSS-KIM LEON TURNER</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:40:21</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 08:21:28</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>13 SINGER,ABINGDON</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>684674</AddressId>
      <City>MDC308</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:40:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 15:08:54</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>684674</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>13</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Singer Abingdon</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.31269405</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4784717166667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/17/2023 23:40:19</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/17/2023 23:40:19</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>62</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/27/2023 07:08:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:40:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>-DUI #22-018- ***Kim Leon Turner *** TFC.R. WARBLE - ID #6762 MARYLAND STATE POLICE  JFK BARRACK M -M-43In-Car/ Body Camera Operational-  -TRAINING/CERTIFICATES- I am trained by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration to administer standardized field sobriety tests. I am certified as a RADAR/LIDAR operator through the Maryland State Police. I am a certified Preliminary Breath Test operator through the Maryland State Police. I am trained in Advanced Roadside Impairment Detection Enforcement through the Maryland State Police.In 2019, I was awarded the DUI Meritorious Recognition award by the Maryland Highway Safety Office.  -ATTACHMENTS-    MVA Printout of Suspects Information, Vehicle Information, and Criminal history  DR-15  MSP 33  Chain of Custody  Property Held Form  Statement of Charges  DR-023    CRIME:    ** Driving Veh While So Far Impaired by Drugs Cannot Drive Safely**  ** Driving Veh while Impaired by A Controlled Dangerous Substance**  ** Negligent Driving**  ** Reckless Driving**  ** Driver Failure to Obey A Properly Placed Traffic Control Device**  ** CR 5- 601 (A) (1) - ...did possess a controlled dangerous substance of schedule I to wit: Heroin/ Fentanyl.**  ** CR 5- 601 (A) (1) - ...did possess a controlled dangerous substance of schedule I to wit: Crack Cocaine.**  ** CR 5- 601 (A) (1) - ...did possess a controlled dangerous substance of schedule I to wit: Heroin/ Fentanyl. **   -DESCRIPTION OF VIOLATION / TRAFFIC STOP (VEHICLE IN MOTION)-  On February 17th 2023, I,TFC. Warble (#6762) of the Maryland State Police JFK Barrack, was on patrol operating marked police vehicle M-43.At approximately 2305 hours I was traveling in the area of Northbound Rt. 24 and Singer Rd when I observed a white Volkswagen Passat make a right turn from Northbound Rt.24 onto Singer Rd to head Westbound. At this time, I observed the Passat make a wide right turn and begin traveling Westbound in the Eastbound lanes on Singer Rd. The Passat continued for awhile on the wrong side of the road until it corrected itself and returned to its lane. The Passat then again crossed the double yellow line and began traveling Westbound Singer Rd in the Eastbound lane. The Passat then reentered the Westbound lanes due to an on coming vehicle headed Eastbound on Singer Ln. At this time, I conducted a traffic stop on the Passat on Singer Rd just prior to Rt.924.  -INITIAL CONTACT WITH DEFENDANT (PERSONAL CONTACT) - At this time, I identified myself as a Maryland State Trooper, advised the driver and sole occupant that they were being audibly and visually recorded and the reason for the stop. I then asked the driver if he had his license with him at which point he fumbled around throughout his front seat trying to find it. After approximately 5 min of the driver fumbling through his front seat he was able to find his Maryland license at which point, I positively identified the driver Kim Leon Turner (B/M/DOB: 04/04/1979). While speaking to Turner I observedhis eyes to be glassy and his pupils to be constricted (Pin point). At this time, I asked Turnerwhere he wastravelingfrom at which point headvised I spent a couple of hours at the grocery store. I then asked Turner what grocery store he was shopping at. Turner responded by saying Walgreens, I mean Redners. I proceeded to ask Turner where he was headed to at which point he responded My cousins house here in Abingdon. Throughout my interaction with Turner his movements were very slow/ lethargic and when he was speaking he continually mumbled. I then returned to my patrol vehicle and requested an additional unit. Once additional units arrived I returned to the Passat where Turner was asleep with a lit cigarette in his right hand. I then tapped on the window and asked Turner to step out of his vehicle and to walk to the front of the Passat. At this time, I advised Turner that I would be conducting the Standardized Field Sobriety Test on him to make sure he was okay to drive at which point, Turner agreed.  -STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFST) (PRE-ARREST SCREENING)-  -TESTING AREA / WEATHER CONDITIONS-  The testing area consisted of a flat, dry asphalt surface that was free of any debris or defects and the area was well illuminated. -MEDICAL PRE-SCREENING-    Have you recently had any hard hits to the head? No  Are you under the care of a doctor? Yes, Blood pressure medication   Are you under the care of a dentist? No  Do you have any physical difficulties walking in a straight line or standing on one leg? No  Have you had any major surgeries that would prohibit you from completing the test? No    -HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN)/ ZERO (0) CLUES- (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: YES)  The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explainedto Turner before he had begun the test. I asked Turnerif he understood the test and he stated, Yes. *Turnerwas told to keep his head still multiple times and to continue following with his eyes*. No clues were observedduringthis test. -WALK AND TURN (WAT)/ SIX (6) CLUES- (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: YES)   The Walk and Turn test was explainedto Turner before he had begun the test. I asked Turnerif he understood the test and he stated, Yes. *Turner was told twice prior to the test which direction I wanted him to walk* The following clues and observations were made during this test: -Cannot keep balance in the Instructional stage. -Steps off line on the first nine steps -No heel to toe on the first nine steps -Unsatisfactory turn -Takes the incorrect number of steps on last nine steps (10) -Stopped walking  -ONE LEG STAND (OLS)/ FOUR (4) CLUES- (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: YES)   The One leg stand test was explained to Turner to which he agreed he understood the test and the instructions by stating, Yes.*Turner put his foot down and was told to pick his foot back up and keep trying* -Swaying  -Puts foot down  -Raises arms for Balance  -Raises arms for balance  -PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) (Serial #:1405663 ) (SUBMITTED)-  (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: YES)  The final test offered to Turner was the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). Turner voluntarily submitted to the PBT which yielded a NEGATIVE result for the presence of alcohol and a 0.000BrAC (Breath Alcohol Concentration).  -ARREST / ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) / CERTIFIED BREATH TEST (SUBMITTED)- Due to my training, knowledge, and experience in the field of DUI / DWI related enforcement I was able to determine that Turner was impaired by the presence of drugs in his system that adversely affected his ability to perform simple tasks (i.e. Eye Examinations  Divided Attention Tests). The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety tests properly can also adversely affect the persons ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. Due to my observations, I placed Turner under arrest for driving under the influence of drugs at 2340HRS (TIME OF OBSERVATION). At approximately 2340 hours I conducted a search incident to arrest on the Passat. While searching the Passat I did not observe any contraband. At the Barrack, I read and presented Turner with the Advice of Rights form (DR-15) in English and he consentedto a certified breath test at 0026hrs. Turner confirmed his voluntary submission the breath test by signing on the Advice of Rights form.Cpl. Harten#1581of the Maryland State Police JFKBarrack M was present to administer the breath test. Turnerwas able to submit two (2) valid breath samplesat 0040hrs (0.000BrAC) and 0042hrs (0.000BrAC). At this time, I explained to Turner that he could elect to have a drug recognition expert trooper come to the barrack to perform another test to which he declined. Tfc. Mott #6918 (Certified DRE) was contact via phone and explained the details of the stop/arrest. Tfc. Mott #6918 advised that based off the phone conversation, reasonable ground of CDS impairment was present and a blood draw was authorized which Turner then refused. Please refer to Tfc.Motts supplement report for further documentation.Turner was then walked to the holding cell in the JFK barrack to wait for paperwork to be completed at which time an additional secondary search was completed in the presence of Cpl. Harten #1581. During this secondary search I located a small plastic baggie with purple powder inside, suspected Heroin/ Fentanyl in his left pant pocket. I know through my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper that the plastic baggie containing a purple power like substance is consistent with schedule I narcotic, Heroin/ Fentanyl (Weight including packaging: 7.6 grams). On 02/18/2023 at approximately 0058 hrs Cpl. Harten #1581 permitted a strip search due to the drug found on Turners person. During that strip search the following contraband was recovered from Turners buttocks:    One (1) clear baggie containing a purple like substance, Heroin/ Fentanyl (Weight including packaging: 7.4 grams)   One (1) clear baggie containing a white rock like substance, Crack Cocaine. (Weight including packaging: 28.7 grams)    I know through my training, knowledge, and experience a Maryland State Trooper that the plastic baggie containing a white rock like substance to be consistent with schedule 1 narcotic, Crack Cocaine and the plastic baggie containing a purple like substance to be consistent with schedule 1 narcotic, Heroin/ Fentanyl. I then seized the CDS and placed Turner into the holding cell to complete processing. The CDS was weighed and placed on a chain of custody and property held form (P-342065).  -THE CERTIFIED RESULTS WERE 0.00BrAC (BREATH ALCOHOL CONCENTRATION) / 0.00GRAMS OF ALCOHOL PER TWO HUNDRED AND TEN (210) LITERS OF BREATH-  At the time of his arrest, Turner mouth cavity had been checked a total of two (2) times: -On scene -Immediately entering the JFKBarrack.  -DISPOSITION OF DEFENDANT AND/OR PROPERTY - CRIMINAL AND/OR TRAFFIC CHARGES-  Turner was issued all the appropriate citations / documentation. Turnerwas instructed on Marylands Twelve (12) Hour Rule and then transported to the Harford County Detention Center.  I respectfully request this case to be closed.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 09:32:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6762</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 12:32:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harsh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Luke</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7200</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McMachan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6940</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Warble</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6762</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harten</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1581</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Warble</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6762</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Warble</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6762</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495658</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4 3550</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 23:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4 3550</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 10:56:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6762</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 10:57:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495658</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 23:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 10:56:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6762</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 10:58:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495658</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 23:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 10:56:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6762</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 11:06:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>43</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 10:56:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370002</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Turner</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kim</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leon</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/04/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 08:49:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T656</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Turner</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kim</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leon</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/04/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T656</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 08:49:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11244</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>RED LION</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>WHITE MARSH</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21162</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>317</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7718</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 11:09:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 11:09:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 11:09:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 10:56:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6762</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 10:56:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 12:02:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6762</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 12:02:21</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) plastic baggie with a purple powder substance inside, heroin/ fentanyl </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244288</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>D</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>7.6</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 12:07:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6762</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 12:07:16</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) plastic baggie containing a white rock like substance, Crack Cocaine.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244289</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>28.7</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GL</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6762</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 12:14:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6762</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 12:14:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) plastic baggie with a purple powder substance inside, heroin/ fentanyl</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244291</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>D</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>7.4</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/18/2023 04:09:14</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/18/2023 04:09:14</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/27/2023 07:08:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 04:09:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 02/18/2023, at approximately 0127 hours, I (TFC Mott #6918) was on-duty in Harford County, Maryland. I was on an incident when TFC Warble of the JFK Highway first attempted to contact me in regard to a DRE consult. Due to being on this incident, my time to respond to TFC Warble was delayed. At approximately 0153 hours, I was able to contact TFC Warble in regard to this investigation. TFC Warble advised me that he had a DUI/DWI arrest were the driver had submitted to the breath test and the results were .00 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. TFC Warble stated that this not consistent with the amount of impairment observed on scene and drug impairment was suspected. TFC Warble advised that he had completed ARIDE training. TFC Warble did state that when he offered his suspect the opportunity for a DRE evaluation, he refused. I conducted an interview of TFC Warble to determine if reasonable grounds for a blood draw were present. TFC Warble stated that he observed the following general indicators of CDS impairment:   Depressed reflexes  Droopy eyelids  drowsiness  Inability to concentrate  On the nod  Slow, low, raspy speech  Slow deliberate movements  Possession of suspected narcotics.  Based on my training, knowledge and experience as a Maryland State Trooper and certified Drug Recognition Expert, I believe reasonable grounds of CDS impairment were present. I authorized TFC Warble to offer a blood draw for CDS, which was refused. TFC Warble was provided with a DR-23 to supplement the DR-15a.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 04:14:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6918</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/26/2023 09:42:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brown</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4758</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mott</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6918</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>