<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009589</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/16/2023 19:19:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/16/2023 19:19:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/16/2023 14:23:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/16/2023 14:23:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>PWID</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 19:19:57</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2936</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 09:58:58</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>687548</AddressId>
      <City>MDC166</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 19:19:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 09:44:40</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>687548</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>12833</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Little Elliott</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
         <SubNumber>3</SubNumber>
         <City>Hagerstown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/16/2023 19:19:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/16/2023 19:19:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/18/2023 12:43:55</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 19:19:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2936</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 09:58:58</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>  On 3/13/2023 Master Trooper Hood and Sgt Roberts were conducting an investigation with Detective (USPIS TFO) Jesson and Postal Inspector Starliper regarding CDS activity in Hagerstown Maryland. On 3/14/2023, Master Trooper Hood and Sgt Roberts seized two parcels addressed to a residence in Hagerstown. The parcels were shipped from California to the address in Hagerstown. Following the investigation throughout the day, the two parcels were searched and found to contain coffee style canisters full of Marijuana. The two parcels were seized and stored on property at the Hagerstown barrack. The total weight of the Marijuana seized from the two parcels: 40 pounds. During the early evening hours of 3/14/2023 Master Trooper Hood and Sergeant Roberts contacted Detective Jesson and Inspector Starliper in regards to furthering this investigation. Master Trooper Hood and Sgt Roberts decided to conduct an interview with a subject believed to be tied to this investigation. Information was obtained on a CDS dealer that may be tied to the parcels. On 3/15/2023, Master Trooper Hood and Sgt Roberts conducted surveillance on the suspected CDS dealer. Based on the activity observed, Master Trooper Authored a search and seizure warrant for the residence of the CDS dealer. At this time they were tracking another parcel that was suspected to be arriving in Hagerstown. This was believed to be tied to the CDS dealer. On 3/16/2023, Master Trooper Hood and Sgt Roberts prepared the search warrant plan but also prepared a surveillance operation on a separate residence that was believed to be tied to this CDS dealer. Teams were split due to two different locations and the operations needing to be done at the same time. At that time Sgt Roberts, Detective Jesson, Inspector Starliper and Corporal Yates from the MSP PACE team conducted a surveillance operation at a residence in Hagerstown. As surveillance was conducted a US Postal vehicle arrived at the residence and placed parcels at the residence. A short time later Sgt Roberts observed a blue Dodge Truck pull up to the residence. Eventually two males were observed exiting the vehicle and loading two parcels into the back of the truck.  As the Dodge truck departed the area Sgt Roberts maintained constant surveillance on the vehicle observing a traffic violation. A traffic stop was conducted on the vehicle and Cpl. Yates responded to the scene in order to conduct a K-9 Scan of the vehicle. At that time Sgt Roberts coordinated with Master Trooper Hood and Detective Sergeant Martin in order to initiate the Search warrant at the CDS dealers residence. Upon receiving a positive alert a Probable Cause search was conducted on the Dodge truck. Inside of the truck a case of THC Vape cartridges were recovered along with two large parcels that contained Coffee style cans that matched the coffee cans seized on 3/14/2023. The coffee cans contained marijuana. All three individuals in the vehicle were taken into custody and transported to the Hagerstown Barrack. Master Trooper Hoods team which included Sgt Hartsock and members of the MSP State team executed the Search Warrant. Once entry was made contact was made with the main target of the investigation. The subject was identified as Jarratt Austin Moats, his girlfriend and one two juveniles. Once the scene was secured, pre-search photos were taken and Moats was advised of his Miranda rights. M/Tpr. Hood began interviewing Moats in a bedroom in reference to the case on hand. Moats advised, he was willing to help with anything he could and that was tired of doing what he was doing anyway. Moats was able to provide information pertaining to who his marijuana and marijuana by-products were coming from and the details pertaining to cost and method of obtaining the marijuana from his supplier. Moats advised, everything in the house was his and that it was all going to be in the master bedroom located in or around the closet. While M/Tpr. Hood was conducting the interviews other members of the team were conducting the search. M/Tpr. Hood asked Moats, how much marijuana he has in the bedroom and he stated a couple pounds of bud and some wax. M/Tpr. Hood then asked Moats if there was any money in the bedroom and again he replied there are like 3 or 4 bands. Moats then advised, the money was money that he had saved from working a job at Sheetz and that he was saving for a car. At this time, M/Tpr. Hood was contacted by Cpl. Mills regarding two handguns that were located in the bedroom.  One of the guns was an 80% ghost gun with no serial number and the other was a Ruger 9mm. Neither of the guns had been reported stolen, however neither of the guns were registered to Moats. M/Tpr. Hood then asked Moats about the guns and he said he purchased the Taurus 9mm at Haffers Guns located in Clear Spring last year. When asked about the ghost gun he advised, someone dropped that off here but would not advised who or where it came from. M/Tpr. Hood then told Moats that he was going to be in contact with him the following week and discuss his options and charges. Moats was then returned to the common living room area. Other members of the unit completed the search and the following items were located.  1-3.43 pounds of suspected marijuana 2-592.5 grams of suspected THC wax 3- 32 count THC vape pens 4-423.9 grams THC edibles 5-$3,470.00 US currency 6- Taurus 9mm Handgun 7. Ghost gun with drum magazine  As Master Trooper Hood concluded the search warrant he responded to the Hagerstown Barrack in order to assist with the interview of the individuals. A lengthy interview was conducted by Master Trooper Hood, Sgt Roberts, Detective Jesson and Inspector Starliper. Information was obtained in the interview that one of the individuals was storing approximately 130 pounds of marijuana in West Virginia. Sgt Roberts made contact with the Martinsburg FBI contact at the Eastern Panhandle Safe Streets Task Force. Coordination was made by Sgt Roberts with the Berkley County Sheriffs Department Narcotics Unit who are part of the Eastern panhandle Safe Streets Task Force. In coordinating with West Virginia M/T Hood, Cpl. Mills, Detective Jesson and Inspector Starliper met with members of the WV unit and the additional 130 pounds of Marijuana were seized. The Marijuana seized is believed to be high grade marijuana with a street value of $175,500.00 USD. The CDS was transported back to the Hagerstown barrack by Master Trooper Hood, Detective Jesson, Inspector Starliper and Cpl. Mills.  The Marijuana was stored at the Hagerstown Barrack. Processing of seized items from the traffic stop on the Dodge Ram revealed the following: 1- Cardboard USPS box containing metal cans with suspected marihuana- weight 13,590.5g (29.96 pounds) 2- Cardboard USPS box containing metal cans with suspected marihuana- weight 14092g (31.06 pounds) 3- Heat sealed bag of suspected marijuana-weight 494.41g (1.09 pounds) 4- One box of boring 95/5 vape cartridges-suspected THC  1220.5g (2.69 pounds) 5- One plastic container containing suspected THC edibles-weight 45 grams. 6- US Currency in the amount of $5,040.00 Processing of the items seized from the West Virginia address revealed 1. Eight extra-large contractor style black trash bags containing 129 individual heat sealed bags on Marijuana-weight 65,589.45 (144.6lbs) In Summary of the entirety of the investigation the following amounts were seized Marijuana to include THC Vape cartridges and THC Wax: 115,746.96g (255.17 pounds) US Currency: $8,510.00 Firearms: 1. Taurus 9mm Handgun 2. Ghost gun with drum magazine.  Case open pending review of Washington County States Attorney for appropriate disposition.  All the above events occurred in Washington County Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 09:47:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 09:38:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hood</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daryl</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5345</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 09:46:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372986</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Moats</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jarratt</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Austin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/19/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2023 09:45:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J630</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Moats</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jarratt</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Austin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/19/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J630</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2023 09:45:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5345</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 09:46:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/21/2023 11:37:44</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/21/2023 11:37:44</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40A</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/24/2023 09:58:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5279</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 11:37:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2936</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 09:58:58</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MOATS, JARRETT; NFD 12833 Little Eliott Dr., Apt. B, Hagerstown, MD 21742;  USPIS Case #: 4010083-PMN  $3,465.00 USC  ASSET ID #23-USP-001244  I completed an electronic Request for Adoption through the United States Postal Inspection Service (USPIS) for the $3,465.00 seized from Jarrett Moats by CED-West. Mr. Moats consented to forfeiture of the above money. Because Moats consented to the forfeiture, Maryland law requirements have been met to submit the money to the USPIS for adoption MD Criminal Procedure Article, Title 12, 212(2).  On June 1, 2023, the MSP was notified that the Adoption Request was approved. I completed an electronic DAG-71 for the above seizure requesting a % of the proceeds. The USPIS will determine the percentage that MSP receives. The DAG-71 was submitted on July 21, 2023. A supplemental report will be written documenting the disposition of the asset upon adjudication of the case. This case is suspended regarding the asset seized in this case.  M/Tpr. Logsdon - 1 hr.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5279</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 11:38:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5279</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 11:38:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40A</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Murphy</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2936</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40A</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Logsdon</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kristopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5279</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>