<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002768</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/23/2023 00:45:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/23/2023 00:45:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/23/2023 00:10:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/23/2023 00:10:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>CDS Not Cannabis</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 00:46:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/09/2023 13:37:57</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OLD TOWN RD/ CARTWRIGHT LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>681462</AddressId>
      <City>MDC162</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 00:46:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 14:46:19</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>681462</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Old Town</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Goldsboro</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.786842</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.034328</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>507-999 OLD TOWN RD / 500-599 CARTWRIGHT LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/23/2023 00:45:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/23/2023 00:45:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/09/2023 13:31:18</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 00:46:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:20:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-002768 Old Town Road @ Cartwright Lane, Goldsboro, Caroline County, MD TROOPER T. BENSON #7099 MARYLAND STATE POLICE - EASTON BARRACK  Maryland State Police (MSP) unmarked patrol vehicle I-5 is equipped with a mobile video recording device. Axon Body Worn Camera operational. Stop recorded.  Defendant(s): Name: Brandon Christopher Citro Date of Birth: 03/30/2001 MD SDX: MD-10272508774  Date of Incident: 01/23/2023 Time of Stop: 0010 hours Time of Arrest: 0022 hours  Name: William Dewilton Satterfield Sr. Date of Birth: 04/26/1974 MD SDX: S-361-887-139-320  Date of Incident: 01/23/2023 Time of Stop: 0010 hours Time of Arrest: 0027 hours  Training  Certificates: * I am trained in the detection and recognition of controlled dangerous substances through the Maryland State Police Academy. * I have successfully completed The Street-Smart Cop  Pro-Active Patrol Tactics training. * I have successfully completed Desert Snow Criminal, Narcotics,  Terrorist Interdiction training. * I have successfully completed Maryland Top Gun: Investigating  Prosecuting Drug Cases training. * I have successfully completed Maryland State Police Conducting the Complete Traffic Stop: Criminal Interdiction training.  Narrative: On Monday, January 23, 2022, at approximately 0010 hours, I, TFC. Benson #7099, was operating Maryland State Police (MSP) unmarked patrol vehicle I-5 in the area of Greensboro Road and Bridgetown Road in Goldsboro, Caroline County, MD. At this time, I observed a green Ford Ranger, bearing MD registration traveling north on Greensboro Road. As I traveled behind the vehicle, I was unable to read the entire registration plate due to the hitch ball attached to the rear bumper of the vehicle; one (1) number on the registration plate was covered by the hitch ball. Traveling behind the vehicle I could only see 2DL-887. The vehicle also had clear plastic covering the rear window of the vehicle and was being operated without the required safety class equipment. At this time, I activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle came to a stop in the parking lot of the Goldsboro Town Hall and Post Office, located at 505 Oldtown Road, Goldsboro, Caroline County, MD. I made contact with the driver and passenger of the vehicle at the drivers side window. Upon contact with the occupants, the driver was identified by his MD drivers license as William Dewilton Satterfield Sr., DOB: 04/26/1974, 2/M, and the passenger was identified by his MD drivers license as Brandon Christopher Citro, DOB: 03/30/2001, 2/M. As I approached the vehicle, Satterfield turned his body around and was leaning out the drivers window prior to me making contact with him. As we spoke, Satterfield bladed his body towards me blocking my view inside the vehicle. I observed a butane lighter on the floor of the truck at Satterfields feet. Satterfield stated his license was expired and that the truck was not registered to him or Citro, stating it was his fathers vehicle. Satterfield stated he was driving Citro home after he had helped him with some work. I know Satterfield to be a Controlled Dangerous Substance (CDS) user and have had previous interaction. At this time, I requested the services of Denton Police Department K-9 Unit to respond and conduct a free air sniff of the vehicle.  At this time, TFC. Fisher made a second approach to the passenger side of the vehicle and made contact with Citro. TFC. Fisher observed Citro digging in his pants as he made contact with the occupants at the passenger side window. Citro was asked to exit the vehicle, to which he agreed, while license and wanted checks were being conducted through the MSP Easton Barrack. Wanted check revealed Citro to be wanted through MSP for Manslaughter and CDS Charges (Warrant #: D220126524  Tracking #: 221001868113). Citro was detained at approximately 0019 hours. Search incident to arrest of Citros person located the following that I recognized and suspected through my training, knowledge, and experience to be controlled dangerous substances (CDS):    margin-bottom:8px; margin-left:8px"&gt;One (1) plastic baggie containing suspected Cocaine residue (P-343333 - Item B).   margin-bottom:8px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Two (2) clear gel capsules containing suspected Heroin  Fentanyl residue (P-343333  Item D).   margin-bottom:8px; margin-left:8px"&gt;One (1) glass smoking device containing suspected Crack Cocaine residue (P-343333  Item E).  The above listed items were located inside the front left pocket of Citros shorts, underneath his sweatpants. Citro was subsequently placed under arrest for CDS: POSSESS-NOT CANNABIS and CDS: POSS PARAPHERNALIA at approximately 0022 hours. As a result, a probable cause search of the vehicle was conducted which located the following that I recognized and suspected through my training, knowledge, and experience to be controlled dangerous substances (CDS):     margin-bottom:8px; margin-left:8px"&gt;One (1) plastic baggie containing suspected Cocaine (P-343333  Item A). Total weight: 27.7 grams. Located inside black backpack sitting at the base of front passenger seat.   margin-bottom:8px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Four (4) plastic bags containing suspected Cocaine residue (P-343333  Item C). Located inside black backpack sitting at the base of front passenger seat.   margin-bottom:8px; margin-left:8px"&gt;One (1) ripped plastic baggie containing suspected Heroin  Fentanyl residue (P-343332  Item A). Located on the floor of the vehicle at the base of the drive seat.   Satterfield was placed under arrest at approximately 0027 hours. Citro and Satterfield were both advised and read their Miranda Rights, to which they both voluntarily agreed to waive at approximately 0038 hours. Citro took possession of both items located inside the black backpack (Item A  Item C), stating the backpack was his and the items did not belong to Satterfield. Satterfield did not take possession of the ripped baggie located on the floor of the driver seat, in the area of the butane lighter, where he was sitting. The vehicle was towed from the scene by Knotts Towing. Citro and Satterfield were transported to the Caroline County Sheriff Office for fingerprinting and processing. Satterfield was issued a Criminal Citation (#: 142003404130) for CDS: POSS PARAPHERNALIA released on his own recognizance at approximately 0146 hours. Citro was interviewed by Caroline County Drug Task Force and brought before the District Court Commissioner via video conference. Citro was Held No Bond and transported to the Caroline County Detention Center where he was released to there care and custody at approximately 0450 hours. Search of his person at the Detention Center revealed the following that I recognized and suspected through my training, knowledge, and experience to be controlled dangerous substances (CDS) hidden in Citros sock:     margin-bottom:8px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Two (2) clear gel capsules containing suspected Heroin  Fentanyl (P-343333  Item F).   margin-bottom:8px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Two (2) blue wax folds with markings BUSTED OUT containing suspected Heroin  Fentanyl (P-343333  Item G). Total weight: 0.6 grams.   margin-bottom:8px; margin-left:8px"&gt;One (1) plastic baggie containing suspected Crack Cocaine (P-343333  Item H). Total weight: 0.4 grams.   margin-bottom:8px; margin-left:8px"&gt;One (1) purple cut plastic straw containing suspected Heroin  Fentanyl residue (P-343333  Item I).  The CDS was transported to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack where it was processed according to policy and procedure. I have received training in the detection and recognition of controlled dangerous substances in the Maryland State Police Academy.  RESQUEST THIS CASE CLOSED BY ARREST.  ALL EVENTS OCCURRED IN CAROLINE COUNTY, MD.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 19:01:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 19:01:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fisher</LastName>
            <FirstName>Rodney</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Walker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7010</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4539</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Benson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492151</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/23/2023 00:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 14:48:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 14:48:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492151</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>5 3550</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/23/2023 00:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>5 3550</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 14:48:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 14:48:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>48</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:01:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>310768</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Satterfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>William</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dewilton</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/26/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18177024E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/19/2021 17:43:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S361</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W450</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Satterfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>William</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dewilton</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/26/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18177024E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S361</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W450</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/19/2021 17:43:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9774</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Foy</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Denton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21629</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.805755</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.876466</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>829</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2249</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:01:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:01:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:01:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>C</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:13:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>363721</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>CITRO</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRANDON</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>C</MiddleName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/19/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C360</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>CITRO</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRANDON</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/19/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C360</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Citro</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christopher</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/30/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.20596359E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>12/15/2022 11:04:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C360</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>CITRO</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRANDON</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>C</MiddleName>
               <SLastName>C360</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/19/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>CITRO</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRANDON</FirstName>
               <SLastName>C360</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/19/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Citro</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christopher</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/30/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.20596359E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>C360</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/15/2022 11:04:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>16638</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Henderson</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Henderson</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21640</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1633</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.771953</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.063863</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>302</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>331</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3967</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:13:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PA</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:13:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:13:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 14:48:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 14:48:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:09</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Ripped plastic baggie containing suspected Heroin &amp; Fentanyl residue</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242953</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>D</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:09</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Baggie containing suspected cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242954</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>27.7</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Ziploc bag containing suspected Cocaine residue</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242955</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Plastic baggies containing suspected Cocaine residue</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242956</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>4</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Gel capsules containing suspected Heroin &amp; Fentanyl residue</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242957</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>D</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>2</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Gel capsules containing suspected Heroin &amp; Fentanyl.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242958</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>D</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>2</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Two (2) blue wax folds with markings "BUSTED OUT" containing suspected Heroin &amp; Fentanyl</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242959</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>D</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.6</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:11</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) baggie containing suspected Crack Cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242960</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.4</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 15:43:11</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Cut purple plastic straw containing suspected Heroin &amp; Fentanyl residue</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242961</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>D</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:44:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 15:44:20</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Glass smoking device containing suspected Crack Cocaine residue.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>100</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242962</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>