<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-026684</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/27/2023 19:52:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/27/2023 19:52:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/27/2023 15:01:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/27/2023 15:01:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Missing Person report in Walkersville, MD.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 19:53:01</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3033</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/04/2023 13:05:49</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>42227</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>512</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 19:53:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/27/2023 19:54:09</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>42227</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>21</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>FREDERICK</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>WALKERSVILLE</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>512</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-77.35051546228753</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.48160731520575</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WALKERSVILLE TOWN OFFICE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/27/2023 19:52:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/27/2023 19:52:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>07/27/2023 21:05:22</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 19:53:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5824</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 10:25:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>**CAR B-66//IN-CAR CAMERA NOT AVAILABLE//BODY-WORN CAMERA AVAILABLE**  ATTACHMENTS: - MVA Printouts -Missing Persons Report   VICTIM(S): Name: Amanda Christine Eyler (DOB 11/19/1995) (**MISSING PERSON**) Last Known Address: 731 Heather Ridge Drive Unit H, Frederick, Maryland 21702 Phone #301-800-4534 (Carrier: Unknown) Height: 507 Weight: 200 Scars, Marks, Tattoos: Birthmark on inside upper arm, unknown which arm  COMPLAINANT(S): Name: Marlene Louise Eyler (DOB 04/09/1951) (**Aunt of Missing Person**) 500 Chapel Court Apartment 105 Walkersville, Maryland 21793 Phone #: 301-606-3564  WITNESS / NEIGHBORHOOD CHECKS: Due to the report being filed several months after the person went missing, a K-9 and helicopter were not called to the scene.  SUSPECT(S):   Not applicable.   SCENE PROCESSING: Information regarding the missing person (Juvenile) gathered with the complainant of the missing at the Walkersville Town Hall, located at 21 West Frederick Street in Walkersville, Frederick County, Maryland. I gathered all pertinent information and documents related to this case. See narrative in report for further investigation.  NARRATIVE:  On 07/27/2023, at approximately 1501 hours, I (TFC J. Blumenauer #6357) of the Maryland State Police Frederick Barrack, responded to the Walkersville Town Hall located at 21 West Frederick Street in Walkersville, Frederick County, Maryland for a report of a missing person. At 1502 hours, I met with the 911 caller, and complainant, who was identified by her Maryland drivers license as Marlene Louise Eyler (DOB 04/09/1951). It should be noted, Eyler resides at 500 Chapel Court Apartment 105 in Walkersville. Eyler advised she wanted to report her niece missing, and was reporting her on behalf of the entire family. Eyler identified her missing niece as Amanda Christine Eyler (DOB 11/19/1995), who was later identified by her Maryland drivers license photograph. While speaking with Marlene, she advised her family had not heard from Amanda since late April and early May of 2023. Marlene advised she has not personally talked to Amanda in over two (2) years. Marlene advised the last person who had heard from Amanda was Amandas mother, identified by her Maryland drivers license as Velma Grace Eyler (DOB 01/19/1960). Marlene advised Velma last heard from Amanda by text message on 05/02/2023, and had last seen Amanda in person on April 28th, 2023. Marlene advised Amanda was last seen by Velma at Amandas most recent residence, located a 731 Heather Ridge Drive Unit H in Frederick, Maryland. Marlene advised Amanda has not resided at the Heather Ridge address since November of 2021. Marlene advised Amanda used to stop by the address because her oldest daughter, and the father of the child reside with her parents at that address. Marlene provided the identities of the parties residing at the address. Amandas mother was identified by her Maryland drivers license as Velma Grace Eyler (DOB 01/19/1960), and Amandas father was identified by his Maryland drivers license as Charles Wayne Eyler (DOB 04/20/1962).  Marlene advised that Amanda has an infant child (boy), named Amari Darnell McRoy/Eyler (DOB 01/22/2023). Marlene advised Amari is a foster child of the Frederick County Child Protective Services (CPS). Marlene advised the case worker for Amari from CPS is Carla. Marlene advised that CPS contacted her other niece, and the half-sister of Amanda, identified by her Maryland drivers license as Sara Lynn Eyler (DOB 07/20/1984), regarding custody of Amari. Marlene advised approximately one (1) week ago, CPS spoke with Sara and inquired if she would foster Amari for a period of at least two (2) years, eventually leading towards adoption of the child. Marlene advised that CPS could not get a hold of Amanda, and did not know her whereabouts since the date of April 28th, 2023.  Marlene advised she is concerned of Amandas welfare because Amanda is a known drug addict. Marlene advised Amanda has been a drug user of heroin and fentanyl for the last 1-1.5 years. Marlene advised she did not know what Amanda was last seen wearing. Marlene described Amanda as a white female, with brown hair, brown eyes, 57 tall, and weighs 200 pounds. Marlene advised Amanda has a chip on one of her front teeth, and her teeth might be rotting. Marlene advised Amanda did not go to the dentist, so she would not have access to any dental records. Marlene advised Amanda did not have any medical conditions, and did not take any medications. Marlene provided a phone number of #301-800-4534 for Amanda. Marlene advised she did not the carrier for Amandas cell phone. Marlene advised the family will attempt to contact Amanda by telephone approximately two (2) times a day since her disappearance to check her welfare. Marlene advised the family will call in the morning hours, and Amandas phone will ring and no one will answer. Marlene advised when the family calls in the evening hours, the call will go right to voicemail, indicating the phone is powered off, or the call was declined. Marlene advised Amanda did not have a vehicle, as her vehicle was repossessed in Baltimore County previously in the beginning of 2023. Marlene advised Amanda has a birthmark on the inside of her upper arm (unknown which arm). Marlene advised she believe that Amanda would be in the company of her current boyfriend, identified by his Maryland drivers license as Lamar Dominique McRoy (DOB 08/07/1989). It should noted, both Lamar and Amanda were currently wanted, with an active arrest warrant for drug charges by the Frederick City Police Department, as of 07/18/2023 (Amanda) and 07/19/2023 (Lamar).  While speaking with Marlene, it was also determined that Amandas half-brother, identified by his Maryland drivers license as Joshua Wayne Eyler (DOB 10/22/1985), last heard from Amanda by text message on May 9th, 2023. At approximately 1545 hours, Cpl. Conklin #5549, contacted Joshua by telephone (#240-440-0813) in reference to this case. Joshua advised Cpl. Conklin that he believed Amanda was with her boyfriend Lamar, and was currently staying at Lamars mothers residence in Montgomery County, Maryland. Marlene identified Lamars mother as Chiffon Christine McRoy (DOB 02/12/1969), later identified by her Maryland drivers license. Chiffons most recent address was listed as 425 North Frederick Avenue Apartment 3A, in Gaithersburg, Montgomery County, Maryland.  At 1906 hours, S/TPR Quase #6306, and TFC Linn #7281, of the Maryland State Police Rockville Barrack responded to the 425 North Frederick Avenue in Gaithersburg, in an attempt to locate Amanda. At this time, they made contact with Chiffon, who advised Lamar was currently in custody of the Baltimore Police Department, as of 07/21/2023. Chiffon also advised Troopers that Amanda was currently located at the Nuwave Health Services, located at the Falls Lane Medical Center. The address is 4419 Falls Rd, Baltimore, MD 21211, and the phone number provided was (443) 869-5522. At 1910 hours, I attempted to call the Nuwave Health Service on four (4) occasions with negative results.   All the above events occurred in Frederick County, Maryland.   CHARGES: - Not applicable.   CASE STATUS: Case open, pending follow-ups.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 20:38:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/27/2023 20:38:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1652</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Blumenauer</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6357</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516129</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>MP1000</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/27/2023 15:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>MP1000</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 19:55:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/27/2023 19:55:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 20:00:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383636</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>EYLER</LastName>
               <FirstName>AMANDA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>CHRISTINE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/19/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/27/2023 19:59:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A553</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>EYLER</LastName>
               <FirstName>AMANDA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>CHRISTINE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/19/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>E460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A553</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/27/2023 19:59:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>731</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Heather Ridge</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>UNIT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>H</SubNumber>
               <City>Frederick</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21702</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.415279</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.440679</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>800</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4534</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 20:00:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>72</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 20:01:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383027</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Eyler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Marlene</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LOUISE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/09/1951 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/20/2023 05:07:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M645</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Eyler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Marlene</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LOUISE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/09/1951 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>E460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M645</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/20/2023 05:07:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>500</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Chapel</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>Unit 105</SubNumber>
               <City>Walkersville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21793</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.341727</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.484771</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>606</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3564</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 20:01:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>R</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 20:01:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 20:01:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/31/2023 15:55:09</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/31/2023 15:55:09</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/01/2023 10:25:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 15:55:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5824</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 10:25:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>NARRATIVE: On 07/27/2023, at 2128 hours, PCO Greenwood of Maryland State Police Frederick Barrack entered Eyler as a missing person into NCIC. It should be noted, the NIC number isM927449001. A copy of the NCIC missing person page was added to the attachments section of this report.  On 07/28/2023, at 1500 hours, Marlene Eyler contacted the MSP Frederick Barrack dispatch regarding this case. PCS Murphy of the MSP Frederick Barrack advised that Marlene Eyler wanted to update the Maryland State Police, and informed PCS Murphy that Amanda Eyler was located in the Nuwave rehabilitation facility in Baltimore, Maryland.  On 07/31/2023, at approximately 1230 hours, I responded to the Walkersville Town Hall at 21 West Frederick Street in Walkersville, and made in-person contact with the complainant, Marlene Eyler. While speaking with Marlene, she advised that the family was going to respond to Nuwave, and make contact with Amanda Eyler. Marlene also advised that Joshua Eyler spoke with the wife of the owner of Nuwave, and confirmed Amanda was staying at the facility. Marlene advised me that Joshua was going to see Amanda later in the day on 07/31/2023, to check her welfare and also to bring her essential clothing and additional food.  On 08/01/2023, at 0940 hours, I contacted Marlene Eyler by telephone for an update in this case. While speaking with Marlene, she me that advised Joshua made in-person contact with Amanda on 07/31/2023, at Nuwave. Marlene advised that Amanda was located safe, and unharmed at Nuwave rehabilitation facility. Marlene advised that she and her family is satisfied with the assistance of police, and wishes to have Amanda removed from NCIC as missing. It should be noted, Marlene advised that Amanda was at Nuwave voluntarily and on her own accord. It should also be noted, the reasons for Amandas disappearance are unknown, and her activities while missing are unknown. Due to Amanda being under medical care at the Nuwave facility, an exit interview will not be practical, and will not be conducted.   CASE STATUS: Subject located safe and unharmed, case closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 15:56:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 10:24:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bonneville</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5824</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Blumenauer</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6357</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>