<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-023252</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/28/2023 17:30:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/28/2023 17:30:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/28/2023 17:19:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/28/2023 17:19:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>MSP BK G DUI 23-107, TA 21-902D1 &amp; CR 5-601A1 CDS: possess not cannabis (REBECCA MOORE BARLOW)</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/28/2023 17:30:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 14:16:06</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BALTIMORE BLVD/ SANDYMOUNT RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>76654</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/28/2023 17:30:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/13/2023 13:46:41</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>76654</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Baltimore</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Finksburg</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21048</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.92165</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.52582</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2100-2118 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2101-2370 SANDYMOUNT RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2088-2098 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2100-2371 SANDYMOUNT RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2130-2272 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2096-2105 SANDYMOUNT RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2101-2119 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2005-2017 SANDYMOUNT RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2100-2118 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2096-2105 SANDYMOUNT RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2120-2284 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2096-2105 SANDYMOUNT RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2089-2101 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2000-2099 SANDYMOUNT RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/28/2023 17:30:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/28/2023 17:30:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/16/2023 08:32:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/28/2023 17:30:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23MSP023252  Incident: traffic collision  MSP Barrack G DUI 23-107 (REBECCA MOORE BARLOW)  TA 21-902(D)(1)i, CR 5-601A1 CDS: possess not cannabis  Date/ Time: 06/28/2023, 1715 hours  Location of Offense: W/B MD 140, E/O Sandymount Rd, Finksburg, Carroll County, MD.  My investigation was recorded on AXON digital recording system assigned to G-39 and AXON body camera assigned to M/Tpr Fair.  Minors in Vehicle:NO  PBT: N/A  EVIDENTIARY TEST: Refused at 1908 hours  DRE (Drug Recognition Expert): N/A  Weather: clear, approximately 78 degrees Fahrenheit  Qualifications:  -Maryland State Police Academy (June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007)  -I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through NHTSA and the Maryland State Police (MSP Academy, June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007).  -I have attended and graduated from the University of Maryland University College Advanced DUI College (UMUC January 7-11, 2013).  -Street Narcotics Investigation for Road Patrol (MPCTC, 05/22/2015)  -I have attended and completed training Enhanced DUI Enforcement: The Complete Arrest (MPCTC, 05/11/2016).  -A.R.I.D.E.: Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (MPCTC, 03/29-03/30/2017)  -Cannabis Impairment Detection Workshop (MPCTC, 09/29/2021)  CDS:  Upon my arrival on scene, I observed the following:  A. oneblue oval pill, inscribed Y, 20,identified through my training and experience with the Maryland State Police, and confirmed by drug.com pill identifier to be alprazolam, a Controlled Dangerous Substance of Schedule 4. The pill was located in plain sight on the drivers seat.The pill was subsequently seized and documented on MSP Form 67, and 63 (P-323302), and submitted to the MSP Westminster Barrack evidence locker in accordance to MSP policy and procedures.  Driver/ Defendant: MD DL B640734609072 REBECCA MOORE BARLOW 127 STONER AVE WESTMINSTER, MD 21157 2/F, DOB 01/27/1976 410-591-6549  Witnesses:  1. John Davis, 410-977-1820  Davis was behind the vehicle the defendant was driving (Chevy SUV, MD tag 9ES8433) and observed it collide into to the rear of another vehicle that was stopped due to traffic conditions, never touching the brakes. Davis advised he saw two people, possible male and female exit the Chevy, and flee the scene on foot.  2. Arabella Estrada, 301-642-8724  Estrada was operating the lead vehicle of the three car collision (vehicle 3, Mercedes Benz), and was struck in the rear by the vehicle 2, after vehicle 2 was struck in the rear by vehicle 1 (Chevy SUV).  3. Tiffany Estrada  Witness 3 is the daughter of witness 2. Witness three was seated in the front passenger seat of vehicle 3. Witness 3 observed a white female wearing a tank top and shorts, and a white male flee vehicle 1, believing the female was the operator of vehicle 1.  4. Dimitry Mitin, 302-588-7321  Mitin was the operator and sole occupant of vehicle 2. Mitin advised he was stopped due to traffic, then was struck in the rear by vehicle 1. Mitin was in extreme discomfort at the time and unable to provide further at this time.  Phase I: Reason for Contact  On 06/28/2023 at approximately 1719 hours I was on duty, in uniform, operating a marked Maryland State Police Patrol vehicle, G-39. I was traveling W/B MD 140, E/O Sandymount Rd, Finksburg, Carroll County, MD, when I came upon a three vehicle traffic collision that occurred moments before. The three vehicles were a Chevy SUV displaying MD tag 9ES8433 (vehicle 1, heavy front end damage, all airbags deployed), a Ford Transit cargo van displaying MD tag 8EP2052 (vehicle 2, rear end damage), and a black Mercedes Benz displaying MD tag 9CK4630 (vehicle 3, superficial damage to the rear). Through my investigation, I was able to determine the following course of events: vehicle 1 collided into the rear of vehicle 2, and vehicle 2 was pushed into the rear of vehicle 3. These events occurred W/B MD 140, E/O Sandymount Rd, Finksburg, Carroll County, MD, in lane 1 (left lane of travel). The occupants (driver and front passenger) fled the scene on foot.  Upon my arrival on scene, I had checked the Chevy SUV for occupants. The vehicle was unoccupied, but I did observe a blue oval pill, inscribed Y, 20 on the drivers seat, in plain view. I was able to utilize the drug.com website pill identifier to identify the pill as alprazolam (a Controlled Dangerous Substance of Schedule 4). I know alprazolam to be a Controlled Dangerous Substance of Schedule 4 through my training and experience with the Maryland State Police. The pill was subsequently seized and documented on MSP Form 67, and 63 (P-323302), and submitted to the MSP Westminster Barrack evidence locker in accordance to MSP policy and procedures.  MSP Westminster dispatch advised a white male with dark hair and beard, wearing a gray shirt, black backpack, and a white female with an orangish/ pink top and backpack were observed leaving the scene, walking through a yard and woods, toward Clydesdale Rd, Finksburg, Carroll County, MD. These subject were subsequently located in front of 2413 Appaloosa Way, Finksburg, Carroll County, MD, by Deputy Metzler of the Carroll County Sherriffs Office, detained and handcuffed after attempting to flee the scene of the collision, and advised of their rights by the Miranda warning. I responded to that location and made contact with the subjects and Deputy Metzler. I was advised by Deputy Metzler, that the subjects waived their rights, and agreed to answer questions without consulting an attorney at this time. The weather was partly cloudy and approximately 78 degrees Fahrenheit.   Phase II: Contact  I identified myself, advised the contact was being recorded, and advised the reason for the contact. I made contact with the female subject first, who was identified by name and subsequent MVA photo comparison to be REBECCA MOORE BARLOW. I asked BARLOW what happened. BARLOW stated to me that she was driving, saw the brake lights of the vehicle in front of her too late, and crashed into the rear of the vehicle. BARLOW stated she got scared and ran due to her license to drive being suspended. I asked BARLOW when she last used any Controlled Dangerous Substances or medications. BARLOW advised she last used yesterday/ last night (06/27/2023). I asked what medications she is on, BARLOW advised last night she took clonidine (sedative and antihypertension medication), Abilify (antidepressant), and gabapentin (anticonvulsant and nerve pain medication). BARLOW denied consuming any other drugs, medications, or CDS. The male subject was identified by MVA photo comparison and name and date of birth to be EDWARD THERMAN BAILEY, DOB 02/26/1984. BAILEY also advised BARLOW was the driver of vehicle 1.  While speaking with BARLOW, I made the following observations:  -pupils pinpoint -eyes glassy -eyelids droopy -arms and legs covered in scabs and pick marks -left foot and ankle beginning to swell  Based on my observations of BARLOW, and the totality of the circumstances (traffic collision, fleeing the scene, and CDS located on the scene on the drivers seat of vehicle 1), I made the decision to administer the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  Phase III: Pre-Arrest Screening  All tests were explained and demonstrated prior to asking the driver to attempt them. The driver was wearing a pink t-shirt, tan shorts, and was barefoot. The driver denied needing or using glasses or contact lenses. The driver did advise her left foot and ankle was causing her great pain and discomfort.  SFSTs:All tests were explained and demonstrated prior to me asking the driver to attempt them.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus:  I conducted this test with the driver seated. The drivers eyes displayed equal pupil size (pinpoint), tracking, and reaction. I was able to observe 6 clues out of the 6 potential clues:  -both eyes lacked smooth pursuit -distinct nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes -onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degree deviation in both eyes  Additional observations:  -eyes glassy -pupils pinpoint  Vertical Nystagmus was observed.  Walk  Turn:unable to due to the injury to her left foot/ ankle.  Additional observations:  -eyes glassy -pupils pinpoint  One Leg Stand:unable to do due to the injury to her left foot/ ankle.  Additional observations:  -eyes glassy -pupils pinpoint  Additional Tests: A.R.I.D.E.  Lack of Convergence:  The lack of convergence was observed: right eye diverged from center.  Additional observations:  -eyes glassy -pinpoint pupils  Finger To Nose: Not conducted.  Modified Romberg:  The driver was placed in modified the instructional position due to her being handcuffed to her front (having been detained and handcuffed by TFC Neild and Deputy Metzler after being located after fleeing the collision scene on foot): standing as best able with her heels together. The driver was instructed when I would tell them to do so, to close their eyes, tilt their head back and estimate the passage of 30 seconds by counting quietly to themselves. After the passage of 30 seconds, the driver was instructed to bring their head down, open their eyes and say done.  Observations:  -during the test, the driver leaned to her right to compensate for the injured ankle/ foot -the driver took 21 seconds (according to the digital recording) to estimate the passage of 30 seconds -mouth open/ slack  Based on my observations of the driver during contact and the SFSTs, as well as the totality of the circumstances, I made the decision to place the driver under arrest for DUI and the CDS that was found on the drivers seat of vehicle 1. The driver was advised she was under arrest for the DUI and CDS. Nothing of evidentiary value was located in the backpack the driver had on when she was detained. EMS was on scene, and the driver declined medical assistance at this time. The driver was already handcuffed and placed in my patrol vehicle, and transported to the MSP Westminster Barrack.  Upon arrival, the driver began to complain that her left foot/ ankle was causing her more and more discomfort. The driver was read the DR15 Advice of Rights at 1858 hours. The driver signed the DR15 at 1908 hours, refusing any further testing. Due to the swelling increasing, and the obvious discomfort of BARLOW, I transported her to Carroll Hospital Center Emergency Room. BARLOW was issued the DR15, DR15A, Notice to Appear, Notice to Right of Counsel, a criminal citation for the CDS charge, and traffic citations LWX0DJH-LXF0DJH. The driver was released to the care of CHC ER staff.  All events occurred in Carroll County, MD.  Case closed on citations. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 09:34:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/15/2023 08:34:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eyler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0670</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nield</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6851</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>512689</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/28/2023 17:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 13:55:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/13/2023 13:55:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>512689</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/28/2023 17:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 13:57:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/13/2023 13:57:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>47</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 14:18:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:02</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382420</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>BARLOW</LastName>
               <FirstName>REBECCA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MOORE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1976 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/13/2023 14:16:02</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R120</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>BARLOW</LastName>
               <FirstName>REBECCA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MOORE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1976 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R120</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/13/2023 14:16:02</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>127</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Stoner</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21157</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.986893</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.55871</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 14:18:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 14:18:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 14:18:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 14:18:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>50</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 11:46:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382504</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>MITIN</LastName>
               <FirstName>DIMITRY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>SERGEEVICH</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/15/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/14/2023 11:46:26</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D536</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>MITIN</LastName>
               <FirstName>DIMITRY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>SERGEEVICH</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/15/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D536</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/14/2023 11:46:26</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>479</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Silver</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21158</Zip5>
               <Zip4>9405</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.017165</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.577545</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>302</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>588</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7371</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 11:46:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>54</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 11:50:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:23</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382505</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>ESTRADA</LastName>
               <FirstName>ARABELLA</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/05/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/14/2023 11:49:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A614</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>ESTRADA</LastName>
               <FirstName>ARABELLA</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/05/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>E236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A614</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/14/2023 11:49:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>733</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Uniontown</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21158</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.023595</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.580388</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>642</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8724</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 11:50:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 11:54:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:23</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382507</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>DAVIS</LastName>
               <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/14/2023 11:54:25</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>DAVIS</LastName>
               <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
               <SLastName>D120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/14/2023 11:54:25</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2950</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Industrial Park</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Finksburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21048</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2338</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.886362</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.499763</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>977</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1820</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 11:54:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 13:55:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/13/2023 13:55:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>135554</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 15:04:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/13/2023 15:04:00</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/04/2022 11:36:07</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>02/04/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>KL7CJMSB0MB349043</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2021</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>LL</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>MAR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>MAR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>MAR</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>MAR</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9ES8433</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9ES8433</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehConditionCode>G</VehConditionCode>
         <VehDamageCode>0</VehDamageCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 14:31:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/13/2023 14:31:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One oval blue pill, inscribed "Y, 20," suspected alprazolam</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>251719</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>O</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/15/2023 16:35:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/15/2023 16:35:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/16/2023 08:32:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 16:35:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Traffic collision added in the attachments.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 16:38:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/15/2023 16:38:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>