<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025680</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/18/2023 16:21:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/18/2023 16:21:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/18/2023 15:15:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/18/2023 15:15:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Two suspects entered Coppermine 4 seasons gym and stole misc items as well as the keys to the facility.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 16:21:42</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6579</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 02:05:24</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>BRG</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>THT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>46499</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>563</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 16:21:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 17:00:43</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>46499</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2710</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>HAMPSTEAD MEXICO</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>HAMPSTEAD</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>563</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-76.89996262905439</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.60893058502143</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FOUR SEASONS SPORTS COMPLEX</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IFO  FOUR SEASONS SPORTS COMPLEX</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/18/2023 16:21:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/18/2023 16:21:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/01/2023 08:03:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 16:21:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6579</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 02:05:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP issued BWC fully operational at time of incident.  Scene Processing:   Two suspects entered the Coppermine 4 Seasons Recreational Center after hours, and stole one pair of sunglasses. Both suspects appeared to be Juveniles, and were wearing masks. The female suspect took a pair of sunglasses from the shop and then both suspects left the scene. The manager of Coppermine has surveillance video of the theft, however, they were not able to provide a copy of the video to me that day. I took two digital photographs of the suspects from the surveillance video which are attached to this report. I conducted a neighborhood check of nearby houses to see if the suspects lived nearby, with no results.  Attachments: 1) Two digital photographs of both suspects.  Stolen Property: 1) One pair of Goodr sunglasses. Value $25.00 USD  Narrative:   On 07/18/2023 at approximately 1515 hours, I (TFC J. Reid #7215) responded to 2710 Hampstead Mexico Rd, Hampstead, MD 21074, the Coppermine 4 Seasons Recreational Center, for the report of a theft.   Upon my arrival, I made contact with Coppermines general manager, Jesseca Marie Dannettel (W/F DOB: 09/12/1980).Dannettel advised on 7/17/2023 at approximately 0200 hours, two suspects broke into Coppermine and stole a pair of Goodr sunglasses from their shop, and stole the master keys to the entire recreational center.Dannettel stated she did not notice anything had been stolen on 7/17/2023, however, when she was looking for the keys today, she could not find them. She advised the evening shift is supposed to leave the master keys on the lobby front desk so they are easy to find for the morning shift.Dannettel advised when the keys were not on the front desk in the morning, she checked the video surveillance footage to see who had the keys, and then she saw two individuals with masks and flashlights enter the lobby from a stairwell that leads downstairs. She stated the suspects can be seen on camera attempting to get into the cash register of their store, and attempting to tamper with the facilityssecurity system.Dannettel advised the suspects are seen entering a small clothing store across from the front desk.Dannettel advised one of the suspects stole a pair of sunglasses off the sunglass rack.Dannettel stated the suspects then exited the sore, took the keys to the facility and go back down the stairwell they were originally seen coming up.Dannettel advised the suspects did not appear on the lobby camera again. I askedDannettel if there were any additional cameras in the parking lots or at the entrances, however, she advised the only cameras they have are in the lobby, and store area.Dannettel just prior to the suspects entering the lobby, she advised a cleaning lady was mopping the floor, and cleaning the facility.Dannettel advised the cleaning lady usually leaves the back door of the gym open so she can easily take trash and other cleaning supplies in and out.Dannettel speculated that while the cleaning lady was in the lobby cleaning, the two suspects snuck into the facility and hid until the cleaning lady left for the night.    I reviewed the video surveillance footage and observed two suspects enter the lobby at approximately 0202 hours. Suspect number one (1) is a white male, medium build with no shirt, a bandana covering the lower half of his face, medium length hair that comes down to his eyes, glasses, dark colored pants with rips in them, and dark colored shoes with white trim. Suspect number two (2), appears to be a white female wearing a dark colored Under Armor hoodie with the hood up, a mask on, and short athletic shorts, skinny build. Both suspects appear to be in their late teens or early twenties. Both suspects enter the store across from the front desk at approximately 0204 hours. Suspect number two (2) is seen on video surveillance taking a pair of sunglasses from the sunglass rack, and putting them on. Suspect number one (1) is seen going around to the cash register and appearing as if he is trying to figure out how to open it. After several seconds of unsuccessfully getting into the cash register, both suspects exit the store at approximately 0205 hours. Both suspects are seen on the lobby camera again and slowly start walking back down the stairs the originally came up. Neither suspect is seen on video surveillance again. I askedDannettel if she has ever seen the suspects before, she stated, No. I asked two of the other employees at Coppermine if they had ever seen the suspects before, and they stated they have not. I took a digital photograph of both suspects from the surveillance video which are attached to this report.   I providedDannettel with the case number, barrack contact information, and reccommended they invest in higher security measures.   I conducted a neighborhood check of houses within the immediate vicinity to see if the suspects were local residence, however, nobody that I spoke to recognized either individual, and nobody reported to have seen anything.   All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.   I request this case be suspended due to no additional leads or suspect information.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 17:17:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 19:36:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Karas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5562</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reid</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7215</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515123</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 3020</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/18/2023 15:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ForcedEntryCode>N</ForcedEntryCode>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 3020</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 17:07:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/25/2023 03:53:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>16</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 17:12:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382852</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 17:12:39</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 17:12:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 17:12:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>16</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 17:12:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382853</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 17:12:39</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 17:12:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 17:12:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240019938</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>Coppermine 4 Seasons Recreational Center</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 17:14:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 17:14:06</UpdatorDate>
         <BusinessAddress>
            <AddressId>46499</AddressId>
            <StreetNumber>2710</StreetNumber>
            <StreetName>HAMPSTEAD MEXICO</StreetName>
            <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
            <City>HAMPSTEAD</City>
            <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
            <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            <Longitude>-76.89996262905439</Longitude>
            <Latitude>39.60893058502143</Latitude>
            <SubBeat>563</SubBeat>
            <AddressCommonName>
               <CommonPlaceName>FOUR SEASONS SPORTS COMPLEX</CommonPlaceName>
            </AddressCommonName>
            <AddressCommonName>
               <CommonPlaceName>IFO  FOUR SEASONS SPORTS COMPLEX</CommonPlaceName>
            </AddressCommonName>
         </BusinessAddress>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>1</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 17:16:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 17:16:11</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One pair of dark sunglasses</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>567</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>25</PropertyValue>
         <Value>25</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>251956</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/27/2023 04:50:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/27/2023 04:50:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/01/2023 08:03:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 04:50:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6579</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 02:05:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative:   On 07/27/2023 at approximately 0231 hours, I (TFC J. Reid #7215) responded back to Coppermine 4 Seasons for the report of two suspects attempting to gain access to the facility. TFC Adle #6906 and I responded. The caller advised she got an alert on her phone saying the security cameras at Coppermine detected motion. She advised she looked at the camera footage on her phone and saw two suspects attempting to enter the pool shed behind the property. She advised she remotely turned on the facilities flood lights remotly. She advised the suspects fled into the woods once the flood lights were turned on. The caller advised the two suspects appeared to be the same as the original suspects who entered the facility on 07/18/2023.   Upon our arrival, we requested the assistance of a K9 to attempt a track. Master Deputy C. Stonesife and his K9 partner K9 Rom responded. K9 Rom picked up a scent at the pool shed and began the track. The track led us to the woodline to the Northwest of the property. The K9 track led us through the wooded area and onto Cape Horn Rd. The K9 lost the scent on Cape Horn Rd. I made contact with the homeowner of 2650 Cape Horn Rd. The homeowner, an elderly woman, advised she and another male live at the property, but she advised the male that lives there is in his 60s, eliminating him as a potential suspect. Both suspects appear to be in their late teens, to early 20s. It was discovered there is a small business located directly next to the property, Sunset Bus Line which has surveillance cameras pointing at the property and roadway. An attempt to retrieve the camera footage will be attempted.   No property at Coppermine 4 Seasons was damaged, and all the doors to the facility were secure.   All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.   Case open pending further investigation.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 04:51:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/27/2023 05:12:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Karas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5562</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reid</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7215</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/10/2023 17:00:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/10/2023 17:00:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/23/2023 02:05:23</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6696</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/10/2023 17:00:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 02:05:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-025680  My body worn camera was operational and recording this incident.  Supplement Narrative:  On July 20, 2023, at approximately 0916 hours, I was dispatched to Coppermine 4 Seasons located at 2710 Hampstead Mexico Road, Hampstead, Carroll County, Maryland for the report of a burglary and theft.  Upon arriving on scene, I made contact with the General Manager of the facility who I identified by her name and date of birth as Jessica Marie Dannettel, W/F, DOB: 09/12/1980. Jessica stated that she had previously spoken with TFC Reid #7215 on July 18, 2023, to report a previous break in and theft from the suspected same two individuals. Jessica stated that the two individuals have keys to the facility because they leave the keys on the front desk for other employees to access different parts of the facility.  Jessica stated that those same two suspected individuals had broken in around 0130 hours the morning of July 20, 2023, and stole a couple items from the clothing store located within the facility. She stated that she was unsure what they stole but knew they were clothing products. Jessica also stated that they had thrown a few pool chairs into the pool located outside behind the facility. Jessica also stated that they threw a plant into the pool as well as the pool ladder, a wooden picnic table, and a couple of trashcans into the pool. The individuals also through a chair over the balcony onto the basketball courts inside the facility. Jessica stated that the locksmith came out and replaced the locks on all the main glass doors but not the rest of the doors of the facility because they had to respond back out another day. I walked through the facility with Jessica to better understand what was stolen and damaged. I also reviewed the video surveillance with Jessica. I asked Jessica if she was able to send me the video surveillance, but she stated that she would not be able to provide it to me right away, however, she did send it to me via email at a later time and I will attach the video surveillance to the report.  Jessica stated that they entered the facility from the back door to the basketball courts and threw a chair over the balcony onto the basketball courts. The two individuals then proceeded into the front lobby opened the cash register and stole a 5 dollar bill. They then proceeded into the clothing store and stole two unknown items that appeared to possibly be a pair of lulu-lemon leggings which are approximately $90 and a pair of Under Armor gym shorts which were approximately $40. Also, after reviewing the video surveillance I was able to identify what each individual was wearing. The first subject was wearing a black Under Armor hooded sweatshirt, black and red plaid pajama pants, and a dark-colored drawstring backpack. The second subject was wearing a purple hooded sweatshirt, gray sweatpants, and a black backpack. Both subjects were wearing some kind of mask covering a majority of their faces.  I received some additional information on July 21, 2023, from Jessica via email with the photos of all items that were thrown into the pool, which will be attached to the report. Jessica also stated that some of her employees possibly recognize one of the subjects by the name of Brenden Blair, W/M, DOB: 09/05/2003 with a possible address of 2610 Hoffman Mill Road, Hampstead, MD. That subject has a possible phone number of 410-339-2560.  All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6696</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/10/2023 17:02:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6696</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 01:40:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McCarty</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cade</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6579</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Iman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6696</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>