<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-003912</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/31/2023 11:11:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/31/2023 11:11:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/31/2023 10:25:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/31/2023 10:25:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Assist other in theft in progress and foot chase</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 11:11:25</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/01/2023 08:16:47</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>THT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>4889</AddressId>
      <City>MDC236</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 11:11:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 12:47:28</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>4889</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>6400</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Ridge</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Sykesville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21784</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.933995</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.397296</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WALMART</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IN FRONT OF JIMMY JOHNS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>DENNYS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/31/2023 11:11:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/31/2023 11:11:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>02/01/2023 08:16:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 11:11:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/01/2023 08:16:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>**Incident was captured on BWC and uploaded to Evidence.com**  ** Related to County Incident 23000475**  On 01/31/2023 at approximately 1025 hours, Carroll County Dispatched toned out a theft in progress at the Ulta located at 6400 Ridge Rd Sykesville MD. Due to proximity of the store, I advised Carroll County Dispatch that I was in the area and on scene shortly. I was informed that there was a black male in jean jacket, black hat and long dreads inside the store still about to check out with items in a bag which were not paid for. As I got on scene, I remained outside the store by the entrance. Once the suspect walked out of the store, I observed the above described male holding a black bag with his right hand. I requested him to walk back into the store to talk. After walking back into the store, I requested the male for identification. The male failed to provide me any identification upon my request. I asked for his name and date of birth. The male subject then provided me with the name of Keith Brown 08/04/78. I then reported that to Carroll Dispatch, which they were unable to locate that subject by the provided name and DOB. While talking to the male, he advised that he bought lotion, which he provided the bag and the receipt. I asked if he walked out of the store with any other item that was not purchased. He mentioned that there was something in his pocket. I then asked for that item and if that was all that was taken, it would only be a criminal citation. I advised that he would be released with a court date and paperwork, which he understood. As conversation continued, I asked again for anything with his name. He then stated that he has something in the black bag that was in his possession as he left the store. I then opened the bag and observed numerous items that were from Ulta. I then began to remove items from the bag and as I did so, the male took off running to the rear of the store. I continued to chase after the male, alerting the County Dispatch of his direction of travel. As I chased after the male suspect, I lost sight of him due to falling during the pursuit. I was later advised over the radio that other units were on scene and have him detained in front of Ulta in the parking lot. I then made contact with the responding deputies and identified the suspect as the suspect. At this point, Carroll County Sheriffs took over the investigation. This concludes my involvement in the investigation.  Case closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6185</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 12:48:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6185</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 13:13:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mcgee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2173</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reuschling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6185</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>